1	journal	NN	O	journal	nn	2	SENT_3	[p1l602t407r726b437],
2	homepage	NN	O	homepage	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l746t407r940b437],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l746t407r940b437],
4	www	NN	O	www	dep	2	SENT_3	[p1l960t407r1566b436],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l960t407r1566b436],

1	e	LS	O	e	dep	2	SENT_4	[p1l960t407r1566b436],
2	|	SYM	O	|	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l960t407r1566b436],
3	sevier.com/locate/palaeo	SYM	O	sevier.com/locate/palaeo	dep	2	SENT_4	[p1l960t407r1566b436],

1	Global	JJ	O	global	amod	3	SENT_5	[p1l6t569r166b614],
2	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	3	SENT_5	[p1l189t569r464b614],
3	zonation	NN	O	zonation	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l486t570r706b614],
4	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l729t569r799b614],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_5	[p1l819t569r899b614],
6	Pliensbachian	NNP	MISC	Pliensbachian	prep_for	3	SENT_5	[p1l922t569r1281b621],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l922t569r1281b621],
8	Toarcian	NNP	O	Toarcian	prep_for	3	SENT_5	[p1l1302t570r1520b614],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1542t569r1633b614],
10	Aalenian	NNP	MISC	Aalenian	conj_and	6	SENT_5	[p1l1654t569r1876b614],

1	Elizabeth	NNP	PERSON	Elizabeth	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l6t671r188b707],
2	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	1	SENT_6	[p1l202t673r231b707],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l202t673r231b707],

1	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l245t673r367b707],
2	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l377t670r401b713],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l377t670r401b713],
4	Spela	NNP	PERSON	Spela	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l416t663r520b716],
5	Gorican	NNP	PERSON	Gorican	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l533t671r686b707],
6	b	NN	O	b	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l698t663r757b713],
7	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l698t663r757b713],
8	*	NN	O	*	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l698t663r757b713],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l698t663r757b713],
10	Jean	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Jean	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l766t673r853b716],
11	Guex	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Guex	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l867t673r969b707],
12	C	NNP	ORGANIZATION	C	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l980t670r1003b712],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l980t670r1003b712],
14	Luis	NNP	PERSON	Luis	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1017t672r1093b707],
15	_	VBD	O	_	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1103t671r1333b721],
16	O'Dogherty	NN	O	o'dogherty	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1103t671r1333b721],
17	d	NN	O	d	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1344t663r1371b712],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1344t663r1371b712],
19	Patrick	NNP	PERSON	Patrick	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1385t671r1522b707],
20	De	NNP	PERSON	De	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1535t673r1586b707],
21	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1597t673r1731b707],
22	6	CD	NUMBER	6	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1742t670r1766b713],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1742t670r1766b713],
24	Paulian	NNP	PERSON	Paulian	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1780t671r1925b707],
25	Dumitrica	NNP	PERSON	Dumitrica	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1939t672r2136b707],
26	f	LS	O	f	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t717r23b766],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l6t717r23b766],
28	Rie	NNP	PERSON	Rie	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l37t726r97b761],
29	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l115t727r144b761],
30	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l163t726r247b761],
31	g	NN	O	g	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l259t724r284b766],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l259t724r284b766],
33	Atsushi	NNP	PERSON	Atsushi	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l301t725r448b761],
34	Matsuoka	NNP	PERSON	Matsuoka	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l466t725r660b761],
35	?	NN	O	?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l672t717r699b766],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l672t717r699b766],
37	Patricia	NNP	PERSON	Patricia	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l717t726r864b761],
38	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l879t727r917b761],
39	Whalen	NNP	PERSON	Whalen	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l933t724r1108b761],
40	?	NN	O	?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l933t724r1108b761],
41	3	CD	NUMBER	3	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t800r15b811],
42	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l26t802r166b828],
43	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l175t801r200b828],
44	Geology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geology	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l206t801r302b828],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l206t801r302b828],
46	Portland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Portland	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l313t801r411b823],
47	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	State	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l421t802r478b823],
48	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l490t801r610b828],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l490t801r610b828],
50	Portland	NNP	LOCATION	Portland	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l621t801r724b826],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l621t801r724b826],
52	OR	NN	LOCATION	or	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l736t802r768b823],
53	97207-0751	CD	NUMBER	97207-0751	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l778t802r924b826],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l778t802r924b826],
55	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l937t802r981b823],
56	b	NN	O	b	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t832r17b846],
57	Paleontoloski	NNP	PERSON	Paleontoloski	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l27t837r181b859],
58	institut	NN	O	institut	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l191t837r275b858],
59	lvana	NN	O	lvana	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l283t838r346b859],
60	Rakovca	NN	PERSON	rakovca	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l357t837r457b862],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l357t837r457b862],
62	ZRC	NNP	O	ZRC	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l467t838r514b859],
63	SAZU	NNP	O	SAZU	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l521t837r586b862],
64	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l521t837r586b862],
65	Novi	NNP	O	Novi	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l597t837r650b859],
66	trg	NN	O	trg	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l661t840r694b864],
67	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l701t838r720b862],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l701t838r720b862],
69	51-1000	CD	NUMBER	51-1000	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l731t838r821b859],
70	Ljubljana	NNP	LOCATION	Ljubljana	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l830t836r942b864],
71	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l830t836r942b864],
72	Slovenia	NNP	LOCATION	Slovenia	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l952t837r1049b859],
73	?	NNP	O	?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t871r15b881],
74	Institut	NNP	O	Institut	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l25t872r110b894],
75	de	IN	O	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l119t872r145b894],
76	G?ologie	NNP	O	G?ologie	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l156t871r253b899],
77	et	FW	O	et	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l263t875r285b894],
78	Pal?ontologie	NNP	O	Pal?ontologie	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l293t871r453b899],
79	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l293t871r453b899],
80	Universit?	NNP	O	Universit?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l465t871r580b894],
81	de	IN	O	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l590t872r616b894],
82	Lausanne	NNP	LOCATION	Lausanne	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l626t873r740b897],
83	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l626t873r740b897],
84	CH	NN	O	ch	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l752t873r853b894],
85	?	CD	NUMBER	?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l752t873r853b894],
86	1015	CD	DATE	1015	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l752t873r853b894],
87	Lausanne	NNP	LOCATION	Lausanne	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l863t873r977b897],
88	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l863t873r977b897],
89	Switzerland	NNP	LOCATION	Switzerland	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l987t872r1124b894],
90	d	NN	O	d	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t902r17b917],
91	Departamento	NNP	O	Departamento	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l28t908r194b934],
92	de	IN	O	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l205t907r231b929],
93	Ciencias	NNP	O	Ciencias	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l242t907r335b929],
94	de	FW	O	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l345t907r371b929],
95	la	FW	O	la	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l382t907r401b929],
96	Tierra	FW	O	tierra	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l412t907r484b932],
97	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l412t907r484b932],
98	Facultad	NNP	O	Facultad	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l495t907r593b929],
99	de	IN	O	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l603t907r629b929],
100	Ciencias	NNP	O	Ciencias	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l640t907r733b929],
101	del	NNP	O	del	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l743t907r777b929],
102	Mar	NNP	DATE	Mar	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l786t908r838b932],
103	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l786t908r838b932],
104	Universidad	NNP	O	Universidad	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l851t907r987b929],
105	de	IN	O	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l998t907r1024b929],
106	Cadiz	NNP	LOCATION	Cadiz	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1034t906r1101b932],
107	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1034t906r1101b932],
108	Campus	NNP	PERSON	Campus	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1113t908r1204b934],
109	Rio	NNP	PERSON	Rio	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1214t906r1249b929],
110	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1259t908r1276b929],
111	Pedro	NNP	PERSON	Pedro	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1287t907r1357b932],
112	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1287t907r1357b932],
113	11510	CD	NUMBER	11510	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1371t908r1441b929],
114	Puerto	NNP	O	Puerto	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1450t908r1525b929],
115	Real	NNP	O	Real	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1535t907r1588b932],
116	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1535t907r1588b932],
117	Cadiz	NNP	LOCATION	Cadiz	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1600t906r1666b932],
118	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1600t906r1666b932],
119	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1677t907r1741b934],
120	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t942r15b952],
121	D?partement	NNP	ORGANIZATION	D?partement	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l27t942r179b970],
122	Histoire	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Histoire	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l187t943r278b964],
123	de	FW	ORGANIZATION	de	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l288t943r314b964],
124	la	FW	ORGANIZATION	la	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l324t942r344b964],
125	Terre	FW	ORGANIZATION	terre	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l354t944r417b968],
126	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l354t944r417b968],
127	Mus?um	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mus?um	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l428t942r527b964],
128	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l537t943r637b964],
129	d'Histoire	NNP	ORGANIZATION	d'Histoire	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l647t942r757b964],
130	Naturelle	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Naturelle	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l766t943r878b968],
131	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l766t943r878b968],
132	43	CD	NUMBER	43	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l888t944r917b964],
133	rue	NN	O	rue	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l927t949r964b965],
134	Buffon	NNP	PERSON	Buffon	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l974t942r1053b970],
135	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l974t942r1053b970],
136	F-75005	NNP	O	F-75005	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1064t944r1160b964],
137	Paris	NNP	LOCATION	Paris	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1170t943r1231b968],
138	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1170t943r1231b968],
139	France	NNP	LOCATION	France	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1241t944r1318b964],
140	?	CD	NUMBER	?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l7t973r14b987],
141	Dennigkofenweg	NNP	O	Dennigkofenweg	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l23t978r217b1005],
142	33	CD	NUMBER	33	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l225t979r258b1003],
143	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l225t979r258b1003],
144	CH	NN	O	ch	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l270t979r372b1000],
145	?	CD	NUMBER	?	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l270t979r372b1000],
146	3073	CD	NUMBER	3073	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l270t979r372b1000],
147	Guemligen	NNP	O	Guemligen	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l382t978r510b1005],
148	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l382t978r510b1005],
149	Switzerland	NNP	LOCATION	Switzerland	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l520t978r657b1000],
150	5	CD	NUMBER	5	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l6t1013r16b1027],
151	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l27t1015r167b1040],
152	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l176t1013r201b1040],
153	Earth	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Earth	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l206t1013r267b1035],
154	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l277t1014r377b1038],
155	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l277t1014r377b1038],
156	Faculty	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Faculty	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l388t1013r471b1040],
157	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l482t1013r507b1040],
158	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l511t1014r601b1038],
159	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l511t1014r601b1038],
160	Ehime	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ehime	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l612t1013r683b1035],
161	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l694t1014r815b1040],
162	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l694t1014r815b1040],
163	Matsuyama	NNP	PERSON	Matsuyama	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l826t1015r962b1040],
164	790-8577	CD	NUMBER	790-8577	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l974t1014r1090b1038],
165	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l974t1014r1090b1038],
166	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1096t1015r1165b1040],
167	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l7t1044r17b1058],
168	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l7t1044r17b1058],
169	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l28t1050r168b1076],
170	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l177t1048r202b1076],
171	Geology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geology	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l208t1048r304b1076],
172	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l208t1048r304b1076],
173	Faculty	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Faculty	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l315t1049r398b1076],
174	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l409t1048r434b1076],
175	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l438t1049r527b1074],
176	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l438t1049r527b1074],
177	Niigata	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Niigata	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l538t1049r621b1076],
178	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l633t1049r754b1076],
179	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l633t1049r754b1076],
180	Niigata	NNP	LOCATION	Niigata	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l765t1049r848b1076],
181	950-2181	CD	NUMBER	950-2181	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l859t1050r976b1074],
182	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l859t1050r976b1074],
183	japan	NN	LOCATION	japan	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l982t1050r1051b1076],
184	i	FW	O	i	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l7t1079r11b1093],
185	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l22t1085r162b1110],
186	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l171t1083r196b1110],
187	Geosciences	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geosciences	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l202t1084r343b1108],
188	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l202t1084r343b1108],
189	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l355t1084r472b1110],
190	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l482t1083r507b1110],
191	Arkansas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Arkansas	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l510t1083r621b1108],
192	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l510t1083r621b1108],
193	118	CD	NUMBER	118	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l635t1085r675b1105],
194	Ozark	NNP	O	Ozark	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l686t1083r752b1105],
195	Hall	NNP	O	Hall	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l761t1083r813b1108],
196	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l761t1083r813b1108],
197	Fayetteville	NNP	LOCATION	Fayetteville	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l823t1083r960b1110],
198	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l823t1083r960b1110],
199	AR	NN	O	ar	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l969t1084r1002b1105],
200	72701	CD	NUMBER	72701	dep	202	SENT_7	[p1l1013t1085r1088b1108],
201	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1013t1085r1088b1108],
202	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	_	0	SENT_7	[p1l1101t1084r1145b1105],

1	ARTICLE	NN	O	article	_	0	SENT_8	[p1l6t1220r230b1242],
2	INFO	NN	O	info	nn	3	SENT_8	[p1l278t1220r401b1242],
3	ABSTRACT	NN	O	abstract	dep	1	SENT_8	[p1l691t1220r960b1242],

1	Article	NNP	O	Article	nn	2	SENT_9	[p1l6t1295r82b1317],
2	l1iSf0Ty	NNP	O	l1iSf0Ty	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l104t1295r190b1322],
3	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l104t1295r190b1322],
4	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	6	SENT_9	[p1l104t1295r190b1322],
5	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	amod	6	SENT_9	[p1l713t1297r818b1327],
6	radiolarians	NNS	O	radiolarian	dep	2	SENT_9	[p1l845t1297r1004b1321],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1031t1297r1095b1321],
8	220	CD	NUMBER	220	num	9	SENT_9	[p1l1122t1298r1171b1321],
9	samples	NNS	O	sample	prep_from	6	SENT_9	[p1l1199t1297r1307b1327],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1334t1297r1359b1321],
11	Queen	NNP	LOCATION	Queen	nn	13	SENT_9	[p1l1386t1298r1472b1326],
12	Charlotte	NNP	LOCATION	Charlotte	nn	13	SENT_9	[p1l1499t1297r1623b1321],
13	Islands	NNP	LOCATION	Islands	prep_in	9	SENT_9	[p1l1650t1297r1749b1325],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1650t1297r1749b1325],
15	B.C.	NNP	LOCATION	B.C.	appos	13	SENT_9	[p1l1776t1298r1830b1325],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l1776t1298r1830b1325],
17	Williston	NNP	LOCATION	Williston	nn	18	SENT_9	[p1l1856t1297r1980b1321],
18	Lake	NNP	LOCATION	Lake	appos	13	SENT_9	[p1l2007t1297r2073b1325],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l2007t1297r2073b1325],
20	B.C.	NNP	O	B.C.	appos	13	SENT_9	[p1l2101t1298r2154b1325],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l2101t1298r2154b1325],
22	east-central	JJ	O	east-central	appos	13	SENT_9	[p1l6t1337r165b1361],
23	Received	VBN	O	receive	rcmod	6	SENT_9	[p1l7t1365r113b1387],
24	21	CD	DATE	21	num	25	SENT_9	[p1l124t1366r150b1387],
25	January	NNP	DATE	January	nsubj	38	SENT_9	[p1l160t1366r255b1392],
26	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	25	SENT_9	[p1l265t1366r324b1387],
27	Received	VBN	O	receive	partmod	25	SENT_9	[p1l7t1401r113b1423],
28	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_9	[p1l125t1401r146b1423],
29	revised	JJ	O	revised	amod	30	SENT_9	[p1l157t1401r243b1423],
30	form	NN	O	form	prep_in	27	SENT_9	[p1l254t1401r311b1423],
31	14	CD	DATE	14	num	30	SENT_9	[p1l323t1402r351b1422],
32	August	NNP	DATE	August	tmod	30	SENT_9	[p1l360t1402r445b1428],
33	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	32	SENT_9	[p1l455t1402r514b1423],
34	Accepted	JJ	O	accepted	amod	35	SENT_9	[p1l6t1437r116b1464],
35	29	CD	DATE	29	tmod	27	SENT_9	[p1l127t1438r156b1459],
36	August	NNP	DATE	August	dep	35	SENT_9	[p1l166t1438r251b1464],
37	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	36	SENT_9	[p1l260t1438r320b1459],
38	Available	JJ	O	available	xcomp	23	SENT_9	[p1l6t1473r117b1494],
39	online	NN	O	online	prep	23	SENT_9	[p1l127t1473r202b1494],
40	29	CD	DATE	29	dep	39	SENT_9	[p1l213t1474r241b1494],
41	September	NNP	DATE	September	tmod	23	SENT_9	[p1l252t1473r382b1500],
42	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	41	SENT_9	[p1l392t1474r451b1494],

1	Oregon	NNP	LOCATION	Oregon	nsubjpass	22	SENT_10	[p1l6t1591r110b1620],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l6t1591r110b1620],
3	Baja	NNP	LOCATION	Baja	nn	5	SENT_10	[p1l127t1590r182b1620],
4	California	NNP	LOCATION	California	nn	5	SENT_10	[p1l198t1590r327b1614],
5	Sur	NNP	LOCATION	Sur	appos	1	SENT_10	[p1l343t1591r393b1618],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l343t1591r393b1618],
7	southern	JJ	O	southern	amod	8	SENT_10	[p1l409t1590r529b1614],
8	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	appos	1	SENT_10	[p1l545t1590r625b1620],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l545t1590r625b1620],
10	Austria	NNP	LOCATION	Austria	appos	1	SENT_10	[p1l640t1590r743b1618],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l640t1590r743b1618],
12	Slovenia	NNP	LOCATION	Slovenia	conj_and	10	SENT_10	[p1l759t1590r879b1618],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l759t1590r879b1618],
14	Turkey	NNP	LOCATION	Turkey	conj_and	10	SENT_10	[p1l894t1590r994b1620],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l894t1590r994b1620],
16	Oman	NNP	LOCATION	Oman	conj_and	10	SENT_10	[p1l1011t1591r1097b1618],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1011t1591r1097b1618],
18	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	Japan	conj_and	10	SENT_10	[p1l1110t1591r1187b1620],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1202t1590r1251b1614],
20	Argentina	NNP	LOCATION	Argentina	conj_and	10	SENT_10	[p1l1266t1590r1400b1620],
21	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_10	[p1l1415t1597r1483b1614],
22	studied	VBN	O	study	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l6t1630r105b1654],
23	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l121t1630r145b1654],
24	order	NN	O	order	prep_in	22	SENT_10	[p1l161t1630r234b1654],
25	to	TO	O	to	aux	26	SENT_10	[p1l248t1633r274b1654],
26	construct	VB	O	construct	xcomp	22	SENT_10	[p1l290t1633r416b1654],
27	global	JJ	O	global	amod	28	SENT_10	[p1l430t1630r511b1660],
28	zonation	NN	O	zonation	dobj	26	SENT_10	[p1l527t1630r644b1654],
29	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l660t1630r697b1654],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_10	[p1l711t1630r754b1654],
31	Pliensbachian	NNP	MISC	Pliensbachian	prep_for	26	SENT_10	[p1l769t1630r961b1658],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l769t1630r961b1658],
33	Toarcian	NNP	O	Toarcian	prep_for	26	SENT_10	[p1l976t1630r1092b1654],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1107t1630r1156b1654],
35	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	36	SENT_10	[p1l1171t1630r1289b1654],
36	stages	NNS	O	stage	prep_for	26	SENT_10	[p1l1304t1633r1393b1660],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_10	[p1l1304t1633r1393b1660],

1	Well	UH	O	well	dep	5	SENT_11	[p1l1407t1630r1482b1654],
2	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1407t1630r1482b1654],
3	Ilizlgi/gl	NN	O	ilizlgi/gl	nn	4	SENT_11	[p1l1599t1611r1720b1668],
4	?is?	NN	O	?is?	nsubj	5	SENT_11	[p1l1599t1611r1720b1668],
5	preserved	VBD	O	preserve	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l6t1670r139b1700],
6	faunas	NNS	O	fauna	dobj	5	SENT_11	[p1l149t1670r235b1694],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l244t1670r309b1694],
8	continuous	JJ	O	continuous	amod	10	SENT_11	[p1l317t1670r467b1694],
9	stratigraphic	JJ	O	stratigraphic	amod	10	SENT_11	[p1l476t1670r647b1700],
10	sections	NNS	O	section	prep_from	5	SENT_11	[p1l656t1670r764b1694],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l773t1670r798b1694],
12	Queen	NNP	LOCATION	Queen	nn	14	SENT_11	[p1l806t1671r893b1699],
13	Charlotte	NNP	LOCATION	Charlotte	nn	14	SENT_11	[p1l901t1670r1025b1694],
14	Islands	NNP	LOCATION	Islands	prep_in	10	SENT_11	[p1l1035t1670r1127b1694],
15	provide	VB	O	provide	dep	5	SENT_11	[p1l1136t1670r1239b1700],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_11	[p1l1248t1670r1291b1694],
17	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	18	SENT_11	[p1l1300t1673r1367b1694],
18	detailed	JJ	O	detailed	iobj	15	SENT_11	[p1l1374t1670r1482b1694],
19	Lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	21	SENT_11	[p1l1600t1684r1674b1704],
20	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	amod	21	SENT_11	[p1l1680t1683r1774b1709],
21	record	NN	O	record	dobj	15	SENT_11	[p1l6t1709r92b1734],
22	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l103t1709r141b1734],
23	this	DT	O	this	det	25	SENT_11	[p1l150t1710r199b1734],
24	time	NN	O	time	nn	25	SENT_11	[p1l209t1710r270b1734],
25	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_for	21	SENT_11	[p1l281t1710r391b1737],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l281t1710r391b1737],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l402t1710r451b1734],
28	all	DT	O	all	det	29	SENT_11	[p1l461t1710r492b1734],
29	collections	NNS	O	collection	nsubjpass	31	SENT_11	[p1l503t1710r646b1734],
30	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	31	SENT_11	[p1l657t1717r698b1734],
31	tied	VBN	O	tie	conj_and	5	SENT_11	[p1l708t1710r759b1734],
32	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l770t1713r796b1734],
33	North	JJ	MISC	north	amod	36	SENT_11	[p1l806t1710r884b1734],
34	American	JJ	MISC	american	amod	36	SENT_11	[p1l893t1710r1024b1734],
35	ammonite	JJ	O	ammonite	amod	36	SENT_11	[p1l1034t1710r1172b1734],
36	zones	NNS	O	zone	prep_to	31	SENT_11	[p1l1183t1717r1259b1734],
37	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1270t1717r1298b1734],
38	assemblages	NNS	O	assemblage	prep_to	31	SENT_11	[p1l1307t1710r1482b1740],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l1307t1710r1482b1740],

1	Middle	NNP	O	Middle	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1600t1718r1683b1740],
2	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l1691t1719r1784b1745],

1	Collections	NNS	O	collection	nsubj	7	SENT_13	[p1l7t1820r154b1844],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l169t1820r234b1844],
3	nearly	RB	O	nearly	quantmod	4	SENT_13	[p1l248t1820r333b1850],
4	all	DT	O	all	num	6	SENT_13	[p1l347t1820r377b1844],
5	other	JJ	O	other	amod	6	SENT_13	[p1l392t1820r465b1844],
6	areas	NNS	O	area	prep_from	1	SENT_13	[p1l478t1827r548b1844],
7	lack	VBP	O	lack	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l563t1820r616b1844],
8	independent	JJ	O	independent	acomp	7	SENT_13	[p1l630t1820r802b1850],
9	dating	VBG	O	date	dep	8	SENT_13	[p1l817t1820r902b1850],
10	except	IN	O	except	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l916t1824r1006b1850],
11	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l1019t1820r1057b1844],
12	early	JJ	O	early	amod	14	SENT_13	[p1l1071t1820r1137b1850],
13	Toarcian	JJ	MISC	toarcian	amod	14	SENT_13	[p1l1150t1821r1266b1844],
14	carbon-isotope	NN	O	carbon-isotope	prep_except_for	9	SENT_13	[p1l1281t1820r1484b1850],
15	dating	VBG	O	date	partmod	14	SENT_13	[p1l7t1860r93b1890],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l103t1860r128b1884],
17	Slovenia	NNP	LOCATION	Slovenia	prep_in	15	SENT_13	[p1l139t1860r252b1884],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l263t1860r312b1884],
19	late	JJ	O	late	amod	21	SENT_13	[p1l323t1860r371b1884],
20	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	21	SENT_13	[p1l381t1860r500b1884],
21	ammonites	NNS	O	ammonite	prep_in	15	SENT_13	[p1l511t1860r662b1884],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l673t1860r698b1884],
23	Spain	NNP	LOCATION	Spain	prep_in	15	SENT_13	[p1l709t1861r789b1890],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l709t1861r789b1890],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_14	[p1l6t1901r26b1924],
2	database	NN	O	database	nsubj	6	SENT_14	[p1l33t1900r147b1924],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l155t1900r182b1924],
4	197	CD	NUMBER	197	prep_of	2	SENT_14	[p1l188t1901r235b1924],
5	widely	RB	O	widely	advmod	6	SENT_14	[p1l243t1900r332b1930],
6	distributed	VBN	O	distribute	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l339t1900r481b1924],
7	updated	VBN	O	update	amod	9	SENT_14	[p1l489t1900r596b1930],
8	taxonomic	JJ	O	taxonomic	amod	9	SENT_14	[p1l604t1901r742b1924],
9	species	NNS	O	species	dobj	6	SENT_14	[p1l750t1900r842b1930],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_14	[p1l850t1907r901b1924],
11	used	VBN	O	use	rcmod	9	SENT_14	[p1l909t1900r970b1924],
12	to	TO	O	to	aux	13	SENT_14	[p1l977t1904r1003b1924],
13	construct	VB	O	construct	xcomp	11	SENT_14	[p1l1011t1904r1133b1924],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_14	[p1l1140t1907r1153b1924],
15	Unitary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Unitary	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1161t1900r1259b1930],
16	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Association	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1265t1900r1413b1924],
17	(	NN	O	(	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1423t1900r1483b1930],
18	UA	NN	ORGANIZATION	ua	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1423t1900r1483b1930],
19	)	NN	O	)	nn	20	SENT_14	[p1l1423t1900r1483b1930],
20	zonation	NN	O	zonation	dobj	13	SENT_14	[p1l7t1940r120b1964],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l128t1940r164b1964],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_14	[p1l171t1940r213b1964],
23	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_for	20	SENT_14	[p1l220t1940r326b1964],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l220t1940r326b1964],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_15	[p1l333t1941r352b1964],
2	global	JJ	O	global	amod	3	SENT_15	[p1l359t1940r437b1970],
3	sequence	NN	O	sequence	nsubjpass	8	SENT_15	[p1l445t1947r566b1970],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l573t1940r601b1964],
5	41	CD	NUMBER	41	num	6	SENT_15	[p1l604t1941r633b1964],
6	UAs	NNS	O	ua	prep_of	3	SENT_15	[p1l644t1941r695b1964],
7	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_15	[p1l702t1947r753b1964],
8	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l762t1940r876b1964],
9	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l884t1940r920b1964],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_15	[p1l926t1940r968b1964],
11	top	NN	O	top	prep_for	8	SENT_15	[p1l975t1943r1018b1970],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1026t1940r1053b1964],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_15	[p1l1057t1940r1099b1964],
14	Sinemurian	JJ	MISC	sinemurian	prep_of	11	SENT_15	[p1l1107t1940r1256b1964],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1264t1943r1289b1964],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_15	[p1l1297t1940r1338b1964],
17	base	NN	O	base	prep_to	8	SENT_15	[p1l1346t1940r1403b1964],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1411t1940r1439b1964],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_15	[p1l1443t1940r1484b1964],
20	Biochronology	NNP	MISC	Biochronology	nn	21	SENT_15	[p1l6t1978r180b2005],
21	Bajocian	NNP	MISC	Bajocian	prep_of	17	SENT_15	[p1l694t1975r808b2004],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l694t1975r808b2004],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_16	[p1l825t1974r874b1998],
2	?rst	NN	O	?rst	nsubj	14	SENT_16	[p1l892t1974r943b1998],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l960t1974r1008b1998],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_16	[p1l1026t1974r1068b1998],
5	last	JJ	O	last	amod	6	SENT_16	[p1l1086t1974r1131b1998],
6	UAs	NNS	O	ua	conj_and	2	SENT_16	[p1l1148t1975r1199b1998],
7	represent	VBP	O	represent	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1218t1978r1342b2004],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_16	[p1l1359t1974r1400b1998],
9	Late	JJ	MISC	late	amod	10	SENT_16	[p1l1419t1976r1471b1998],
10	Sinemurian	JJ	MISC	sinemurian	dobj	7	SENT_16	[p1l1489t1975r1639b1998],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1657t1974r1705b1998],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_16	[p1l1723t1974r1764b1998],
13	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	14	SENT_16	[p1l1783t1974r1848b2004],
14	Bajocian	JJ	MISC	bajocian	conj_and	7	SENT_16	[p1l1865t1975r1974b2004],
15	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	14	SENT_16	[p1l1993t1974r2154b2004],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1993t1974r2154b2004],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_17	[p1l6t2013r54b2037],
2	Unitary	JJ	O	unitary	amod	3	SENT_17	[p1l68t2013r158b2040],
3	Associations	NNS	O	association	nsubjpass	8	SENT_17	[p1l167t2013r315b2035],
4	remaining	VBG	O	remain	partmod	3	SENT_17	[p1l754t2013r888b2043],
5	39	CD	NUMBER	39	num	6	SENT_17	[p1l900t2014r932b2037],
6	UAs	NNS	O	ua	dobj	4	SENT_17	[p1l946t2014r997b2037],
7	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_17	[p1l1010t2020r1076b2037],
8	merged	VBN	O	merge	dep	12	SENT_17	[p1l1090t2013r1189b2043],
9	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1203t2013r1254b2037],
10	nine	CD	NUMBER	nine	num	11	SENT_17	[p1l1268t2013r1325b2037],
11	zones	NNS	O	zone	prep_into	8	SENT_17	[p1l1338t2020r1412b2037],
12	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1427t2013r1492b2043],
13	four	CD	NUMBER	four	dobj	12	SENT_17	[p1l1427t2013r1492b2043],
14	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	15	SENT_17	[p1l1505t2013r1571b2043],
15	Pliensbachian	NN	MISC	pliensbachian	nsubj	12	SENT_17	[p1l1583t2013r1767b2041],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1583t2013r1767b2041],
17	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	19	SENT_17	[p1l1781t2020r1828b2037],
18	Late	JJ	O	late	amod	19	SENT_17	[p1l1843t2015r1895b2037],
19	Pliensbachian	NN	O	pliensbachian	appos	15	SENT_17	[p1l1909t2013r2093b2041],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1909t2013r2093b2041],
21	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	23	SENT_17	[p1l2107t2020r2154b2037],
22	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	23	SENT_17	[p1l6t2053r72b2083],
23	Toarcian	NN	MISC	toarcian	appos	15	SENT_17	[p1l6t2092r124b2120],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l6t2092r124b2120],
25	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	26	SENT_17	[p1l141t2099r189b2116],
26	Middle	NN	O	middle	appos	15	SENT_17	[p1l206t2092r368b2116],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l206t2092r368b2116],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l206t2092r368b2116],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l206t2092r368b2116],

1	Late	RB	MISC	late	advmod	2	SENT_19	[p1l206t2092r368b2116],
2	Toarcian	NNP	MISC	Toarcian	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l384t2092r502b2120],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l384t2092r502b2120],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l520t2092r568b2116],
5	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	7	SENT_19	[p1l585t2096r635b2116],
6	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	7	SENT_19	[p1l652t2092r776b2122],
7	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	2	SENT_19	[p1l652t2092r776b2122],
8	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l796t2092r923b2122],
9	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	7	SENT_19	[p1l939t2096r965b2116],
10	prominent	JJ	O	prominent	amod	13	SENT_19	[p1l982t2092r1122b2122],
11	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	13	SENT_19	[p1l1139t2092r1280b2116],
12	faunal	JJ	O	faunal	amod	13	SENT_19	[p1l1297t2092r1376b2116],
13	breaks	NNS	O	break	pobj	7	SENT_19	[p1l1393t2092r1478b2116],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1496t2092r1544b2116],
15	ammonite	JJ	O	ammonite	amod	16	SENT_19	[p1l1563t2093r1697b2116],
16	data	NNS	O	datum	conj_and	13	SENT_19	[p1l1720t2092r1781b2117],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1720t2092r1781b2117],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_20	[p1l1803t2092r1851b2116],
2	new	JJ	O	new	amod	3	SENT_20	[p1l1875t2099r1932b2116],
3	zones	NNS	O	zone	nsubj	10	SENT_20	[p1l1953t2099r2027b2116],
4	are	VBP	O	be	cop	10	SENT_20	[p1l2050t2099r2090b2116],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_20	[p1l2113t2092r2154b2116],
6	Canutus	NN	MISC	canutus	nn	10	SENT_20	[p1l6t2132r107b2156],
7	tipperi	NN	O	tipperus	nn	10	SENT_20	[p1l134t2132r215b2162],
8	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	10	SENT_20	[p1l241t2146r256b2148],
9	Katroma	NN	O	katroma	nn	10	SENT_20	[p1l282t2133r391b2156],
10	clara	NN	O	clara	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l418t2131r479b2156],
11	Zone	NNP	O	Zone	amod	10	SENT_20	[p1l505t2133r569b2156],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_20	[p1l598t2131r679b2162],
13	latest	JJS	O	latest	dep	11	SENT_20	[p1l598t2131r679b2162],
14	Sinemurian/earliest	JJ	O	sinemurian/earliest	amod	16	SENT_20	[p1l705t2131r961b2160],
15	Pliensbachian	JJ	O	pliensbachian	amod	16	SENT_20	[p1l984t2131r1182b2162],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	13	SENT_20	[p1l984t2131r1182b2162],
17	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l984t2131r1182b2162],
18	Zartus	NNP	O	Zartus	dep	13	SENT_20	[p1l1201t2133r1281b2156],
19	mostlen	JJS	O	mostlen	dep	18	SENT_20	[p1l1301t2131r1402b2156],
20	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	22	SENT_20	[p1l1421t2146r1435b2148],
21	Pseudoristola	NN	O	pseudoristolum	nn	22	SENT_20	[p1l1455t2131r1621b2156],
22	megaglobosa	NN	O	megaglobosa	dep	18	SENT_20	[p1l1640t2131r1808b2162],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1640t2131r1808b2162],
24	Hsuum	NN	O	hsuum	nn	25	SENT_20	[p1l1827t2133r1916b2156],
25	mulleri	NNS	O	mullerus	appos	13	SENT_20	[p1l1936t2131r2024b2156],
26	?	VBP	O	?	rcmod	25	SENT_20	[p1l2043t2146r2058b2148],
27	Trillus	JJ	O	trillus	amod	28	SENT_20	[p1l2079t2131r2154b2156],
28	elkhomensis	NN	O	elkhomensis	nsubj	36	SENT_20	[p1l6t2171r161b2195],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l176t2171r223b2195],
30	Gigi	NN	PERSON	gigus	nn	35	SENT_20	[p1l239t2172r288b2201],
31	fustis	NN	O	fusti	nn	35	SENT_20	[p1l293t2171r362b2201],
32	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	35	SENT_20	[p1l378t2185r392b2188],
33	Lantus	NNP	MISC	Lantus	nn	35	SENT_20	[p1l411t2172r497b2195],
34	sixi	NN	O	sixus	nn	35	SENT_20	[p1l520t2171r563b2195],
35	zones	NNS	O	zone	nsubj	36	SENT_20	[p1l587t2178r663b2195],
36	(	VBP	O	(	ccomp	26	SENT_20	[p1l690t2171r769b2201],
37	Early	JJ	O	early	amod	39	SENT_20	[p1l690t2171r769b2201],
38	Pliensbachian	JJ	O	pliensbachian	amod	39	SENT_20	[p1l793t2171r999b2201],
39	)	NN	O	)	dobj	36	SENT_20	[p1l793t2171r999b2201],
40	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l793t2171r999b2201],
41	Eucyrtidiellum	NN	O	eucyrtidiellum	dep	25	SENT_20	[p1l1024t2171r1212b2201],
42	nagaiae	FW	O	nagaiae	nn	41	SENT_20	[p1l1237t2171r1337b2201],
43	?	FW	O	?	nn	41	SENT_20	[p1l1362t2185r1377b2188],
44	Praeparvicingula	FW	O	praeparvicingula	nn	41	SENT_20	[p1l1401t2171r1620b2201],
45	tlellensis	FW	O	tlellensis	dep	41	SENT_20	[p1l1646t2171r1756b2195],
46	Zone	NNP	O	Zone	dep	41	SENT_20	[p1l1779t2172r1845b2195],
47	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	46	SENT_20	[p1l1872t2171r1937b2201],
48	Late	JJ	O	late	amod	50	SENT_20	[p1l1872t2171r1937b2201],
49	Pliensbachian	JJ	O	pliensbachian	amod	50	SENT_20	[p1l1956t2171r2154b2201],
50	)	NN	O	)	dep	41	SENT_20	[p1l1956t2171r2154b2201],
51	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1956t2171r2154b2201],
52	Napora	NNP	O	Napora	dep	25	SENT_20	[p1l6t2212r99b2241],
53	relica	NN	O	relica	nn	56	SENT_20	[p1l109t2210r176b2235],
54	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	56	SENT_20	[p1l186t2225r201b2227],
55	Eucyrtidiellum	NN	O	eucyrtidiellum	nn	56	SENT_20	[p1l210t2210r391b2241],
56	disparile	NN	O	disparile	dep	52	SENT_20	[p1l402t2210r507b2241],
57	Zone	NNP	O	Zone	nn	61	SENT_20	[p1l516t2212r580b2235],
58	(	NNP	O	(	nn	61	SENT_20	[p1l592t2210r669b2241],
59	Early	NNP	O	Early	nn	61	SENT_20	[p1l592t2210r669b2241],
60	Toarcian	NNP	O	Toarcian	nn	61	SENT_20	[p1l677t2210r809b2241],
61	)	NN	O	)	dep	52	SENT_20	[p1l677t2210r809b2241],
62	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l677t2210r809b2241],
63	Elodiam	NN	O	elodiam	nn	64	SENT_20	[p1l820t2210r922b2235],
64	pessagnoi	NN	O	pessagnous	dep	25	SENT_20	[p1l930t2211r1054b2241],
65	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	67	SENT_20	[p1l1064t2225r1078b2227],
66	Hexasaturnalis	NN	O	hexasaturnali	nn	67	SENT_20	[p1l1088t2210r1274b2235],
67	hexagonus	NN	O	hexagonus	dep	64	SENT_20	[p1l1288t2210r1420b2241],
68	Zone	NNP	O	Zone	nn	70	SENT_20	[p1l1428t2212r1492b2235],
69	(	NNP	O	(	nn	70	SENT_20	[p1l1502t2210r1604b2240],
70	Middle	NNP	O	Middle	dep	64	SENT_20	[p1l1502t2210r1604b2240],
71	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1612t2210r1660b2235],
72	[	NNP	O	[	nsubj	73	SENT_20	[p1l1669t2212r1721b2235],
73	ate	VBD	O	eat	conj_and	10	SENT_20	[p1l1669t2212r1721b2235],
74	Toarcian	JJ	MISC	toarcian	amod	75	SENT_20	[p1l1728t2210r1860b2241],
75	)	NN	O	)	dobj	73	SENT_20	[p1l1728t2210r1860b2241],
76	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1728t2210r1860b2241],
77	Higumastra	NNP	O	Higumastra	nn	79	SENT_20	[p1l1870t2211r2017b2241],
78	transversa	NN	O	transversa	nn	79	SENT_20	[p1l2025t2214r2154b2235],
79	?	NN	O	?	dep	82	SENT_20	[p1l6t2264r20b2267],
80	Napora	NN	O	napora	nn	82	SENT_20	[p1l30t2252r123b2280],
81	nipponica	NN	O	nipponica	nn	82	SENT_20	[p1l135t2251r257b2280],
82	Zone	NNP	O	Zone	conj_and	73	SENT_20	[p1l267t2252r331b2274],
83	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	86	SENT_20	[p1l344t2250r419b2280],
84	early	JJ	O	early	amod	86	SENT_20	[p1l344t2250r419b2280],
85	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	86	SENT_20	[p1l426t2250r560b2280],
86	)	NN	O	)	dep	82	SENT_20	[p1l426t2250r560b2280],
87	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l426t2250r560b2280],
88	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l573t2250r621b2274],
89	Minfusus	NNP	O	Minfusus	nsubj	90	SENT_20	[p1l637t2250r754b2280],
90	proavas	VBZ	O	proava	conj_and	73	SENT_20	[p1l765t2257r866b2280],
91	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	93	SENT_20	[p1l878t2264r893b2267],
92	Transhsuum	NN	O	transhsuum	nn	93	SENT_20	[p1l906t2250r1059b2274],
93	hisuikyoense	NN	O	hisuikyoense	dobj	90	SENT_20	[p1l1072t2250r1231b2280],
94	Zone	NNP	O	Zone	dep	96	SENT_20	[p1l1242t2252r1306b2274],
95	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	94	SENT_20	[p1l1321t2250r1379b2280],
96	late	JJ	O	late	prep	90	SENT_20	[p1l1321t2250r1379b2280],
97	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	98	SENT_20	[p1l1390t2250r1523b2280],
98	)	NN	O	)	dep	96	SENT_20	[p1l1390t2250r1523b2280],
99	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1390t2250r1523b2280],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_21	[p1l1534t2250r1610b2274],
2	zones	NNS	O	zone	nsubjpass	5	SENT_21	[p1l1623t2257r1696b2274],
3	can	MD	O	can	aux	5	SENT_21	[p1l1709t2257r1753b2274],
4	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_21	[p1l1765t2250r1796b2274],
5	correlated	VBN	O	correlate	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1808t2250r1939b2274],
6	worldwide	JJ	O	worldwide	amod	9	SENT_21	[p1l1952t2250r2094b2274],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l2106t2250r2154b2274],
8	linkpreviouslyestablished	JJ	O	linkpreviouslyestablished	amod	9	SENT_21	[p1l6t2289r349b2320],
9	UAzonations	NNS	O	uazonation	nsubj	10	SENT_21	[p1l360t2290r530b2314],
10	forthe	VBP	O	forthe	ccomp	5	SENT_21	[p1l542t2289r625b2314],
11	l-lettangian	JJ	O	l-lettangian	acomp	10	SENT_21	[p1l637t2290r948b2320],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l637t2290r948b2320],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l637t2290r948b2320],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l637t2290r948b2320],

1	Sinemurian	JJ	PERSON	sinemurian	amod	4	SENT_23	[p1l637t2290r948b2320],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l955t2289r1002b2314],
3	the	DT	O	the	conj_and	1	SENT_23	[p1l1009t2289r1051b2314],
4	Middle	NN	MISC	middle	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1062t2289r1153b2314],
5	to	TO	MISC	to	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1160t2293r1185b2314],
6	UpperJurassic	NNP	MISC	UpperJurassic	prep_to	4	SENT_23	[p1l1192t2289r1436b2320],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1192t2289r1436b2320],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_24	[p1l1192t2289r1436b2320],
2	new	JJ	O	new	amod	3	SENT_24	[p1l1447t2296r1504b2314],
3	zonation	NN	O	zonation	nsubj	14	SENT_24	[p1l1521t2290r1634b2314],
4	allows	VBZ	O	allow	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1652t2289r1735b2314],
5	high	JJ	O	high	amod	7	SENT_24	[p1l1753t2289r1953b2320],
6	?	NN	O	?	nn	7	SENT_24	[p1l1753t2289r1953b2320],
7	resolution	NN	O	resolution	dobj	4	SENT_24	[p1l1753t2289r1953b2320],
8	dating	VBG	O	date	partmod	7	SENT_24	[p1l1971t2289r2054b2320],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l2071t2290r2095b2314],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_24	[p1l2112t2289r2154b2314],
11	studied	VBN	O	study	amod	12	SENT_24	[p1l1303t2329r1398b2354],
12	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_in	8	SENT_24	[p1l1412t2329r1511b2354],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1524t2329r1572b2354],
14	provides	VBZ	O	provide	conj_and	4	SENT_24	[p1l1586t2329r1697b2360],
15	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_24	[p1l1711t2336r1724b2354],
16	solid	JJ	O	solid	amod	17	SENT_24	[p1l1738t2329r1798b2354],
17	basis	NN	O	basis	dobj	14	SENT_24	[p1l1812t2329r1875b2354],
18	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1888t2329r1924b2354],
19	analyzing	VBG	O	analyze	prepc_for	14	SENT_24	[p1l1937t2329r2062b2360],
20	faunal	JJ	O	faunal	amod	21	SENT_24	[p1l2075t2329r2154b2354],
21	turnovers	NNS	O	turnover	dobj	19	SENT_24	[p1l679t2373r805b2393],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l814t2369r862b2393],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_24	[p1l871t2369r913b2393],
24	paleobiogeography	NN	O	paleobiogeography	conj_and	21	SENT_24	[p1l923t2369r1172b2399],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1181t2369r1208b2393],
26	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	amod	27	SENT_24	[p1l1211t2369r1312b2399],
27	radiolarians	NNS	O	radiolarian	prep_of	24	SENT_24	[p1l1321t2369r1480b2394],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1321t2369r1480b2394],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l11t2699r59b2748],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l11t2699r59b2748],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l84t2696r480b2748],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_27	[p1l105t2866r212b2918],
2	construction	NN	O	construction	nsubj	21	SENT_27	[p1l233t2867r601b2918],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l621t2866r682b2918],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_27	[p1l696t2881r726b2918],
5	global	JJ	O	global	amod	7	SENT_27	[p1l745t2866r921b2931],
6	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	7	SENT_27	[p1l943t2866r1262b2918],
7	zonation	NN	O	zonation	prep_of	2	SENT_27	[p1l1283t2867r1538b2918],
8	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1559t2866r1640b2918],
9	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	11	SENT_27	[p1l1659t2866r1812b2918],
10	Jurassic	JJ	MISC	jurassic	amod	11	SENT_27	[p1l1826t2867r2054b2931],
11	stages	NNS	O	stage	prep_for	7	SENT_27	[p1l11t2959r202b3016],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l11t2959r202b3016],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_27	[p1l230t2951r322b3003],
14	Pliensbachian	NNP	MISC	Pliensbachian	appos	11	SENT_27	[p1l350t2951r766b3011],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l350t2951r766b3011],
16	Toarcian	NNP	PERSON	Toarcian	appos	11	SENT_27	[p1l792t2952r1044b3003],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1070t2951r1177b3003],
18	Aalenian	NNP	MISC	Aalenian	appos	11	SENT_27	[p1l1202t2951r1473b3011],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1202t2951r1473b3011],
20	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	21	SENT_27	[p1l1502t2952r1544b3003],
21	essential	JJ	O	essential	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1572t2951r1826b3003],
22	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1854t2951r1935b3003],
23	the	DT	DATE	the	det	25	SENT_27	[p1l1960t2951r2052b3003],
24	future	JJ	DATE	future	amod	25	SENT_27	[p1l10t3036r187b3088],
25	zonation	NN	O	zonation	prep_for	21	SENT_27	[p1l206t3037r461b3088],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l478t3036r539b3088],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_27	[p1l550t3036r642b3088],
28	entire	JJ	O	entire	amod	29	SENT_27	[p1l661t3037r832b3088],
29	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	prep_of	25	SENT_27	[p1l843t3037r1085b3102],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l843t3037r1085b3102],

1	Earliest	JJS	O	earliest	nsubj	15	SENT_28	[p1l1104t3036r1321b3088],
2	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	amod	4	SENT_28	[p1l1330t3037r1558b3102],
3	(	NN	O	(	nn	4	SENT_28	[p1l1579t3036r1928b3102],
4	Hettangian	NN	O	hettangian	dep	1	SENT_28	[p1l1579t3036r1928b3102],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1946t3036r2052b3088],
6	Sinemurian	JJ	MISC	sinemurian	amod	7	SENT_28	[p1l10t3122r370b3187],
7	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	1	SENT_28	[p1l10t3122r370b3187],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l418t3122r524b3174],
9	Middle	NN	O	middle	conj_and	1	SENT_28	[p1l569t3122r773b3174],
10	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l817t3130r873b3174],
11	Late	JJ	O	late	amod	13	SENT_28	[p1l917t3125r1035b3174],
12	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	amod	13	SENT_28	[p1l1071t3122r1299b3187],
13	radiolarians	NNS	O	radiolarian	prep_to	7	SENT_28	[p1l1342t3122r1687b3174],
14	have	VBP	O	have	aux	15	SENT_28	[p1l1733t3122r1869b3174],
15	been	VBN	O	be	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1912t3122r2053b3174],

1	Tel.	NNP	O	Tel.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l656t3329r752b3371],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l656t3329r752b3371],
3	+386	CD	NUMBER	+386	number	4	SENT_30	[p1l779t3331r915b3373],
4	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_30	[p1l937t3331r955b3370],
5	4706371	CD	NUMBER	4706371	dep	4	SENT_30	[p1l979t3331r1199b3377],
6	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l979t3331r1199b3377],
7	fax	NN	O	fax	dep	1	SENT_30	[p1l1223t3329r1305b3371],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1223t3329r1305b3371],
9	+386	CD	NUMBER	+386	number	10	SENT_30	[p1l1332t3331r1468b3373],
10	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	7	SENT_30	[p1l1490t3331r1508b3370],
11	4257755	CD	NUMBER	4257755	dep	10	SENT_30	[p1l1531t3331r1749b3371],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1531t3331r1749b3371],

1	E-mail	NN	O	e-mail	nn	2	SENT_31	[p1l105t3399r254b3440],
2	addresses	NNS	O	address	nsubj	22	SENT_31	[p1l272t3399r502b3441],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l272t3399r502b3441],
4	cartermicro@earthlink.net	NN	O	cartermicro@earthlink.net	nn	7	SENT_31	[p1l523t3399r1142b3441],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_31	[p1l1164t3399r1260b3451],
6	E.S.	NNP	PERSON	E.S.	nn	7	SENT_31	[p1l1164t3399r1260b3451],
7	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	nn	8	SENT_31	[p1l1280t3399r1456b3451],
8	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_31	[p1l1280t3399r1456b3451],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1280t3399r1456b3451],
10	spela@zrc?sazu.si	NN	O	spela@zrc?sazu.si	appos	2	SENT_31	[p1l1477t3399r1882b3451],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_31	[p1l12t3459r68b3521],
12	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	nn	14	SENT_31	[p1l12t3459r68b3521],
13	Gorican	NNP	PERSON	Gorican	nn	14	SENT_31	[p1l87t3469r302b3521],
14	)	NN	O	)	dep	10	SENT_31	[p1l87t3469r302b3521],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l87t3469r302b3521],
16	jean.guex@unil.ch	NN	O	jean.guex@unil.ch	nn	20	SENT_31	[p1l316t3469r747b3521],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_31	[p1l769t3469r813b3521],
18	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	20	SENT_31	[p1l769t3469r813b3521],
19	Guex	NNP	O	Guex	nn	20	SENT_31	[p1l833t3469r986b3521],
20	)	NNP	O	)	appos	2	SENT_31	[p1l833t3469r986b3521],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l833t3469r986b3521],
22	luis.odogherty@uca.es	VBZ	O	luis.odogherty@uca.es	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1006t3469r1526b3521],
23	(	NNP	O	(	nn	26	SENT_31	[p1l1549t3469r1602b3521],
24	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	nn	26	SENT_31	[p1l1549t3469r1602b3521],
25	O'Dogherty	NNP	PERSON	O'Dogherty	nn	26	SENT_31	[p1l1622t3469r1922b3521],
26	)	NN	O	)	dobj	22	SENT_31	[p1l1622t3469r1922b3521],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1622t3469r1922b3521],
28	pdewever@mnhn.fr	NN	O	pdewever@mnhn.fr	dep	39	SENT_31	[p1l10t3539r476b3592],
29	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	39	SENT_31	[p1l497t3539r554b3591],
30	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	39	SENT_31	[p1l497t3539r554b3591],
31	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	39	SENT_31	[p1l574t3542r634b3581],
32	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	nn	39	SENT_31	[p1l652t3539r842b3591],
33	)	NN	O	)	nn	39	SENT_31	[p1l652t3539r842b3591],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l652t3539r842b3591],
35	Paulian.Dumitrica@uni1.ch	NN	O	paulian.dumitrica@uni1.ch	dep	39	SENT_31	[p1l862t3539r1482b3581],
36	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	39	SENT_31	[p1l1505t3539r1562b3591],
37	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	39	SENT_31	[p1l1505t3539r1562b3591],
38	Dumitrica	NNP	PERSON	Dumitrica	nn	39	SENT_31	[p1l1582t3539r1850b3591],
39	)	NN	O	)	ccomp	22	SENT_31	[p1l1582t3539r1850b3591],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1582t3539r1850b3591],
41	shori@sci.ehime-u.ac.jp	JJ	O	shori@sci.ehime-u.ac.jp	amod	45	SENT_31	[p1l10t3609r561b3661],
42	(	NN	O	(	nn	45	SENT_31	[p1l585t3609r683b3661],
43	R.S.	NNP	PERSON	R.S.	nn	45	SENT_31	[p1l585t3609r683b3661],
44	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	nn	45	SENT_31	[p1l703t3609r838b3661],
45	)	NNP	O	)	dep	57	SENT_31	[p1l703t3609r838b3661],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l703t3609r838b3661],
47	matsuoka@geo.sc.niigata-u.ac.jp	JJ	O	matsuoka@geo.sc.niigata-u.ac.jp	amod	51	SENT_31	[p1l858t3609r1617b3661],
48	(	NN	O	(	nn	51	SENT_31	[p1l1639t3609r1701b3661],
49	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	nn	51	SENT_31	[p1l1639t3609r1701b3661],
50	Matsuoka	NNP	PERSON	Matsuoka	nn	51	SENT_31	[p1l1721t3609r1983b3661],
51	)	NNP	O	)	appos	45	SENT_31	[p1l1721t3609r1983b3661],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1721t3609r1983b3661],
53	micropaw14@ipa.net	NN	O	micropaw14@ipa.net	appos	51	SENT_31	[p1l10t3680r508b3731],
54	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	57	SENT_31	[p1l530t3679r633b3731],
55	P.A.	NNP	PERSON	P.A.	nn	57	SENT_31	[p1l530t3679r633b3731],
56	Whalen	NNP	PERSON	Whalen	nn	57	SENT_31	[p1l651t3679r869b3731],
57	)	NN	O	)	ccomp	22	SENT_31	[p1l651t3679r869b3731],
58	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l651t3679r869b3731],

1	doi	FW	O	doi	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l9t121r795b173],
2	:10.1016	CD	NUMBER	:10.1016	dep	1	SENT_33	[p2l9t121r795b173],
3	/	:	O	/	punct	5	SENT_33	[p2l9t121r795b173],
4	j.	NN	O	j.	nn	5	SENT_33	[p2l9t121r795b173],
5	palaeo	NN	O	palaeo	dep	2	SENT_33	[p2l9t121r795b173],
6	.2010.08.024	CD	NUMBER	.2010.08.024	dep	2	SENT_33	[p2l9t121r795b173],

1	?	RB	O	?	advmod	7	SENT_34	[p2l1046t206r1090b250],
2	2010	CD	DATE	2010	num	6	SENT_34	[p2l1113t205r1247b250],
3	Elsevier	NNP	MISC	Elsevier	nn	6	SENT_34	[p2l1271t202r1484b250],
4	B.V.	NNP	MISC	B.V.	nn	6	SENT_34	[p2l1506t205r1604b251],
5	All	NNP	MISC	All	nn	6	SENT_34	[p2l1626t202r1699b250],
6	rights	NNS	O	rights	nsubj	7	SENT_34	[p2l1724t202r1878b262],
7	reserved	VBD	O	reserve	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1903t202r2148b251],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1903t202r2148b251],

1	studied	VBN	O	study	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l52t502r273b555],
2	extensively	RB	O	extensively	advmod	1	SENT_35	[p2l311t502r654b568],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	4	SENT_35	[p2l694t502r904b568],
4	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	dobj	1	SENT_35	[p2l694t502r904b568],
5	et	FW	O	et	nn	6	SENT_35	[p2l940t510r996b555],
6	al.	FW	O	al.	nsubjpass	28	SENT_35	[p2l1033t502r1112b563],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1033t502r1112b563],
8	1998	CD	DATE	1998	appos	6	SENT_35	[p2l1154t504r1317b563],
9	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1154t504r1317b563],
10	Baumgartner	NNP	PERSON	Baumgartner	nsubjpass	28	SENT_35	[p2l1360t505r1755b568],
11	et	FW	O	et	nn	12	SENT_35	[p2l1791t510r1848b555],
12	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	10	SENT_35	[p2l1884t502r1962b563],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1884t502r1962b563],
14	1995	CD	DATE	1995	conj_and	6	SENT_35	[p2l2005t505r2148b555],
15	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	16	SENT_35	[p2l51t587r438b654],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	rcmod	14	SENT_35	[p2l51t587r438b654],
17	but	CC	O	but	prep	16	SENT_35	[p2l480t587r580b641],
18	Pliensbachian	NNP	PERSON	Pliensbachian	nn	20	SENT_35	[p2l617t587r1044b649],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l617t587r1044b649],
20	Toarcian	NNP	PERSON	Toarcian	dep	17	SENT_35	[p2l1081t588r1340b641],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l1378t587r1487b641],
22	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	23	SENT_35	[p2l1523t587r1787b641],
23	faunas	NNS	O	fauna	nsubjpass	28	SENT_35	[p2l1826t587r2019b641],
24	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	28	SENT_35	[p2l2058t603r2149b641],
25	much	RB	O	much	advmod	27	SENT_35	[p2l51t674r219b727],
26	less	RBR	O	less	advmod	27	SENT_35	[p2l238t674r345b727],
27	well	RB	O	well	advmod	28	SENT_35	[p2l362t674r490b727],
28	known	VBN	O	know	rcmod	4	SENT_35	[p2l508t674r716b727],
29	biochronologically	RB	O	biochronologically	advmod	28	SENT_35	[p2l733t674r1305b740],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l733t674r1305b740],

1	To	TO	O	to	aux	2	SENT_36	[p2l1321t677r1393b727],
2	address	VB	O	address	purpcl	11	SENT_36	[p2l1412t674r1641b727],
3	this	DT	O	this	det	4	SENT_36	[p2l1658t674r1767b727],
4	need	NN	O	need	dobj	2	SENT_36	[p2l1786t674r1945b735],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1786t674r1945b735],
6	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_36	[p2l1964t689r1995b727],
7	joint	JJ	O	joint	amod	9	SENT_36	[p2l2005t675r2151b740],
8	international	JJ	O	international	amod	9	SENT_36	[p2l51t760r441b813],
9	project	NN	O	project	nsubjpass	11	SENT_36	[p2l462t761r674b826],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_36	[p2l690t775r807b813],
11	initiated	VBN	O	initiate	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l828t760r1079b813],
12	under	IN	O	under	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1099t760r1278b813],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_36	[p2l1295t760r1390b813],
14	framework	NN	O	framework	prep_under	11	SENT_36	[p2l1411t760r1746b813],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1764t760r1826b813],
16	INTERRAD	NNP	O	INTERRAD	nn	19	SENT_36	[p2l1839t762r2150b813],
17	(	NNP	O	(	nn	19	SENT_36	[p2l55t845r472b911],
18	International	NNP	ORGANIZATION	International	nn	19	SENT_36	[p2l55t845r472b911],
19	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Association	prep_of	14	SENT_36	[p2l497t846r841b898],
20	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l867t845r930b898],
21	Radiolarian	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Radiolarian	nn	23	SENT_36	[p2l950t845r1291b898],
22	Paleontologists	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paleontologists	nn	23	SENT_36	[p2l1318t845r1798b912],
23	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	19	SENT_36	[p2l1318t845r1798b912],
24	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1830t845r2029b912],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_36	[p2l2054t845r2149b898],
26	9th	JJ	ORDINAL	9th	amod	28	SENT_36	[p2l51t932r150b985],
27	INTERRAD	NN	O	interrad	nn	28	SENT_36	[p2l174t934r485b984],
28	meeting	NN	O	meeting	prep_during	11	SENT_36	[p2l509t932r756b998],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l779t932r835b984],
30	Blairsden	NNP	LOCATION	Blairsden	nn	32	SENT_36	[p2l858t932r1150b993],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l858t932r1150b993],
32	California	NNP	LOCATION	California	prep_in	28	SENT_36	[p2l1176t931r1465b985],
33	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1487t933r1543b984],
34	2000	CD	DATE	2000	prep_in	11	SENT_36	[p2l1567t934r1729b985],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1567t934r1729b985],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_37	[p2l1752t932r1862b985],
2	?rst	JJ	O	?rst	amod	3	SENT_37	[p2l1885t931r2005b985],
3	step	NN	O	step	nsubj	14	SENT_37	[p2l2027t940r2149b998],
4	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l51t1017r135b1071],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_37	[p2l177t1017r272b1071],
6	Pliensbachian	NNP	MISC	Pliensbachian	prep_for	3	SENT_37	[p2l316t1017r730b1071],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l773t1025r830b1071],
8	Aalenian	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Aalenian	nn	10	SENT_37	[p2l872t1017r1137b1071],
9	Working	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Working	nn	10	SENT_37	[p2l1177t1017r1444b1084],
10	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	prep_to	6	SENT_37	[p2l1486t1020r1672b1084],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_37	[p2l1720t1017r1884b1084],
12	PTA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	PTA	nn	13	SENT_37	[p2l1720t1017r1884b1084],
13	)	NN	O	)	dep	10	SENT_37	[p2l1720t1017r1884b1084],
14	was	VBD	O	be	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1931t1033r2048b1071],
15	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_37	[p2l2091t1025r2149b1071],
16	establish	VB	O	establish	ccomp	14	SENT_37	[p2l51t1104r316b1157],
17	a	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_37	[p2l339t1119r369b1157],
18	set	NN	O	set	dobj	16	SENT_37	[p2l394t1112r479b1157],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l500t1104r562b1157],
20	clearly	RB	O	clearly	advmod	21	SENT_37	[p2l579t1104r778b1170],
21	de?ned	VBN	O	de?ned	prepc_of	18	SENT_37	[p2l800t1104r1024b1157],
22	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1049t1104r1158b1157],
23	updated	VBN	O	update	amod	25	SENT_37	[p2l1182t1104r1429b1170],
24	taxonomic	JJ	O	taxonomic	amod	25	SENT_37	[p2l1452t1105r1772b1157],
25	species	NNS	O	species	conj_and	18	SENT_37	[p2l1795t1105r2007b1170],
26	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	29	SENT_37	[p2l2031t1104r2152b1157],
27	would	MD	O	would	aux	29	SENT_37	[p2l49t1190r239b1243],
28	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	29	SENT_37	[p2l263t1190r332b1243],
29	used	VBN	O	use	rcmod	25	SENT_37	[p2l356t1190r494b1243],
30	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l518t1191r573b1242],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_37	[p2l596t1190r691b1243],
32	construction	NN	O	construction	prep_in	29	SENT_37	[p2l715t1191r1093b1243],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1116t1190r1178b1243],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_37	[p2l1194t1190r1289b1243],
35	zonation	NN	O	zonation	prep_of	32	SENT_37	[p2l1312t1191r1574b1243],
36	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1597t1190r1706b1243],
37	to	TO	O	to	aux	38	SENT_37	[p2l1730t1198r1787b1243],
38	agree	VB	O	agree	conj_and	16	SENT_37	[p2l1811t1205r1973b1256],
39	upon	IN	O	upon	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1997t1205r2150b1256],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_37	[p2l50t1275r146b1328],
41	sections	NNS	O	section	prep_upon	38	SENT_37	[p2l178t1276r417b1328],
42	to	TO	O	to	aux	44	SENT_37	[p2l447t1283r505b1328],
43	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	44	SENT_37	[p2l535t1275r604b1328],
44	used	VBN	O	use	xcomp	38	SENT_37	[p2l635t1275r788b1329],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l635t1275r788b1329],

1	This	DT	O	this	nsubjpass	3	SENT_38	[p2l817t1275r940b1328],
2	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	3	SENT_38	[p2l970t1291r1087b1328],
3	accomplished	VBN	O	accomplish	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1118t1275r1529b1342],
4	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1560t1275r1759b1342],
5	meetings	NNS	O	meeting	prep_during	3	SENT_38	[p2l1789t1276r2064b1342],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l2094t1276r2150b1328],
7	2001	CD	DATE	2001	prep_in	5	SENT_38	[p2l51t1364r192b1414],
8	and	CC	DATE	and	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l227t1361r337b1414],
9	2002	CD	DATE	2002	prep_in	5	SENT_38	[p2l365t1364r512b1414],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l542t1362r597b1414],
11	Slovenia	NNP	LOCATION	Slovenia	prep_in	5	SENT_38	[p2l625t1361r891b1423],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l625t1361r891b1423],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l919t1361r1029b1414],
14	?nal	JJ	O	?nal	amod	15	SENT_38	[p2l1058t1361r1187b1414],
15	editing	NN	O	editing	conj_and	5	SENT_38	[p2l1216t1361r1427b1428],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1453t1362r1509b1414],
17	2004	CD	DATE	2004	prep_in	15	SENT_38	[p2l1537t1364r1686b1414],
18	and	CC	DATE	and	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1713t1361r1823b1414],
19	2005	CD	DATE	2005	prep_in	15	SENT_38	[p2l1850t1364r2013b1415],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l1850t1364r2013b1415],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_39	[p2l2040t1361r2150b1414],
2	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	3	SENT_39	[p2l52t1448r361b1514],
3	Catalogue	NN	MISC	catalogue	nsubj	21	SENT_39	[p2l52t1448r361b1514],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l393t1448r502b1501],
5	systematics	NNS	O	systematic	conj_and	3	SENT_39	[p2l534t1448r882b1514],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l913t1447r976b1501],
7	Pliensbachian	NNP	LOCATION	Pliensbachian	nn	9	SENT_39	[p2l1000t1448r1428b1509],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1000t1448r1428b1509],
9	Toarcian	NNP	PERSON	Toarcian	prep_of	5	SENT_39	[p2l1457t1449r1716b1501],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1747t1448r1857b1501],
11	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	13	SENT_39	[p2l1885t1448r2150b1501],
12	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	13	SENT_39	[p2l51t1533r378b1587],
13	genera	NN	O	genus	conj_and	3	SENT_39	[p2l396t1549r601b1600],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l619t1533r728b1587],
15	species	NNS	O	species	conj_and	5	SENT_39	[p2l748t1534r975b1600],
16	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	15	SENT_39	[p2l748t1534r975b1600],
17	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	21	SENT_39	[p2l995t1534r1038b1587],
18	now	RB	DATE	now	advmod	21	SENT_39	[p2l1059t1549r1190b1587],
19	complete	JJ	O	complete	amod	21	SENT_39	[p2l1208t1533r1486b1600],
20	(	NN	O	(	nn	21	SENT_39	[p2l1508t1533r1766b1600],
21	GoriEan	NNP	O	GoriEan	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1508t1533r1766b1600],
22	et	FW	O	et	nn	23	SENT_39	[p2l1785t1541r1841b1586],
23	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	21	SENT_39	[p2l1858t1534r1937b1595],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1858t1534r1937b1595],
25	2006	CD	DATE	2006	num	26	SENT_39	[p2l1957t1534r2149b1600],
26	)	NN	O	)	appos	23	SENT_39	[p2l1957t1534r2149b1600],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1957t1534r2149b1600],

1	402	CD	NUMBER	402	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l271t1676r315b1697],
2	E5	NN	O	e5	dep	1	SENT_40	[p2l816t1676r853b1697],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l816t1676r853b1697],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_42	[p2l11t1814r123b1869],
2	systematics	NNS	O	systematic	nsubjpass	7	SENT_42	[p2l161t1815r514b1883],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l553t1814r616b1869],
4	280	CD	NUMBER	280	num	5	SENT_42	[p2l646t1817r758b1869],
5	taxa	NN	O	taxa	prep_of	2	SENT_42	[p2l795t1822r923b1869],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_42	[p2l961t1815r1005b1869],
7	included	VBN	O	include	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1044t1814r1322b1877],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1044t1814r1322b1877],
9	each	DT	O	each	advmod	7	SENT_42	[p2l1360t1814r1499b1869],
10	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1534t1814r1675b1869],
11	an	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_42	[p2l1713t1830r1784b1869],
12	up	RB	O	up	quantmod	15	SENT_42	[p2l1821t1814r2150b1883],
13	?	CD	NUMBER	?	number	15	SENT_42	[p2l1821t1814r2150b1883],
14	to	TO	O	to	dep	15	SENT_42	[p2l1821t1814r2150b1883],
15	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	17	SENT_42	[p2l1821t1814r2150b1883],
16	date	NN	O	date	nn	17	SENT_42	[p2l1821t1814r2150b1883],
17	synonymy	NN	O	synonymy	prep_with	7	SENT_42	[p2l14t1919r346b1972],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l14t1919r346b1972],
19	original	JJ	O	original	amod	22	SENT_42	[p2l370t1903r603b1972],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l626t1903r737b1958],
21	subsequent	JJ	O	subsequent	conj_and	19	SENT_42	[p2l761t1903r1113b1972],
22	de?nitions	NNS	O	de?nitions	dobj	7	SENT_42	[p2l1134t1903r1476b1966],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1134t1903r1476b1966],
24	remarks	NNS	O	remark	conj_and	22	SENT_42	[p2l1500t1903r1764b1966],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1500t1903r1764b1966],
26	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1788t1903r1899b1958],
27	data	NNS	O	datum	dobj	7	SENT_42	[p2l1923t1903r2053b1958],
28	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l2076t1919r2151b1958],
29	geographic	JJ	O	geographic	amod	30	SENT_42	[p2l12t1992r360b2061],
30	distribution	NN	O	distribution	prep_on	7	SENT_42	[p2l408t1992r793b2048],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l408t1992r793b2048],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_43	[p2l840t1992r954b2047],
2	plates	NNS	O	plate	nsubj	3	SENT_43	[p2l1003t1992r1186b2061],
3	illustrate	VBP	O	illustrate	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1237t1992r1516b2047],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_43	[p2l1564t1992r1663b2047],
5	holotype	NN	O	holotype	nsubj	16	SENT_43	[p2l1713t1992r1987b2061],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l2037t1992r2150b2047],
7	suf?cient	JJ	O	suf?cient	amod	9	SENT_43	[p2l14t2081r297b2136],
8	other	JJ	O	other	amod	9	SENT_43	[p2l323t2081r488b2136],
9	specimens	NNS	O	specimen	nsubj	16	SENT_43	[p2l514t2082r833b2150],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l862t2081r1008b2136],
11	different	JJ	O	different	amod	13	SENT_43	[p2l1035t2081r1300b2136],
12	paleogeographic	JJ	O	paleogeographic	amod	13	SENT_43	[p2l1326t2081r1833b2150],
13	realms	NNS	O	realm	prep_from	9	SENT_43	[p2l1859t2081r2063b2136],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_43	[p2l2091t2089r2150b2136],
15	clearly	RB	O	clearly	advmod	16	SENT_43	[p2l14t2171r217b2239],
16	illustrate	VB	O	illustrate	xcomp	3	SENT_43	[p2l242t2171r513b2226],
17	intraspeci?c	JJ	O	intraspeci?c	amod	18	SENT_43	[p2l541t2171r915b2239],
18	variability	NN	O	variability	dobj	16	SENT_43	[p2l938t2171r1264b2239],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l938t2171r1264b2239],

1	Concurrently	RB	O	concurrently	advmod	22	SENT_44	[p2l1292t2171r1705b2239],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1292t2171r1705b2239],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_44	[p2l1733t2187r1764b2226],
4	preliminary	JJ	O	preliminary	amod	5	SENT_44	[p2l1791t2171r2152b2239],
5	zonation	NN	O	zonation	nsubjpass	22	SENT_44	[p2l14t2260r280b2315],
6	calculated	VBN	O	calculate	partmod	5	SENT_44	[p2l299t2260r607b2315],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l626t2260r767b2315],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_44	[p2l786t2260r883b2315],
9	UA	NNP	O	UA	nn	10	SENT_44	[p2l901t2262r993b2315],
10	program	NN	O	program	prep_with	6	SENT_44	[p2l1010t2275r1274b2328],
11	BioGraph	NNP	MISC	BioGraph	nn	13	SENT_44	[p2l1293t2260r1577b2328],
12	(	NNP	O	(	nn	13	SENT_44	[p2l1601t2260r1831b2328],
13	Savary	NNP	PERSON	Savary	dep	10	SENT_44	[p2l1601t2260r1831b2328],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1847t2260r1959b2315],
15	Guex	NNP	O	Guex	prep_with	6	SENT_44	[p2l1979t2262r2150b2323],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1979t2262r2150b2323],
17	1991	CD	DATE	1991	appos	15	SENT_44	[p2l17t2351r179b2412],
18	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l17t2351r179b2412],
19	1999	CD	DATE	1999	num	20	SENT_44	[p2l204t2348r377b2416],
20	)	NN	O	)	appos	15	SENT_44	[p2l204t2348r377b2416],
21	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_44	[p2l400t2364r519b2403],
22	presented	VBN	O	present	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l540t2348r845b2417],
23	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l865t2356r922b2403],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_44	[p2l940t2348r1038b2403],
25	6th	JJ	ORDINAL	6th	amod	27	SENT_44	[p2l1058t2348r1158b2403],
26	International	NNP	MISC	International	nn	27	SENT_44	[p2l1179t2348r1577b2403],
27	Symposium	NNP	MISC	Symposium	prep_at	22	SENT_44	[p2l1597t2349r1958b2417],
28	of	IN	MISC	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1978t2348r2041b2403],
29	the	DT	MISC	the	det	31	SENT_44	[p2l2053t2348r2150b2403],
30	Jurassic	JJ	MISC	jurassic	amod	31	SENT_44	[p2l6t2438r245b2506],
31	System	NN	MISC	system	prep_of	27	SENT_44	[p2l278t2440r498b2506],
32	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l533t2438r590b2492],
33	Sicily	NNP	LOCATION	Sicily	nn	35	SENT_44	[p2l625t2437r786b2506],
34	(	NNP	O	(	nn	35	SENT_44	[p2l823t2437r1182b2506],
35	September	NNP	DATE	September	prep_in	31	SENT_44	[p2l823t2437r1182b2506],
36	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	35	SENT_44	[p2l1214t2440r1380b2501],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1214t2440r1380b2501],
38	Palermo	NNP	LOCATION	Palermo	prep_in	31	SENT_44	[p2l1417t2437r1693b2506],
39	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	38	SENT_44	[p2l1417t2437r1693b2506],
40	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1732t2437r1843b2492],
41	the	DT	O	the	det	43	SENT_44	[p2l1879t2437r1976b2492],
42	10th	JJ	ORDINAL	10th	amod	43	SENT_44	[p2l2015t2437r2151b2492],
43	meeting	NN	O	meeting	prep_in	31	SENT_44	[p2l14t2527r266b2595],
44	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l282t2526r346b2581],
45	INTERRAD	NNP	O	INTERRAD	prep_of	31	SENT_44	[p2l356t2529r673b2581],
46	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	45	SENT_44	[p2l695t2526r1053b2595],
47	September	NNP	DATE	September	tmod	31	SENT_44	[p2l695t2526r1053b2595],
48	2003	CD	DATE	2003	num	47	SENT_44	[p2l1069t2529r1235b2590],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1069t2529r1235b2590],
50	Lausanne	NNP	LOCATION	Lausanne	appos	27	SENT_44	[p2l1254t2527r1583b2595],
51	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	50	SENT_44	[p2l1254t2527r1583b2595],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1254t2527r1583b2595],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_45	[p2l1599t2526r1712b2581],
2	species	NNS	O	species	nsubj	6	SENT_45	[p2l1730t2527r1946b2595],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1966t2527r2021b2581],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_45	[p2l2039t2526r2149b2581],
5	catalogue	NN	O	catalogue	prep_in	2	SENT_45	[p2l14t2616r305b2684],
6	provide	VBP	O	provide	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l324t2616r557b2684],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_45	[p2l575t2616r672b2671],
8	framework	NN	O	framework	dobj	6	SENT_45	[p2l691t2616r1031b2671],
9	upon	IN	O	upon	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1047t2632r1202b2684],
10	which	WDT	O	which	dobj	13	SENT_45	[p2l1219t2616r1408b2671],
11	zonation	NN	O	zonation	nsubjpass	13	SENT_45	[p2l1426t2617r1693b2671],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_45	[p2l1711t2617r1755b2671],
13	constructed	VBN	O	construct	prepc_upon	6	SENT_45	[p2l1774t2616r2149b2671],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1774t2616r2149b2671],

1	Species	NNP	O	Species	nsubjpass	10	SENT_46	[p2l14t2705r236b2773],
2	to	TO	O	to	aux	4	SENT_46	[p2l268t2713r326b2760],
3	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_46	[p2l357t2705r428b2760],
4	included	VBN	O	include	infmod	1	SENT_46	[p2l459t2705r722b2760],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l755t2705r811b2759],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_46	[p2l842t2705r939b2760],
7	total	JJ	O	total	amod	8	SENT_46	[p2l970t2705r1108b2760],
8	dataset	NN	O	dataset	prep_in	4	SENT_46	[p2l1139t2705r1361b2760],
9	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_46	[p2l1388t2720r1542b2760],
10	selected	VBN	O	select	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1574t2705r1821b2760],
11	conservatively	RB	O	conservatively	advmod	10	SENT_46	[p2l1852t2720r2150b2760, p2l13t2793r201b2862],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1852t2720r2150b2760, p2l13t2793r201b2862],
13	indeed	RB	O	indeed	advmod	25	SENT_46	[p2l225t2793r447b2857],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l225t2793r447b2857],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_46	[p2l466t2793r563b2848],
16	ranges	NNS	O	range	nsubjpass	25	SENT_46	[p2l583t2809r783b2862],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l802t2793r866b2848],
18	fewer	JJR	O	fewer	quantmod	22	SENT_46	[p2l878t2793r1053b2848],
19	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	22	SENT_46	[p2l1069t2793r1207b2848],
20	half	PDT	O	half	quantmod	22	SENT_46	[p2l1226t2793r1347b2848],
21	the	DT	O	the	quantmod	22	SENT_46	[p2l1357t2793r1454b2848],
22	available	JJ	O	available	num	23	SENT_46	[p2l1473t2793r1743b2848],
23	species	NNS	O	species	prep_of	16	SENT_46	[p2l1763t2794r1979b2862],
24	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	25	SENT_46	[p2l1997t2809r2150b2848],
25	incorporated	VBN	O	incorporate	parataxis	10	SENT_46	[p2l14t2882r408b2951],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l427t2883r483b2936],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_46	[p2l500t2882r598b2937],
28	?nal	JJ	O	?nal	amod	29	SENT_46	[p2l616t2882r748b2937],
29	dataset	NN	O	dataset	prep_in	25	SENT_46	[p2l766t2882r1001b2938],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l766t2882r1001b2938],

1	Eliminated	VBN	O	eliminate	csubj	3	SENT_47	[p2l1020t2882r1350b2937],
2	were	VBD	O	be	cop	3	SENT_47	[p2l1367t2898r1521b2937],
3	those	DT	O	those	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1538t2882r1703b2937],
4	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	7	SENT_47	[p2l1720t2882r1843b2937],
5	are	VBP	O	be	cop	7	SENT_47	[p2l1859t2898r1953b2937],
6	either	RB	O	either	advmod	7	SENT_47	[p2l1971t2882r2153b2937],
7	rare	JJ	O	rare	rcmod	3	SENT_47	[p2l14t2987r149b3035],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l14t2987r149b3035],
9	long	JJ	O	long	advmod	10	SENT_47	[p2l172t2971r304b3040],
10	ranging	VBG	O	range	xcomp	7	SENT_47	[p2l325t2972r559b3040],
11	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l578t2987r642b3026],
12	non	JJ	O	non	amod	13	SENT_47	[p2l662t2971r1122b3040],
13	?	NN	O	?	conj_or	3	SENT_47	[p2l662t2971r1122b3040],
14	diagnostic	JJ	O	diagnostic	amod	13	SENT_47	[p2l662t2971r1122b3040],
15	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1141t2971r1282b3026],
16	wide	JJ	O	wide	amod	17	SENT_47	[p2l1301t2971r1452b3026],
17	limits	NNS	O	limit	prep_with	13	SENT_47	[p2l1474t2971r1644b3026],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1666t2971r1730b3026],
19	variability	NN	O	variability	prep_of	17	SENT_47	[p2l1742t2971r2067b3040],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1742t2971r2067b3040],
21	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l2089t2987r2152b3026],
22	others	NNS	O	other	conj_or	3	SENT_47	[p2l14t3060r205b3115],
23	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	24	SENT_47	[p2l226t3060r350b3115],
24	occur	VBP	O	occur	rcmod	22	SENT_47	[p2l369t3076r536b3115],
25	sporadically	RB	O	sporadically	advmod	24	SENT_47	[p2l556t3060r925b3129],
26	because	IN	O	because	mark	31	SENT_47	[p2l944t3060r1186b3115],
27	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	28	SENT_47	[p2l1207t3060r1354b3115],
28	skeletons	NNS	O	skeleton	nsubj	31	SENT_47	[p2l1373t3060r1659b3115],
29	are	VBP	O	be	cop	31	SENT_47	[p2l1681t3076r1774b3115],
30	too	RB	O	too	advmod	31	SENT_47	[p2l1795t3068r1891b3115],
31	delicate	JJ	O	delicate	advcl	24	SENT_47	[p2l1913t3060r2150b3115],
32	to	TO	O	to	aux	34	SENT_47	[p2l13t3158r72b3205],
33	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	34	SENT_47	[p2l107t3150r177b3205],
34	preserved	VBN	O	preserve	xcomp	31	SENT_47	[p2l213t3150r531b3218],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l213t3150r531b3218],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_48	[p2l565t3152r610b3204],
2	list	NN	O	list	nsubjpass	25	SENT_48	[p2l643t3150r734b3205],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l768t3150r832b3205],
4	all	DT	O	all	det	5	SENT_48	[p2l858t3150r928b3205],
5	species	NNS	O	species	prep_of	2	SENT_48	[p2l965t3151r1196b3218],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l965t3151r1196b3218],
7	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1231t3150r1372b3205],
8	generic	JJ	O	generic	amod	9	SENT_48	[p2l1406t3151r1631b3218],
9	names	NNS	O	name	prep_with	2	SENT_48	[p2l1666t3166r1863b3205],
10	updated	VBN	O	update	partmod	9	SENT_48	[p2l1899t3150r2150b3218],
11	according	VBG	O	accord	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l13t3239r312b3307],
12	to	TO	O	to	prepc_according_to	10	SENT_48	[p2l330t3247r388b3294],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_48	[p2l408t3238r505b3294],
14	recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	15	SENT_48	[p2l525t3247r717b3294],
15	revision	NN	O	revision	pobj	10	SENT_48	[p2l735t3239r978b3294],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l998t3238r1061b3294],
17	O'Dogherty	NNP	O	O'Dogherty	prep_of	15	SENT_48	[p2l1073t3239r1421b3307],
18	et	FW	O	et	dep	17	SENT_48	[p2l1439t3247r1496b3294],
19	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	20	SENT_48	[p2l1514t3239r1579b3294],
20	(	FW	O	(	dep	18	SENT_48	[p2l1603t3239r1825b3307],
21	2009	CD	DATE	2009	num	22	SENT_48	[p2l1603t3239r1825b3307],
22	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	18	SENT_48	[p2l1603t3239r1825b3307],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1603t3239r1825b3307],
24	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	25	SENT_48	[p2l1846t3239r1889b3294],
25	given	VBN	O	give	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1908t3239r2075b3307],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l2095t3239r2151b3293],
27	Appendix	NN	O	appendix	nn	28	SENT_48	[p2l11t3327r310b3396],
28	A	NN	O	a	prep_in	25	SENT_48	[p2l330t3329r375b3381],
29	(	CD	NUMBER	(	nsubj	30	SENT_48	[p2l402t3327r524b3395],
30	see	VBP	O	see	rcmod	28	SENT_48	[p2l402t3327r524b3395],
31	supplement	NN	O	supplement	nn	32	SENT_48	[p2l549t3327r914b3396],
32	data	NNS	O	datum	dobj	30	SENT_48	[p2l938t3327r1068b3382],
33	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1093t3328r1148b3381],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_48	[p2l1172t3327r1270b3382],
35	electronic	JJ	O	electronic	amod	37	SENT_48	[p2l1294t3327r1596b3382],
36	version	NN	O	version	nn	37	SENT_48	[p2l1618t3327r1888b3395],
37	)	NN	O	)	prep_in	32	SENT_48	[p2l1618t3327r1888b3395],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1618t3327r1888b3395],

1	Pliensbachian	NNP	MISC	Pliensbachian	nsubjpass	10	SENT_49	[p2l116t3416r541b3480],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l116t3416r541b3480],
3	Toarcian	NNP	PERSON	Toarcian	conj_and	1	SENT_49	[p2l568t3417r827b3471],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l853t3416r963b3471],
5	early	JJ	O	early	amod	7	SENT_49	[p2l991t3416r1140b3485],
6	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	7	SENT_49	[p2l1163t3416r1428b3471],
7	radiolarians	NNS	O	radiolarian	conj_and	1	SENT_49	[p2l1455t3416r1809b3471],
8	have	VBP	O	have	aux	10	SENT_49	[p2l1838t3416r1979b3471],
9	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_49	[p2l2006t3416r2150b3471],
10	studied	VBN	O	study	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l14t3505r234b3560],
11	systematically	RB	O	systematically	advmod	10	SENT_49	[p2l270t3505r696b3574],
12	mostly	RB	O	mostly	advmod	10	SENT_49	[p2l729t3505r933b3574],
13	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l966t3505r1109b3560],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_49	[p2l1142t3505r1237b3560],
15	Circum	NNP	O	Circum	prep_from	10	SENT_49	[p2l1272t3505r1706b3560],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1272t3505r1706b3560],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1272t3505r1706b3560],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1272t3505r1706b3560],

1	Paci?c	NNP	O	Paci?c	nn	2	SENT_51	[p2l1272t3505r1706b3560],
2	belt	NN	O	belt	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1738t3505r1869b3561],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1738t3505r1869b3561],
4	western	JJ	O	western	amod	8	SENT_51	[p2l1906t3513r2150b3560],
5	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	nn	8	SENT_51	[p2l14t3594r188b3649],
6	America	NNP	LOCATION	America	nn	8	SENT_51	[p2l222t3595r472b3649],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_51	[p2l512t3595r811b3663],
8	Pessagno	NNP	PERSON	Pessagno	dep	2	SENT_51	[p2l512t3595r811b3663],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l848t3594r957b3649],
10	Blome	NNP	PERSON	Blome	dep	2	SENT_51	[p2l995t3594r1198b3658],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l995t3594r1198b3658],
12	1980	CD	DATE	1980	appos	10	SENT_51	[p2l1239t3597r1402b3658],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1239t3597r1402b3658],
14	Pessagno	NNP	LOCATION	Pessagno	dep	10	SENT_51	[p2l1444t3598r1717b3663],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1754t3594r1863b3649],
16	Whalen	NNP	PERSON	Whalen	conj_and	14	SENT_51	[p2l1899t3594r2149b3658],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1899t3594r2149b3658],
18	1982	CD	DATE	1982	appos	14	SENT_51	[p2l17t3687r180b3747],
19	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l17t3687r180b3747],
20	Pessagno	NNP	O	Pessagno	dep	10	SENT_51	[p2l210t3687r483b3752],
21	et	FW	O	et	nn	22	SENT_51	[p2l507t3692r565b3739],
22	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	20	SENT_51	[p2l586t3684r664b3747],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l586t3684r664b3747],
24	1986	CD	DATE	1986	appos	22	SENT_51	[p2l694t3687r857b3747],
25	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l694t3687r857b3747],
26	Yeh	NNP	PERSON	Yeh	dep	10	SENT_51	[p2l883t3684r1012b3747],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l883t3684r1012b3747],
28	1987a	NN	DATE	1987a	appos	26	SENT_51	[p2l1041t3687r1233b3747],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1041t3687r1233b3747],
30	b	NN	O	b	appos	26	SENT_51	[p2l1258t3684r1312b3747],
31	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1258t3684r1312b3747],
32	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	dep	10	SENT_51	[p2l1341t3687r1525b3739],
33	et	FW	O	et	nn	34	SENT_51	[p2l1547t3692r1604b3739],
34	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	32	SENT_51	[p2l1626t3684r1704b3747],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1626t3684r1704b3747],
36	1988	CD	DATE	1988	appos	34	SENT_51	[p2l1733t3687r1896b3747],
37	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1733t3687r1896b3747],
38	Cordey	NNP	O	Cordey	dep	36	SENT_51	[p2l1926t3684r2149b3752],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1926t3684r2149b3752],

1	1998	CD	DATE	1998	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l17t19r180b80],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l17t19r180b80],
3	Whalen	NNP	PERSON	Whalen	dep	1	SENT_52	[p3l200t17r437b72],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l454t17r564b72],
5	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	dep	1	SENT_52	[p3l583t19r778b80],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l583t19r778b80],
7	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	8	SENT_52	[p3l797t17r1171b85],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	appos	1	SENT_52	[p3l797t17r1171b85],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l797t17r1171b85],
10	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	11	SENT_52	[p3l797t17r1171b85],
11	apan	NN	O	apan	appos	1	SENT_52	[p3l797t17r1171b85],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	11	SENT_52	[p3l1193t17r1440b85],
13	Kishida	NNP	PERSON	Kishida	dep	1	SENT_52	[p3l1193t17r1440b85],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1456t17r1565b72],
15	Hisada	NNP	PERSON	Hisada	dep	1	SENT_52	[p3l1585t17r1799b80],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1585t17r1799b80],
17	1985	CD	DATE	1985	appos	13	SENT_52	[p3l1821t19r1985b80],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1821t19r1985b80],
19	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l2007t17r2149b80],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l2007t17r2149b80],
21	1988	CD	DATE	1988	appos	19	SENT_52	[p3l17t107r180b167],
22	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l17t107r180b167],
23	Sashida	NNP	LOCATION	Sashida	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l219t104r459b167],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l219t104r459b167],
25	1988	CD	DATE	1988	appos	23	SENT_52	[p3l496t107r659b167],
26	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l496t107r659b167],
27	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l697t105r826b158],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l859t104r968b158],
29	Otsuka	NNP	PERSON	Otsuka	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l1003t104r1222b166],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1003t104r1222b166],
31	1989	CD	DATE	1989	appos	27	SENT_52	[p3l1260t107r1423b166],
32	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1260t107r1423b166],
33	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l1462t105r1605b167],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1462t105r1605b167],
35	1990	CD	DATE	1990	appos	33	SENT_52	[p3l1642t107r1806b166],
36	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1642t107r1806b166],
37	Matsuoka	NNP	PERSON	Matsuoka	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l1844t104r2149b166],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1844t104r2149b166],
39	1991	CD	DATE	1991	appos	37	SENT_52	[p3l17t195r155b247],
40	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l171t208r180b256],
41	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l203t193r345b255],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l203t193r345b255],
43	1997	CD	DATE	1997	appos	41	SENT_52	[p3l367t195r531b256],
44	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l367t195r531b256],
45	Yao	NNP	PERSON	Yao	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l550t195r675b255],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l550t195r675b255],
47	1997	CD	DATE	1997	appos	45	SENT_52	[p3l697t195r861b255],
48	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l697t195r861b255],
49	Matsuoka	NNP	PERSON	Matsuoka	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l883t192r1189b255],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l883t192r1189b255],
51	2004	CD	DATE	2004	num	52	SENT_52	[p3l1208t192r1400b260],
52	)	NN	O	)	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l1208t192r1400b260],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1208t192r1400b260],
54	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1417t192r1528b247],
55	the	DT	O	the	det	56	SENT_52	[p3l1545t192r1640b247],
56	Philippines	NNPS	LOCATION	Philippines	dep	13	SENT_52	[p3l1659t192r1990b261],
57	(	NNP	O	(	nn	58	SENT_52	[p3l2013t192r2150b260],
58	Yeh	NNP	PERSON	Yeh	dep	1	SENT_52	[p3l2013t192r2150b260],
59	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l14t281r123b336],
60	Cheng	NNP	PERSON	Cheng	conj_and	58	SENT_52	[p3l152t281r352b350],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l152t281r352b350],
62	1996	CD	DATE	1996	appos	1	SENT_52	[p3l385t284r545b345],
63	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l385t284r545b345],
64	1998	CD	DATE	1998	num	65	SENT_52	[p3l577t282r765b350],
65	)	NN	O	)	appos	1	SENT_52	[p3l577t282r765b350],
66	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l577t282r765b350],

1	Only	RB	O	only	quantmod	3	SENT_53	[p3l794t281r934b350],
2	a	DT	O	a	quantmod	3	SENT_53	[p3l961t297r992b336],
3	few	JJ	O	few	num	4	SENT_53	[p3l1020t281r1131b336],
4	localities	NNS	O	locality	nsubjpass	6	SENT_53	[p3l1158t281r1419b336],
5	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_53	[p3l1448t297r1539b336],
6	described	VBN	O	describe	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1568t281r1855b336],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1884t281r2027b336],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_53	[p3l2054t281r2150b336],
9	Tethyan	NNP	MISC	Tethyan	nn	10	SENT_53	[p3l11t370r256b439],
10	realm	NN	O	realm	prep_from	6	SENT_53	[p3l279t370r451b425],
11	s.s.	NN	O	s.s.	dep	10	SENT_53	[p3l474t386r575b426],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l474t386r575b426],
13	Turkey	NNP	LOCATION	Turkey	nn	16	SENT_53	[p3l600t370r812b439],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_53	[p3l837t371r941b439],
15	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	16	SENT_53	[p3l837t371r941b439],
16	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	dep	10	SENT_53	[p3l961t374r1176b434],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l961t374r1176b434],
18	1981a	NN	DATE	1981a	appos	16	SENT_53	[p3l1203t370r1453b434],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1203t370r1453b434],
20	b	NN	O	b	appos	16	SENT_53	[p3l1203t370r1453b434],
21	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1203t370r1453b434],
22	Pessagno	NNP	PERSON	Pessagno	dep	10	SENT_53	[p3l1481t374r1754b439],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1777t370r1886b425],
24	Poisson	NNP	PERSON	Poisson	dep	10	SENT_53	[p3l1910t371r2150b434],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1910t371r2150b434],
26	1981	CD	DATE	1981	appos	22	SENT_53	[p3l17t463r180b523],
27	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l17t463r180b523],
28	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	29	SENT_53	[p3l219t463r297b515],
29	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	dep	10	SENT_53	[p3l327t463r541b523],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l327t463r541b523],
31	1982a	NN	DATE	1982a	appos	29	SENT_53	[p3l579t460r855b528],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l579t460r855b528],
33	b	NN	O	b	nn	34	SENT_53	[p3l579t460r855b528],
34	)	NN	O	)	appos	29	SENT_53	[p3l579t460r855b528],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l579t460r855b528],
36	Oman	NNP	LOCATION	Oman	nn	39	SENT_53	[p3l888t463r1068b515],
37	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	39	SENT_53	[p3l1105t460r1208b528],
38	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	39	SENT_53	[p3l1105t460r1208b528],
39	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	appos	29	SENT_53	[p3l1239t463r1442b515],
40	et	FW	O	et	nn	41	SENT_53	[p3l1473t468r1530b515],
41	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	39	SENT_53	[p3l1562t460r1639b523],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1562t460r1639b523],
43	1990	CD	DATE	1990	num	44	SENT_53	[p3l1677t460r1866b528],
44	)	NN	O	)	appos	29	SENT_53	[p3l1677t460r1866b528],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1677t460r1866b528],
46	Slovenia	NNP	LOCATION	Slovenia	conj_and	10	SENT_53	[p3l1900t460r2151b515],
47	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	46	SENT_53	[p3l18t549r275b617],
48	GoriEan	NNP	O	GoriEan	dep	46	SENT_53	[p3l18t549r275b617],
49	et	FW	O	et	nn	50	SENT_53	[p3l296t557r352b604],
50	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	46	SENT_53	[p3l372t549r451b612],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l372t549r451b612],
52	2003	CD	DATE	2003	num	53	SENT_53	[p3l472t549r646b617],
53	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	50	SENT_53	[p3l472t549r646b617],
54	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l671t549r781b604],
55	Austria	NNP	LOCATION	Austria	nn	57	SENT_53	[p3l800t549r1016b604],
56	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	57	SENT_53	[p3l1041t549r1408b617],
57	O'Dogherty	NN	O	o'dogherty	dep	46	SENT_53	[p3l1041t549r1408b617],
58	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1428t549r1537b604],
59	Gawlick	NN	PERSON	gawlick	conj_and	10	SENT_53	[p3l1560t549r1814b612],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1560t549r1814b612],
61	2008	CD	DATE	2008	num	62	SENT_53	[p3l1836t549r2028b617],
62	)	NN	O	)	appos	59	SENT_53	[p3l1836t549r2028b617],
63	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l1836t549r2028b617],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_54	[p3l2047t552r2150b604],
2	note	VBP	O	note	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l14t645r146b692],
3	that	IN	O	that	complm	11	SENT_54	[p3l179t637r299b692],
4	most	JJS	O	most	nsubjpass	11	SENT_54	[p3l330t645r480b692],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l511t637r573b692],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_54	[p3l597t637r693b692],
7	published	VBN	O	publish	amod	9	SENT_54	[p3l726t637r1021b706],
8	taxonomic	JJ	O	taxonomic	amod	9	SENT_54	[p3l1053t638r1372b692],
9	work	NN	O	work	prep_of	4	SENT_54	[p3l1402t637r1560b692],
10	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_54	[p3l1591t638r1634b692],
11	based	VBN	O	base	ccomp	2	SENT_54	[p3l1667t637r1838b692],
12	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1871t653r1946b692],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	41	SENT_54	[p3l1978t653r2009b692],
14	few	JJ	O	few	amod	41	SENT_54	[p3l2041t637r2152b692],
15	excellently	RB	O	excellently	advmod	16	SENT_54	[p3l14t726r341b795],
16	preserved	JJ	O	preserved	amod	41	SENT_54	[p3l372t726r668b795],
17	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l702t726r803b781],
18	isolated	VBN	O	isolate	amod	41	SENT_54	[p3l834t726r1066b781],
19	samples	NNS	O	sample	dobj	18	SENT_54	[p3l1100t726r1341b795],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	19	SENT_54	[p3l1379t726r1501b795],
21	e.g.	FW	O	e.g.	dep	19	SENT_54	[p3l1379t726r1501b795],
22	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	23	SENT_54	[p3l1535t729r1614b781],
23	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	dep	21	SENT_54	[p3l1643t729r1859b790],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1643t729r1859b790],
25	1981a	NN	DATE	1981a	appos	23	SENT_54	[p3l1896t726r2146b789],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1896t726r2146b789],
27	b	NN	O	b	appos	25	SENT_54	[p3l1896t726r2146b789],
28	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1896t726r2146b789],
29	Pessagno	NNP	PERSON	Pessagno	dep	25	SENT_54	[p3l14t819r305b884],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l14t819r305b884],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l352t815r462b870],
32	Poisson	NNP	PERSON	Poisson	dep	25	SENT_54	[p3l508t816r751b879],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l508t816r751b879],
34	1981	CD	DATE	1981	appos	32	SENT_54	[p3l801t818r966b879],
35	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l801t818r966b879],
36	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	37	SENT_54	[p3l1017t819r1095b870],
37	Wever	NNP	PERSON	Wever	dep	25	SENT_54	[p3l1138t819r1355b879],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1138t819r1355b879],
39	1982a	NN	DATE	1982a	appos	37	SENT_54	[p3l1405t815r1658b879],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1405t815r1658b879],
41	b	NN	O	b	prep_on	11	SENT_54	[p3l1405t815r1658b879],
42	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1405t815r1658b879],
43	Yeh	NNP	PERSON	Yeh	dep	41	SENT_54	[p3l1706t815r1836b879],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1706t815r1836b879],
45	1987a	NN	DATE	1987a	appos	43	SENT_54	[p3l1886t815r2146b884],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1886t815r2146b884],
47	b	NN	O	b	appos	43	SENT_54	[p3l1886t815r2146b884],
48	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	47	SENT_54	[p3l1886t815r2146b884],
49	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	59	SENT_54	[p3l12t904r266b959],
50	few	JJ	O	few	amod	52	SENT_54	[p3l291t904r402b959],
51	continuous	JJ	O	continuous	amod	52	SENT_54	[p3l426t905r758b959],
52	sections	NNS	O	section	nsubjpass	59	SENT_54	[p3l785t905r1024b959],
53	suitable	JJ	O	suitable	amod	52	SENT_54	[p3l1051t904r1283b959],
54	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l1309t904r1392b959],
55	biochronological	JJ	O	biochronological	amod	56	SENT_54	[p3l1415t904r1914b973],
56	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_for	53	SENT_54	[p3l1940t904r2150b959],
57	have	VBP	O	have	aux	59	SENT_54	[p3l14t994r154b1049],
58	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	59	SENT_54	[p3l177t994r322b1049],
59	analyzed	VBN	O	analyze	dep	47	SENT_54	[p3l344t994r609b1062],
60	thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	61	SENT_54	[p3l632t994r761b1049],
61	far	RB	O	far	advmod	59	SENT_54	[p3l785t994r877b1049],
62	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l785t994r877b1049],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_55	[p3l898t994r1008b1049],
2	existing	VBG	O	exist	amod	4	SENT_55	[p3l1032t995r1269b1062],
3	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	4	SENT_55	[p3l1290t994r1616b1049],
4	zonations	NNS	O	zonation	nsubjpass	30	SENT_55	[p3l1638t995r1928b1049],
5	for	IN	O	for	prep	4	SENT_55	[p3l1951t994r2034b1049],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_55	[p3l2054t994r2150b1049],
7	Pliensbachian	NN	MISC	pliensbachian	dep	13	SENT_55	[p3l14t1083r426b1138],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l444t1091r502b1138],
9	Aalenian	JJ	MISC	aalenian	amod	10	SENT_55	[p3l520t1083r784b1138],
10	time	NN	O	time	prep_to	7	SENT_55	[p3l802t1083r938b1138],
11	interval	JJ	O	interval	amod	12	SENT_55	[p3l958t1083r1187b1138],
12	(	NN	O	(	dep	13	SENT_55	[p3l1211t1083r1510b1151],
13	Pessagno	NNP	O	Pessagno	dep	5	SENT_55	[p3l1211t1083r1510b1151],
14	et	FW	O	et	nn	15	SENT_55	[p3l1530t1091r1586b1138],
15	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	13	SENT_55	[p3l1604t1083r1682b1146],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1604t1083r1682b1146],
17	1987	CD	DATE	1987	appos	15	SENT_55	[p3l1707t1085r1870b1146],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1707t1085r1870b1146],
19	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	dep	15	SENT_55	[p3l1894t1085r2078b1138],
20	et	FW	O	et	nn	21	SENT_55	[p3l2096t1091r2152b1138],
21	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	19	SENT_55	[p3l14t1171r92b1234],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l14t1171r92b1234],
23	1988	CD	DATE	1988	appos	21	SENT_55	[p3l130t1174r293b1234],
24	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l130t1174r293b1234],
25	Hori	NNP	PERSON	Hori	dep	15	SENT_55	[p3l333t1172r475b1234],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l333t1172r475b1234],
27	1990	CD	DATE	1990	num	28	SENT_55	[p3l514t1171r685b1239],
28	)	NN	O	)	appos	25	SENT_55	[p3l514t1171r685b1239],
29	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	30	SENT_55	[p3l723t1187r815b1226],
30	local	JJ	O	local	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l850t1171r986b1226],
31	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1021t1171r1130b1226],
32	mainly	RB	O	mainly	advmod	33	SENT_55	[p3l1166t1171r1373b1240],
33	characterized	VBN	O	characterize	conj_and	30	SENT_55	[p3l1406t1171r1808b1226],
34	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1843t1171r1917b1240],
35	a	DT	O	a	det	37	SENT_55	[p3l1948t1187r1979b1226],
36	lowresolution	JJ	O	lowresolution	amod	37	SENT_55	[p3l2014t1171r2149b1226, p3l14t1260r317b1315],
37	potential	NN	O	potential	prep_by	33	SENT_55	[p3l347t1260r628b1329],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l347t1260r628b1329],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_56	[p3l656t1260r766b1315],
2	only	RB	O	only	advmod	3	SENT_56	[p3l796t1260r927b1329],
3	high	JJ	O	high	amod	7	SENT_56	[p3l956t1260r1420b1329],
4	?	NN	O	?	nn	7	SENT_56	[p3l956t1260r1420b1329],
5	resolution	NN	O	resolution	nn	7	SENT_56	[p3l956t1260r1420b1329],
6	range	NN	O	range	nn	7	SENT_56	[p3l1451t1276r1618b1329],
7	chart	NN	O	chart	nsubj	11	SENT_56	[p3l1648t1260r1802b1315],
8	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	11	SENT_56	[p3l1831t1261r1874b1315],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_56	[p3l1903t1260r1999b1315],
10	Late	JJ	MISC	late	amod	11	SENT_56	[p3l2030t1263r2150b1315],
11	Pliensbachian	NN	MISC	pliensbachian	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l14t1349r439b1404],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l485t1357r543b1404],
13	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	15	SENT_56	[p3l592t1349r746b1418],
14	Bajocian	JJ	MISC	bajocian	amod	15	SENT_56	[p3l792t1350r1050b1418],
15	zonation	NN	O	zonation	prep_to	11	SENT_56	[p3l1097t1350r1365b1404],
16	constructed	VBN	O	construct	partmod	15	SENT_56	[p3l1412t1349r1775b1404],
17	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1823t1349r1909b1404],
18	Queen	NNP	O	Queen	nn	22	SENT_56	[p3l1954t1352r2150b1415],
19	Charlotte	NNP	LOCATION	Charlotte	nn	22	SENT_56	[p3l14t1438r290b1493],
20	Islands	NNP	LOCATION	Islands	nn	22	SENT_56	[p3l313t1438r519b1493],
21	(	NNP	O	(	nn	22	SENT_56	[p3l547t1438r756b1506],
22	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	prep_for	16	SENT_56	[p3l547t1438r756b1506],
23	et	FW	O	et	nn	24	SENT_56	[p3l778t1446r835b1493],
24	al.	FW	O	al.	tmod	16	SENT_56	[p3l856t1438r934b1501],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l856t1438r934b1501],
26	1988	CD	DATE	1988	num	27	SENT_56	[p3l962t1438r1132b1506],
27	)	NN	O	)	appos	24	SENT_56	[p3l962t1438r1132b1506],
28	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1159t1438r1260b1493],
29	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	30	SENT_56	[p3l1282t1439r1322b1493],
30	contains	VBZ	O	contain	conj_but	11	SENT_56	[p3l1344t1439r1595b1493],
31	an	DT	O	a	det	33	SENT_56	[p3l1619t1454r1691b1493],
32	unfossiliferous	JJ	O	unfossiliferous	amod	33	SENT_56	[p3l1713t1438r2150b1493],
33	interval	NN	O	interval	dobj	30	SENT_56	[p3l14t1527r244b1582],
34	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l266t1528r321b1582],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_56	[p3l343t1527r439b1582],
36	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	37	SENT_56	[p3l461t1527r611b1596],
37	Toarcian	NN	MISC	toarcian	prep_in	33	SENT_56	[p3l629t1528r900b1583],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l629t1528r900b1583],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_57	[p3l113t1616r225b1671],
2	primary	JJ	O	primary	amod	3	SENT_57	[p3l250t1617r496b1685],
3	goal	NN	O	goal	nsubj	7	SENT_57	[p3l517t1616r642b1685],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l667t1616r730b1671],
5	this	DT	O	this	det	6	SENT_57	[p3l746t1616r857b1671],
6	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_of	3	SENT_57	[p3l882t1632r1057b1685],
7	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1079t1617r1124b1671],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_57	[p3l1148t1624r1206b1671],
9	establish	VB	O	establish	xcomp	7	SENT_57	[p3l1231t1616r1500b1671],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_57	[p3l1523t1632r1555b1671],
11	precise	JJ	O	precise	amod	14	SENT_57	[p3l1578t1617r1793b1685],
12	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	14	SENT_57	[p3l1818t1616r2150b1671],
13	range	NN	O	range	nn	14	SENT_57	[p3l14t1721r185b1774],
14	chart	NN	O	chart	dobj	9	SENT_57	[p3l206t1706r364b1761],
15	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	17	SENT_57	[p3l382t1706r505b1761],
16	will	MD	O	will	aux	17	SENT_57	[p3l523t1706r638b1760],
17	serve	VB	O	serve	rcmod	14	SENT_57	[p3l660t1721r820b1761],
18	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l841t1721r900b1761],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_57	[p3l923t1721r954b1761],
20	powerful	JJ	O	powerful	amod	21	SENT_57	[p3l975t1705r1251b1774],
21	tool	NN	O	tool	prep_as	17	SENT_57	[p3l1272t1706r1389b1761],
22	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1411t1705r1496b1761],
23	dating	VBG	O	date	prepc_for	17	SENT_57	[p3l1515t1706r1710b1774],
24	Pliensbachian	NNP	O	Pliensbachian	dobj	23	SENT_57	[p3l1730t1706r2150b1761],
25	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l13t1803r72b1850],
26	Aalenian	NNP	MISC	Aalenian	nn	28	SENT_57	[p3l119t1795r393b1850],
27	pelagic	JJ	O	pelagic	amod	28	SENT_57	[p3l441t1795r659b1863],
28	successions	NNS	O	succession	prep_to	23	SENT_57	[p3l708t1795r1065b1850],
29	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1114t1810r1189b1850],
30	a	DT	O	a	det	32	SENT_57	[p3l1238t1810r1269b1850],
31	global	JJ	O	global	amod	32	SENT_57	[p3l1316t1795r1503b1863],
32	scale	NN	O	scale	prep_on	28	SENT_57	[p3l1553t1795r1717b1850],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1553t1795r1717b1850],

1	We	PRP	O	we	nsubj	2	SENT_58	[p3l1764t1798r1868b1850],
2	present	VBP	DATE	present	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1917t1803r2152b1863],
3	biostratigraphic	JJ	O	biostratigraphic	amod	4	SENT_58	[p3l13t1883r500b1952],
4	ranges	NNS	O	range	dobj	2	SENT_58	[p3l531t1899r730b1952],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l762t1883r826b1938],
6	197	CD	NUMBER	197	num	7	SENT_58	[p3l852t1886r960b1938],
7	species	NNS	O	species	prep_of	4	SENT_58	[p3l994t1884r1210b1952],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1242t1884r1298b1937],
9	220	CD	NUMBER	220	num	10	SENT_58	[p3l1329t1886r1442b1938],
10	samples	NNS	O	sample	prep_in	7	SENT_58	[p3l1474t1883r1719b1952],
11	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1752t1883r1898b1938],
12	various	JJ	O	various	amod	14	SENT_58	[p3l1926t1884r2150b1938],
13	paleogeographic	JJ	O	paleogeographic	amod	14	SENT_58	[p3l14t1972r521b2041],
14	provinces	NNS	O	province	prep_from	2	SENT_58	[p3l565t1973r860b2041],
15	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	16	SENT_58	[p3l905t1972r1028b2027],
16	include	VBP	O	include	rcmod	14	SENT_58	[p3l1072t1972r1296b2027],
17	low	JJ	O	low	acomp	16	SENT_58	[p3l1341t1972r1454b2027],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1497t1972r1608b2027],
19	middle	JJ	O	middle	conj_and	17	SENT_58	[p3l1655t1972r1868b2027],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1912t1980r1971b2027],
21	high	JJ	O	high	amod	22	SENT_58	[p3l2017t1972r2151b2041],
22	paleolatitudes	NNS	O	paleolatitude	prep_to	16	SENT_58	[p3l14t2061r461b2130],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l14t2061r461b2130],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_59	[p3l500t2061r613b2116],
2	zonation	NN	O	zonation	nsubj	4	SENT_59	[p3l654t2062r920b2116],
3	will	MD	O	will	aux	4	SENT_59	[p3l960t2061r1074b2116],
4	have	VB	O	have	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1116t2061r1259b2116],
5	important	JJ	O	important	amod	6	SENT_59	[p3l1300t2062r1610b2130],
6	implications	NNS	O	implication	dobj	4	SENT_59	[p3l1649t2061r2025b2130],
7	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l2068t2061r2152b2116],
8	accurate	JJ	O	accurate	prep_for	4	SENT_59	[p3l14t2159r270b2206],
9	dating	VBG	O	date	xcomp	4	SENT_59	[p3l291t2151r485b2219],
10	around	IN	O	around	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l504t2151r721b2206],
11	one	CD	NUMBER	one	prep_around	9	SENT_59	[p3l742t2167r852b2206],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l873t2151r937b2206],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_59	[p3l949t2151r1046b2206],
14	major	JJ	O	major	amod	18	SENT_59	[p3l1067t2152r1248b2219],
15	ecologic	JJ	O	ecologic	amod	18	SENT_59	[p3l1266t2151r1515b2219],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1533t2151r1644b2206],
17	biotic	JJ	O	biotic	conj_and	15	SENT_59	[p3l1665t2151r1836b2206],
18	crisis	NN	O	crisis	prep_of	11	SENT_59	[p3l1856t2152r2009b2206],
19	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	20	SENT_59	[p3l2029t2151r2152b2206],
20	culminated	VBD	O	culminate	rcmod	18	SENT_59	[p3l14t2240r358b2295],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l387t2240r443b2294],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_59	[p3l471t2240r568b2295],
23	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	24	SENT_59	[p3l596t2239r750b2308],
24	Toarcian	NN	MISC	toarcian	prep_in	20	SENT_59	[p3l773t2240r1051b2295],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l773t2240r1051b2295],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1080t2243r1137b2294],
2	further	JJ	O	further	amod	4	SENT_60	[p3l1165t2239r1381b2295],
3	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	4	SENT_60	[p3l1407t2240r1740b2295],
4	research	NN	O	research	prep_in	8	SENT_60	[p3l1768t2240r2026b2295],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_60	[p3l2053t2240r2150b2295],
6	zonation	NN	O	zonation	nsubj	8	SENT_60	[p3l14t2329r280b2383],
7	can	MD	O	can	aux	8	SENT_60	[p3l300t2344r403b2383],
8	serve	VB	O	serve	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l425t2344r584b2383],
9	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l604t2344r663b2383],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_60	[p3l684t2344r715b2383],
11	basis	NN	O	basis	prep_as	8	SENT_60	[p3l735t2328r883b2383],
12	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l904t2328r990b2383],
13	studying	VBG	O	study	prepc_for	8	SENT_60	[p3l1008t2328r1274b2397],
14	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	16	SENT_60	[p3l1293t2328r1626b2383],
15	faunal	JJ	O	faunal	amod	16	SENT_60	[p3l1646t2328r1834b2383],
16	turnovers	NNS	O	turnover	dobj	13	SENT_60	[p3l1853t2336r2150b2383],
17	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l13t2417r260b2486],
18	this	DT	O	this	det	20	SENT_60	[p3l277t2417r388b2472],
19	critical	JJ	O	critical	amod	20	SENT_60	[p3l406t2417r612b2472],
20	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_through	13	SENT_60	[p3l631t2417r880b2481],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l631t2417r880b2481],
22	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	20	SENT_60	[p3l900t2417r1110b2472],
23	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1126t2425r1185b2472],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_60	[p3l1203t2417r1300b2472],
25	manner	NN	O	manner	prep_to	22	SENT_60	[p3l1319t2433r1559b2472],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1575t2418r1631b2471],
27	which	WDT	O	which	rel	40	SENT_60	[p3l1647t2417r1837b2472],
28	zonations	NNS	O	zonation	nsubjpass	40	SENT_60	[p3l1855t2418r2150b2472],
29	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l13t2506r88b2575],
30	Jud	NN	PERSON	jud	prep_by	28	SENT_60	[p3l129t2506r236b2575],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	30	SENT_60	[p3l291t2506r501b2575],
32	1994	CD	DATE	1994	num	33	SENT_60	[p3l291t2506r501b2575],
33	)	NN	O	)	dep	30	SENT_60	[p3l291t2506r501b2575],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l555t2506r669b2561],
35	O'Dogherty	NN	O	o'dogherty	conj_and	30	SENT_60	[p3l720t2506r1082b2575],
36	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	35	SENT_60	[p3l1134t2506r1344b2575],
37	1994	CD	DATE	1994	num	38	SENT_60	[p3l1134t2506r1344b2575],
38	)	NN	O	)	dep	35	SENT_60	[p3l1134t2506r1344b2575],
39	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	40	SENT_60	[p3l1397t2522r1555b2561],
40	used	VBN	O	use	rcmod	25	SENT_60	[p3l1605t2506r1750b2561],
41	to	TO	O	to	aux	42	SENT_60	[p3l1800t2514r1860b2561],
42	analyze	VB	O	analyze	xcomp	40	SENT_60	[p3l1911t2506r2150b2575],
43	radiolarian	JJ	O	radiolarian	amod	44	SENT_60	[p3l14t2595r357b2650],
44	turnovers	NNS	O	turnover	dobj	42	SENT_60	[p3l405t2603r709b2650],
45	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l759t2595r1011b2664],
46	the	DT	O	the	det	49	SENT_60	[p3l1059t2595r1158b2650],
47	Cretaceous	JJ	O	cretaceous	amod	49	SENT_60	[p3l1208t2598r1549b2650],
48	(	NN	O	(	nn	49	SENT_60	[p3l1603t2595r1989b2664],
49	O'Dogherty	NN	O	o'dogherty	prep_through	42	SENT_60	[p3l1603t2595r1989b2664],
50	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l2037t2595r2150b2650],
51	Guex	NN	O	guex	conj_and	49	SENT_60	[p3l14t2687r185b2748],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l14t2687r185b2748],
53	2002	CD	DATE	2002	num	54	SENT_60	[p3l211t2685r406b2753],
54	)	NN	O	)	appos	49	SENT_60	[p3l211t2685r406b2753],
55	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l211t2685r406b2753],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l433t2688r490b2739],
2	addition	NN	O	addition	prep_in	7	SENT_61	[p3l515t2684r784b2748],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l515t2684r784b2748],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_61	[p3l810t2685r907b2740],
5	vast	JJ	O	vast	amod	6	SENT_61	[p3l930t2693r1055b2740],
6	dataset	NN	O	dataset	nsubj	7	SENT_61	[p3l1079t2684r1301b2740],
7	provides	VBZ	O	provide	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1324t2685r1587b2753],
8	new	JJ	O	new	amod	9	SENT_61	[p3l1613t2700r1744b2740],
9	insights	NNS	O	insight	dobj	7	SENT_61	[p3l1768t2685r2005b2753],
10	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l2031t2685r2150b2740],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_61	[p3l13t2774r110b2829],
12	paleobiogeography	NN	O	paleobiogeography	prep_into	7	SENT_61	[p3l136t2774r725b2842],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l748t2773r811b2829],
14	Jurassic	JJ	O	jurassic	amod	15	SENT_61	[p3l820t2774r1058b2842],
15	radiolarians	NNS	O	radiolarian	prep_of	12	SENT_61	[p3l1082t2774r1459b2829],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1082t2774r1459b2829],
