1	Paleontological	NNP	O	Paleontological	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l17t81r380b129],
2	Society	NNP	O	Society	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l398t81r574b129],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_2	[p1l15t270r92b302],
2	Earliest	JJS	O	earliest	amod	3	SENT_2	[p1l113t270r277b302],
3	Gastrochaenolites	NNS	O	gastrochaenolite	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l298t270r684b302],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_2	[p1l705t266r834b313],
5	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	6	SENT_2	[p1l705t266r834b313],
6	Pennsylvanian	NN	MISC	pennsylvanian	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l855t270r1182b313],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l855t270r1182b313],
8	Arkansas	NNP	LOCATION	Arkansas	nn	10	SENT_2	[p1l1208t270r1416b307],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1208t270r1416b307],
10	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	6	SENT_2	[p1l1442t266r1556b306],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	10	SENT_2	[p1l1442t266r1556b306],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1442t266r1556b306],
13	An	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_2	[p1l1578t270r1640b302],
14	Upper	NNP	O	Upper	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l1661t270r1792b313],
15	Paleozoic	JJ	O	paleozoic	amod	17	SENT_2	[p1l1813t270r2001b302],
16	Bivalve	NNP	O	Bivalve	nn	17	SENT_2	[p1l15t324r169b355],
17	Boring	NNP	O	Boring	dep	14	SENT_2	[p1l190t321r360b368],
18	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l190t321r360b368],

1	Author	NN	O	author	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l15t373r232b413],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_3	[p1l15t373r232b413],
3	s	NNS	O	s	dep	1	SENT_3	[p1l15t373r232b413],
4	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	3	SENT_3	[p1l15t373r232b413],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l15t373r232b413],
6	Mark	NNP	PERSON	Mark	nn	8	SENT_3	[p1l255t377r369b409],
7	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	8	SENT_3	[p1l390t377r432b409],
8	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	Wilson	dep	4	SENT_3	[p1l456t377r604b409],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l625t377r700b409],
10	Timothy	NNP	PERSON	Timothy	nn	13	SENT_3	[p1l721t377r913b420],
11	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	13	SENT_3	[p1l934t377r973b409],
12	Palmer	NNP	PERSON	Palmer	nn	13	SENT_3	[p1l996t377r1147b409],
13	Source	NNP	O	Source	conj_and	8	SENT_3	[p1l15t431r166b463],
14	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l15t431r166b463],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l190t431r363b463],

1	Tourna1	NN	O	tourna1	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l190t431r363b463],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l383t431r433b463],
3	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	nn	5	SENT_4	[p1l448t431r739b476],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l448t431r739b476],
5	Vol	NNP	O	Vol	prep_of	1	SENT_4	[p1l765t431r845b463],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l765t431r845b463],

1	72	CD	NUMBER	72	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l868t431r925b468],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l868t431r925b468],
3	No.	NN	O	no.	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l951t431r1018b463],
4	4	CD	NUMBER	4	number	5	SENT_5	[p1l1042t431r1062b463],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_5	[p1l1084t427r1193b468],
6	Jul	NNP	DATE	Jul	dep	3	SENT_5	[p1l1084t427r1193b468],
7	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1084t427r1193b468],
8	1998	CD	DATE	1998	num	9	SENT_5	[p1l1224t427r1340b468],
9	)	NN	O	)	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l1224t427r1340b468],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1224t427r1340b468],
11	pp	NN	O	pp	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l1366t442r1428b474],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1366t442r1428b474],

1	http://www.j	NN	O	http://www.j	nn	2	SENT_12	[p1l13t1404r222b1442],
2	stor.org	NN	O	stor.org	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l227t1408r353b1442],

1	BUATOIS	NNP	O	BUATOIS	nn	3	SENT_13	[p1l275t1663r436b1692],
2	ET	NNP	O	ET	nn	3	SENT_13	[p1l449t1662r499b1691],
3	AL.	NNP	O	AL.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l507t1662r855b1692],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l507t1662r855b1692],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l507t1662r855b1692],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l507t1662r855b1692],

1	ICHNOGENUS	NN	O	ichnogenus	nn	2	SENT_15	[p1l507t1662r855b1692],
2	CURVOLITHUS	NNS	O	curvolithus	nsubj	3	SENT_15	[p1l867t1661r1144b1691],
3	REVISITED	VBN	O	revisit	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1158t1662r1351b1691],
4	769	CD	NUMBER	769	dobj	3	SENT_15	[p1l1826t1661r1884b1691],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	2	SENT_16	[p1l73t1840r235b1891],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l258t1838r443b1891],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l468t1839r609b1890],
4	an	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_16	[p1l631t1855r698b1891],
5	Upper	NNP	MISC	Upper	nn	8	SENT_16	[p1l721t1839r904b1905],
6	Carboniferous	NNP	MISC	Carboniferous	nn	8	SENT_16	[p1l924t1837r1343b1890],
7	tidal	JJ	O	tidal	amod	8	SENT_16	[p1l1367t1837r1494b1890],
8	shoreline	NN	O	shoreline	prep_from	2	SENT_16	[p1l1518t1837r1785b1889],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_16	[p1l1808t1837r1967b1901],
10	Stull	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stull	nn	12	SENT_16	[p1l1808t1837r1967b1901],
11	Shale	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Shale	nn	12	SENT_16	[p1l1989t1837r2149b1889],
12	Member	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Member	dep	2	SENT_16	[p1l74t1916r326b1968],
13	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l350t1915r414b1968],
14	Eastern	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Eastern	nn	16	SENT_16	[p1l434t1917r653b1968],
15	Kansas	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Kansas	nn	16	SENT_16	[p1l681t1916r932b1977],
16	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	12	SENT_16	[p1l681t1916r932b1977],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l681t1916r932b1977],

1	30th	JJ	ORDINAL	30th	amod	4	SENT_17	[p1l961t1914r1089b1966],
2	Intemational	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Intemational	nn	4	SENT_17	[p1l1114t1913r1489b1966],
3	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	4	SENT_17	[p1l1514t1913r1835b1980],
4	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Congress	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1859t1913r2148b1980],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1859t1913r2148b1980],
6	Beijing	NNP	LOCATION	Beijing	appos	4	SENT_17	[p1l74t1992r307b2060],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l74t1992r307b2060],

1	Abstract	JJ	O	abstract	amod	2	SENT_18	[p1l338t1992r587b2044],
2	Volume	NN	O	volume	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l612t1992r842b2044],
3	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	2	SENT_18	[p1l870t1991r920b2052],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l870t1991r920b2052],
5	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	2	SENT_18	[p1l950t2007r1001b2058],
6	133	CD	NUMBER	133	num	5	SENT_18	[p1l1038t1991r1155b2043],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1038t1991r1155b2043],

1	MAPLES	NNP	LOCATION	MAPLES	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l6t2071r263b2130],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l6t2071r263b2130],
3	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	nn	4	SENT_19	[p1l300t2070r363b2122],
4	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	appos	1	SENT_19	[p1l399t2070r486b2130],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l399t2070r486b2130],
6	AND	NNP	O	AND	nn	9	SENT_19	[p1l522t2082r645b2121],
7	L.	NNP	PERSON	L.	nn	9	SENT_19	[p1l678t2070r737b2122],
8	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	9	SENT_19	[p1l773t2070r817b2121],
9	SUTTNER	NNP	PERSON	SUTTNER	appos	4	SENT_19	[p1l855t2069r1135b2121],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l855t2069r1135b2121],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1179t2068r1333b2120],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1179t2068r1333b2120],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	2	SENT_21	[p1l1370t2069r1531b2121],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1565t2067r1750b2120],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1785t2067r1890b2120],
4	marinenonmarine	NN	O	marinenonmarine	nn	5	SENT_21	[p1l1922t2067r2148b2119, p1l75t2147r390b2199],
5	cyclicity	NN	O	cyclicity	conj_and	2	SENT_21	[p1l416t2146r667b2213],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l697t2147r750b2198],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_21	[p1l776t2148r865b2198],
8	Fountain	NNP	MISC	Fountain	prep_in	5	SENT_21	[p1l890t2146r1151b2198],
9	Formation	NN	MISC	formation	nn	11	SENT_21	[p1l1177t2146r1483b2197],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_21	[p1l1509t2145r1977b2211],
11	Pennsylvanian	NNP	MISC	Pennsylvanian	dep	5	SENT_21	[p1l1509t2145r1977b2211],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1509t2145r1977b2211],
13	Morrowian/Atokan	NN	O	morrowian/atokan	nn	14	SENT_21	[p1l2005t2146r2148b2196, p1l75t2225r541b2286],
14	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_21	[p1l2005t2146r2148b2196, p1l75t2225r541b2286],
15	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l572t2239r699b2276],
16	Manitou	NNP	LOCATION	Manitou	nn	17	SENT_21	[p1l726t2224r974b2275],
17	Springs	NNP	LOCATION	Springs	prep_near	14	SENT_21	[p1l1005t2223r1244b2290],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1005t2223r1244b2290],
19	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	Colorado	appos	17	SENT_21	[p1l1275t2222r1563b2275],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1275t2222r1563b2275],

1	Joumal	NNP	O	Joumal	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1594t2223r1809b2275],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1840t2221r1903b2274],
3	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	prep_of	1	SENT_22	[p1l1927t2222r2148b2274, p1l75t2300r277b2367],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1927t2222r2148b2274, p1l75t2300r277b2367],
5	64:859	CD	NUMBER	64:859	num	6	SENT_22	[p1l308t2300r678b2352],
6	-880	CD	NUMBER	-880	appos	3	SENT_22	[p1l308t2300r678b2352],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l308t2300r678b2352],

1	METZ	NNP	O	METZ	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l9t2380r194b2438],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l9t2380r194b2438],
3	R.	NNP	O	R.	appos	1	SENT_23	[p1l223t2380r285b2430],
4	1989	CD	DATE	1989	num	3	SENT_23	[p1l324t2379r476b2430],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l324t2379r476b2430],

1	Scoyenia	NNP	O	Scoyenia	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l506t2379r772b2443],
2	ichnofacies	NNS	O	ichnofacy	dep	1	SENT_24	[p1l801t2377r1132b2430],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1161t2378r1302b2429],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_24	[p1l1328t2377r1415b2429],
5	Passaic	NNP	O	Passaic	nn	6	SENT_24	[p1l1443t2376r1656b2429],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	2	SENT_24	[p1l1684t2375r1989b2429],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_24	[p1l2015t2378r2149b2443, p1l76t2470r171b2521],
8	Upper	NNP	O	Upper	nn	10	SENT_24	[p1l2015t2378r2149b2443, p1l76t2470r171b2521],
9	Triassic	NNP	O	Triassic	nn	10	SENT_24	[p1l205t2455r455b2517],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_24	[p1l205t2455r455b2517],
11	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l492t2470r619b2506],
12	Milford	NNP	LOCATION	Milford	prep_near	10	SENT_24	[p1l653t2454r897b2514],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l653t2454r897b2514],
14	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	15	SENT_24	[p1l935t2455r1070b2505],
15	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	appos	1	SENT_24	[p1l1106t2455r1303b2520],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1106t2455r1303b2520],

1	Northeastem	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Northeastem	nn	2	SENT_25	[p1l1340t2453r1719b2505],
2	Geology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geology	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1755t2452r2021b2520],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1755t2452r2021b2520],
4	11	CD	NUMBER	11	num	6	SENT_25	[p1l2066t2454r2145b2504],
5	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l2066t2454r2145b2504],
6	212-217	CD	NUMBER	212-217	appos	2	SENT_25	[p1l79t2532r350b2583],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l79t2532r350b2583],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l161t2653r170b2662],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l220t2611r374b2663],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l220t2611r374b2663],

1	Discussion	NN	O	discussion	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l415t2611r754b2662],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l415t2611r754b2662],

1	Scoyenia	NNP	O	Scoyenia	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l795t2612r1060b2675],
2	ichnofacies	NNS	O	ichnofacy	dep	1	SENT_29	[p1l1100t2609r1432b2662],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1472t2609r1613b2661],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_29	[p1l1652t2609r1739b2661],
5	Passaic	NNP	O	Passaic	nn	6	SENT_29	[p1l1778t2608r1991b2661],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	2	SENT_29	[p1l2030t2611r2149b2661, p1l78t2688r279b2739],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_29	[p1l310t2688r518b2753],
8	Upper	NNP	O	Upper	nn	10	SENT_29	[p1l310t2688r518b2753],
9	Triassic	NNP	O	Triassic	nn	10	SENT_29	[p1l544t2687r794b2748],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_29	[p1l544t2687r794b2748],
11	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l824t2702r950b2738],
12	Milford	NNP	LOCATION	Milford	prep_near	10	SENT_29	[p1l976t2686r1219b2745],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l976t2686r1219b2745],
14	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	15	SENT_29	[p1l1248t2687r1386b2738],
15	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	appos	1	SENT_29	[p1l1412t2687r1609b2752],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1412t2687r1609b2752],

1	Northeastem	NNP	O	Northeastem	nn	2	SENT_30	[p1l1638t2686r2016b2738],
2	Geology	NNP	O	Geology	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l2041t2685r2149b2737, p1l77t2763r259b2830],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l2041t2685r2149b2737, p1l77t2763r259b2830],
4	12:159	CD	NUMBER	12:159	num	5	SENT_30	[p1l296t2763r659b2815],
5	-161	CD	NUMBER	-161	appos	2	SENT_30	[p1l296t2763r659b2815],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l296t2763r659b2815],

1	MIKULAS	NNP	LOCATION	MIKULAS	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l10t2841r290b2900],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l10t2841r290b2900],
3	R.	NNP	O	R.	appos	1	SENT_31	[p1l318t2842r378b2892],
4	1987	CD	DATE	1987	num	3	SENT_31	[p1l415t2842r561b2893],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l415t2842r561b2893],

1	Ichnofosilie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ichnofosilie	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l590t2840r922b2892],
2	v	LS	O	v	dep	1	SENT_32	[p1l949t2856r981b2890],
3	kosovsk?m	NN	O	kosovsk?m	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l1006t2840r1323b2892],
4	souvrstvi	NN	O	souvrstvus	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l1350t2840r1600b2892],
5	cesk?ho	NN	O	cesk?ho	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1626t2840r1852b2892],
6	svrchniho	NN	O	svrchniho	dep	7	SENT_32	[p1l1878t2839r2151b2891],
7	ordoviku	NN	O	ordoviku	amod	5	SENT_32	[p1l78t2918r344b2970],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l78t2918r344b2970],

1	Diplomova	NN	O	diplomova	nn	2	SENT_33	[p1l375t2918r693b2984],
2	prace	NN	O	prace	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l716t2917r868b2984],
3	Prirodoved	NNP	O	Prirodoved	dep	2	SENT_33	[p1l893t2917r1217b2969],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l893t2917r1217b2969],

1	fak	NN	O	fak	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1245t2916r1347b2968],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1245t2916r1347b2968],

1	Univ.	NNP	O	Univ.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1377t2916r1528b2969],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1377t2916r1528b2969],

1	Karl	NNP	PERSON	Karl	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1557t2917r1692b2968],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1557t2917r1692b2968],

1	Praha	NN	O	praha	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1721t2917r1894b2968],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1721t2917r1894b2968],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l162t3039r170b3047],

1	1992	CD	DATE	1992	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l219t2995r365b3048],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l219t2995r365b3048],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	2	SENT_40	[p1l404t2996r559b3047],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l595t2995r770b3047],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l809t2994r945b3046],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_40	[p1l981t2995r1065b3046],
5	Kosov	NNP	MISC	Kosov	nn	6	SENT_40	[p1l1101t2996r1284b3047],
6	Formation	NN	MISC	formation	prep_from	2	SENT_40	[p1l1320t2994r1613b3046],
7	of	IN	MISC	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l1649t2994r1711b3045],
8	the	DT	MISC	the	det	11	SENT_40	[p1l1742t2994r1827b3046],
9	Bohemian	NNP	MISC	Bohemian	nn	11	SENT_40	[p1l1861t2994r2150b3046],
10	Upper	NNP	MISC	Upper	nn	11	SENT_40	[p1l78t3073r256b3139],
11	Ordovician	NNP	MISC	Ordovician	prep_of	2	SENT_40	[p1l281t3071r609b3124],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l281t3071r609b3124],

1	Sbomik	NNP	O	Sbomik	nn	2	SENT_41	[p1l638t3071r860b3124],
2	geologickych	NNP	O	geologickych	nsubj	3	SENT_41	[p1l886t3071r1261b3139],
3	ved	VBD	O	ved	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1289t3071r1403b3131],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1289t3071r1403b3131],
5	Paleontologie	NN	O	paleontologie	dobj	3	SENT_41	[p1l1431t3070r1829b3138],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1431t3070r1829b3138],
7	3229-54	CD	NUMBER	3229-54	appos	5	SENT_41	[p1l1857t3070r2103b3123],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l1857t3070r2103b3123],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l161t3190r171b3200],

1	1994a	NN	O	1994a	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l212t3148r389b3200],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l212t3148r389b3200],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	2	SENT_44	[p1l425t3149r577b3200],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l610t3148r784b3200],
3	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l817t3157r867b3200],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_44	[p1l897t3148r981b3200],
5	Arenig-Llanvirn	NNP	MISC	Arenig-Llanvirn	prep_at	2	SENT_44	[p1l1011t3147r1470b3215],
6	boundary	NN	O	boundary	nn	8	SENT_44	[p1l1500t3147r1766b3213],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_44	[p1l1799t3147r2150b3210],
8	Ordovician	NNP	MISC	Ordovician	dep	2	SENT_44	[p1l1799t3147r2150b3210],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1799t3147r2150b3210],
10	Czech	NNP	LOCATION	Czech	nn	12	SENT_44	[p1l77t3226r253b3278],
11	Republic	NNP	LOCATION	Republic	nn	12	SENT_44	[p1l280t3226r568b3292],
12	)	NN	O	)	appos	8	SENT_44	[p1l280t3226r568b3292],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l280t3226r568b3292],

1	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l597t3226r802b3278],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l829t3226r892b3277],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_45	[p1l911t3226r996b3278],
4	Czech	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Czech	nn	6	SENT_45	[p1l1022t3225r1197b3277],
5	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	6	SENT_45	[p1l1222t3225r1528b3292],
6	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_of	1	SENT_45	[p1l1555t3225r1774b3291],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1555t3225r1774b3291],
8	39:205	CD	NUMBER	39:205	num	9	SENT_45	[p1l1801t3224r2148b3277],
9	-210	CD	NUMBER	-210	appos	6	SENT_45	[p1l1801t3224r2148b3277],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1801t3224r2148b3277],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l162t3346r171b3355],

1	1994b	NN	O	1994b	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l210t3303r400b3356],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l210t3303r400b3356],

1	New	NNP	O	New	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l430t3304r567b3355],
2	?nds	NNS	O	?nds	dep	1	SENT_48	[p1l595t3303r734b3355],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l764t3303r828b3354],
4	trace	NN	O	trace	nn	5	SENT_48	[p1l849t3312r990b3355],
5	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	prep_of	2	SENT_48	[p1l1017t3302r1202b3355],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l1231t3302r1373b3354],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_48	[p1l1399t3302r1486b3354],
8	Bohdaled	NNP	O	Bohdaled	prep_from	5	SENT_48	[p1l1512t3302r1792b3354],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l1820t3302r1922b3354],
10	Kraluv	NNP	PERSON	Kraluv	prep_from	5	SENT_48	[p1l1950t3302r2150b3354],

1	Dvur	NNP	O	Dvur	nn	5	SENT_49	[p2l78t20r230b71],
2	Formations	NNPS	O	Formations	nn	5	SENT_49	[p2l260t20r594b71],
3	(	NNP	O	(	nn	5	SENT_49	[p2l629t20r782b81],
4	Late	NNP	MISC	Late	nn	5	SENT_49	[p2l629t20r782b81],
5	Ordovician	NNP	MISC	Ordovician	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l815t19r1160b79],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l815t19r1160b79],
7	Barrandian	NNP	LOCATION	Barrandian	nn	8	SENT_49	[p2l1194t18r1521b70],
8	area	NN	O	area	appos	5	SENT_49	[p2l1554t33r1689b77],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1554t33r1689b77],
10	Czech	NNP	LOCATION	Czech	nn	12	SENT_49	[p2l1723t18r1904b70],
11	Republic	NNP	LOCATION	Republic	nn	12	SENT_49	[p2l1936t18r2149b85, p2l78t96r189b159],
12	)	NN	O	)	appos	8	SENT_49	[p2l1936t18r2149b85, p2l78t96r189b159],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1936t18r2149b85, p2l78t96r189b159],

1	Joumal	NNP	PERSON	Joumal	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l219t96r434b149],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l464t96r527b148],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_50	[p2l549t96r638b147],
4	Czech	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Czech	nn	6	SENT_50	[p2l666t96r847b148],
5	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	6	SENT_50	[p2l875t95r1197b162],
6	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_of	1	SENT_50	[p2l1226t95r1458b162],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1226t95r1458b162],
8	39:303	CD	NUMBER	39:303	num	9	SENT_50	[p2l1488t95r1852b148],
9	-312	CD	NUMBER	-312	appos	6	SENT_50	[p2l1488t95r1852b148],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1488t95r1852b148],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l162t216r171b225],

1	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l214t174r267b225],
2	press	NN	O	press	pobj	1	SENT_52	[p2l305t189r470b240],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l305t189r470b240],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l512t174r673b226],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	dep	1	SENT_53	[p2l710t173r893b225],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l934t174r1074b225],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_53	[p2l1111t174r1199b225],
5	Letna	NNP	O	Letna	prep_from	2	SENT_53	[p2l1235t174r1403b225],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	8	SENT_53	[p2l1438t172r1743b225],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_53	[p2l1781t173r2150b236],
8	Ordovician	NNP	MISC	Ordovician	dep	5	SENT_53	[p2l1781t173r2150b236],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1781t173r2150b236],

1	Czech	NNP	LOCATION	Czech	nn	2	SENT_54	[p2l77t251r260b304],
2	Republic	NNP	LOCATION	Republic	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l289t251r593b318],
3	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_54	[p2l289t251r593b318],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l289t251r593b318],

1	Sbornik	NNP	O	Sbornik	nn	2	SENT_55	[p2l625t251r856b325],
2	geologickych	NNP	O	geologickych	nsubj	3	SENT_55	[p2l885t250r1279b319],
3	ved	VBD	O	ved	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1308t251r1427b312],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1308t251r1427b312],
5	Paleontologie	NNP	PERSON	Paleontologie	dep	3	SENT_55	[p2l1457t250r1875b318],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1457t250r1875b318],

1	MULLER	NNP	LOCATION	MULLER	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l11t330r276b388],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l11t330r276b388],
3	A.	NNP	O	A.	nn	4	SENT_56	[p2l312t329r379b380],
4	H.	NNP	O	H.	appos	1	SENT_56	[p2l418t330r482b380],
5	1969	CD	DATE	1969	dep	4	SENT_56	[p2l529t328r682b380],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l529t328r682b380],

1	Uber	NNP	O	Uber	nn	2	SENT_57	[p2l720t317r867b380],
2	ein	NN	O	ein	nsubj	3	SENT_57	[p2l900t329r987b379],
3	neues	VBZ	O	neue	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1022t343r1185b379],
4	Ichnogenus	NNP	O	Ichnogenus	nsubj	12	SENT_57	[p2l1222t328r1557b394],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_57	[p2l1596t328r1841b391],
6	Tambia	NNP	O	Tambia	nn	12	SENT_57	[p2l1596t328r1841b391],
7	n.g.	NNP	O	n.g.	nn	12	SENT_57	[p2l1876t329r2007b394],
8	)	NNP	O	)	nn	12	SENT_57	[p2l1876t329r2007b394],
9	und	NN	O	und	nn	12	SENT_57	[p2l2042t328r2149b379],
10	andere	NN	O	andere	nn	12	SENT_57	[p2l78t405r273b457],
11	Problematica	NNP	O	Problematica	nn	12	SENT_57	[p2l300t405r689b457],
12	aus	NN	O	aus	xcomp	3	SENT_57	[p2l715t420r808b457],
13	dem	DT	O	dem	det	16	SENT_57	[p2l837t405r962b457],
14	Rotliegenden	JJ	PERSON	rotliegenden	amod	16	SENT_57	[p2l988t405r1379b472],
15	(	NN	O	(	nn	16	SENT_57	[p2l1406t405r1770b471],
16	Unterperm	NN	O	unterperm	dep	12	SENT_57	[p2l1406t405r1770b471],
17	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	18	SENT_57	[p2l1406t405r1770b471],
18	von	NN	O	von	dep	12	SENT_57	[p2l1797t420r1904b456],
19	Th1	NN	O	th1	nn	21	SENT_57	[p2l1928t405r2150b456, p2l79t498r199b549],
20	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1928t405r2150b456, p2l79t498r199b549],
21	iringen	NN	O	iringen	dep	18	SENT_57	[p2l1928t405r2150b456, p2l79t498r199b549],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l1928t405r2150b456, p2l79t498r199b549],

1	Deutsch	NNP	PERSON	Deutsch	nn	7	SENT_58	[p2l230t483r468b535],
2	Akademie	NNP	PERSON	Akademie	nn	7	SENT_58	[p2l496t483r798b535],
3	der	FW	PERSON	der	nn	7	SENT_58	[p2l824t483r919b534],
4	Wissenchaften	NNP	PERSON	Wissenchaften	nn	7	SENT_58	[p2l942t482r1373b535],
5	zu	NNP	O	zu	nn	7	SENT_58	[p2l1400t498r1467b533],
6	Berlin	NNP	LOCATION	Berlin	nn	7	SENT_58	[p2l1492t482r1674b534],
7	Abhandlungen	NNP	LOCATION	Abhandlungen	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1698t482r2150b549],
8	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1698t482r2150b549],
9	Monatsberichte	NNP	O	Monatsberichte	nn	13	SENT_58	[p2l79t559r554b618],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l79t559r554b618],
11	Geologie	NNP	PERSON	Geologie	appos	13	SENT_58	[p2l582t559r851b625],
12	und	NN	O	und	nn	13	SENT_58	[p2l878t559r986b610],
13	Mineralogie	NNP	O	Mineralogie	dep	7	SENT_58	[p2l1014t558r1390b625],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1014t558r1390b625],
15	11:922	CD	NUMBER	11:922	num	16	SENT_58	[p2l1426t558r1783b611],
16	-932	CD	NUMBER	-932	appos	13	SENT_58	[p2l1426t558r1783b611],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1426t558r1783b611],

1	NARBONNE	NNP	LOCATION	NARBONNE	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l10t637r358b695],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l10t637r358b695],
3	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	4	SENT_59	[p2l387t636r453b688],
4	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	appos	1	SENT_59	[p2l485t637r583b695],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l485t637r583b695],
6	AND	NNP	O	AND	nn	9	SENT_59	[p2l613t649r736b687],
7	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	9	SENT_59	[p2l764t636r806b687],
8	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	9	SENT_59	[p2l837t637r915b688],
9	MYROW	NNP	PERSON	MYROW	appos	4	SENT_59	[p2l946t637r1201b688],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l946t637r1201b688],

1	1988	CD	DATE	1988	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l1240t635r1392b688],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l1240t635r1392b688],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	3	SENT_61	[p2l1423t636r1584b688],
2	fossil	NN	O	fossil	nn	3	SENT_61	[p2l1611t635r1767b688],
3	biostratigraphy	NN	O	biostratigraphy	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1794t636r2151b703, p2l79t713r186b779],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l216t714r268b765],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_61	[p2l297t713r384b765],
6	Precambrian-Cambrian	JJ	MISC	precambrian-cambrian	amod	8	SENT_61	[p2l410t713r1099b765],
7	boundary	NN	O	boundary	nn	8	SENT_61	[p2l1124t713r1404b779],
8	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_in	3	SENT_61	[p2l1433t713r1675b772],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1433t713r1675b772],
10	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	8	SENT_61	[p2l1703t728r1752b779],
11	72-76	CD	NUMBER	72-76	num	10	SENT_61	[p2l1781t713r1977b764],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1781t713r1977b764],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l2005t715r2064b764],
2	E.	NNP	O	E.	pobj	1	SENT_62	[p2l2088t714r2148b764],
3	Landing	NN	O	landing	rcmod	2	SENT_62	[p2l78t790r340b856],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l78t790r340b856],
5	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	7	SENT_62	[p2l368t790r434b842],
6	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	7	SENT_62	[p2l464t792r542b842],
7	Narbonne	NNP	PERSON	Narbonne	appos	3	SENT_62	[p2l571t791r877b850],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l571t791r877b850],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l905t790r1009b842],
10	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	13	SENT_62	[p2l1036t791r1077b841],
11	Myrow	NNP	PERSON	Myrow	nn	13	SENT_62	[p2l1106t792r1320b856],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_62	[p2l1348t790r1526b853],
13	eds	NNS	O	ed	appos	3	SENT_62	[p2l1348t790r1526b853],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1348t790r1526b853],
15	)	SYM	O	)	dep	3	SENT_62	[p2l1348t790r1526b853],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1348t790r1526b853],
2	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	dep	3	SENT_63	[p2l1553t791r1714b842],
3	Fossils	NNPS	O	Fossils	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1739t790r1958b850],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1739t790r1958b850],
5	Small	JJ	O	small	amod	7	SENT_63	[p2l1983t790r2151b842],
6	Shelly	NNP	O	Shelly	nn	7	SENT_63	[p2l80t867r264b934],
7	Fossils	NNPS	O	Fossils	appos	3	SENT_63	[p2l298t868r498b920],
8	and	CC	O	and	prep	3	SENT_63	[p2l532t868r635b919],
9	the	DT	O	the	dep	8	SENT_63	[p2l667t868r754b919],
10	Precambrian-Cambrian	JJ	MISC	precambrian-cambrian	amod	11	SENT_63	[p2l785t867r1483b920],
11	boundary	NN	O	boundary	dep	9	SENT_63	[p2l1515t867r1808b934],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1515t867r1808b934],

1	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	4	SENT_64	[p2l1841t868r1977b919],
2	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	nn	4	SENT_64	[p2l2009t868r2151b920],
3	State	NNP	LOCATION	State	nn	4	SENT_64	[p2l79t944r223b996],
4	Museum	NNP	LOCATION	Museum	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l251t946r524b1004],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l251t946r524b1004],
6	Bulletin	NNP	O	Bulletin	appos	4	SENT_64	[p2l553t944r806b1004],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l553t944r806b1004],
8	463	CD	NUMBER	463	appos	6	SENT_64	[p2l835t944r959b997],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l835t944r959b997],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l160t1062r172b1080],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l356t1062r368b1080],
3	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l402t1034r524b1072],
4	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	5	SENT_65	[p2l557t1022r635b1072],
5	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	6	SENT_65	[p2l671t1023r748b1072],
6	ANDERSON	NNP	PERSON	ANDERSON	conj_and	1	SENT_65	[p2l783t1022r1123b1073],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l783t1022r1123b1073],

1	1987	CD	DATE	1987	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l1166t1021r1317b1073],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l1166t1021r1317b1073],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_67	[p2l1353t1022r1404b1072],
2	candidate	NN	O	candidate	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l1435t1021r1717b1073],
3	stratotype	NN	O	stratotype	dep	2	SENT_67	[p2l1749t1030r2037b1087],
4	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l2068t1022r2153b1073],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_67	[p2l77t1098r166b1150],
6	Precambrian-Cambrian	JJ	MISC	precambrian-cambrian	amod	7	SENT_67	[p2l190t1098r876b1150],
7	boundary	NN	O	boundary	prep_for	3	SENT_67	[p2l900t1098r1196b1164],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l900t1098r1196b1164],
9	Fortune	NNP	O	Fortune	nn	10	SENT_67	[p2l1221t1099r1447b1149],
10	Head	NNP	O	Head	appos	7	SENT_67	[p2l1468t1099r1639b1158],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l1468t1099r1639b1158],
12	Burin	NNP	LOCATION	Burin	nn	13	SENT_67	[p2l1662t1098r1826b1150],
13	Peninsula	NNP	LOCATION	Peninsula	appos	10	SENT_67	[p2l1848t1098r2149b1158],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l1848t1098r2149b1158],

1	southeastem	NN	O	southeastem	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l76t1486r441b1539],
2	Newfoundland	NNP	LOCATION	Newfoundland	dep	1	SENT_70	[p2l468t1485r920b1538],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l468t1485r920b1538],

1	Canadian	JJ	MISC	canadian	amod	2	SENT_71	[p2l949t1486r1224b1539],
2	Joumal	NN	O	joumal	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1248t1486r1466b1538],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1492t1485r1556b1537],
4	Earth	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Earth	nn	5	SENT_71	[p2l1575t1485r1733b1538],
5	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_of	2	SENT_71	[p2l1758t1485r2030b1545],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1758t1485r2030b1545],
7	24	CD	NUMBER	24	num	9	SENT_71	[p2l2056t1486r2142b1537],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l2056t1486r2142b1537],
9	1277-1293	CD	DATE	1277-1293	appos	5	SENT_71	[p2l82t1561r421b1613],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l82t1561r421b1613],

1	OSGOOD	NNP	LOCATION	OSGOOD	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l9t1639r274b1699],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l9t1639r274b1699],
3	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	5	SENT_72	[p2l307t1639r368b1690],
4	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	5	SENT_72	[p2l401t1638r468b1690],
5	JR.	NNP	PERSON	JR.	appos	1	SENT_72	[p2l498t1639r580b1690],
6	1970	CD	DATE	1970	dep	5	SENT_72	[p2l620t1638r773b1690],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l620t1638r773b1690],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	2	SENT_73	[p2l807t1638r968b1690],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l997t1637r1183b1690],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l1214t1637r1278b1690],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_73	[p2l1302t1638r1391b1690],
5	Cincinnati	NNP	LOCATION	Cincinnati	nn	6	SENT_73	[p2l1421t1637r1724b1690],
6	area	NN	O	area	prep_of	2	SENT_73	[p2l1757t1652r1892b1689],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l1757t1652r1892b1689],

1	Paleontographica	NN	LOCATION	paleontographica	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l1925t1637r2146b1689, p2l75t1715r387b1783],

1	Americana	NNS	O	americana	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l411t1715r750b1777],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l411t1715r750b1777],
3	62279-444	CD	NUMBER	62279-444	appos	1	SENT_75	[p2l779t1714r1116b1768],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l779t1714r1116b1768],

1	PICKERILL	NNP	O	PICKERILL	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l7t1794r327b1852],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l7t1794r327b1852],
3	R.	NNP	O	R.	nn	4	SENT_76	[p2l355t1792r417b1844],
4	K.	NNP	O	K.	appos	1	SENT_76	[p2l447t1792r512b1844],
5	1990	CD	DATE	1990	dep	4	SENT_76	[p2l548t1792r701b1844],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l548t1792r701b1844],

1	Discussion	NN	O	discussion	_	0	SENT_77	[p2l731t1791r1068b1844],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p2l731t1791r1068b1844],

1	Scoyenia	NNP	O	Scoyenia	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1097t1793r1361b1857],
2	ichnofacies	NNS	O	ichnofacy	dep	1	SENT_78	[p2l1388t1790r1719b1844],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1746t1790r1887b1843],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_78	[p2l1911t1790r2000b1843],
5	Passaic	NNP	O	Passaic	nn	6	SENT_78	[p2l2024t1792r2147b1843, p2l77t1870r187b1922],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	2	SENT_78	[p2l227t1870r532b1923],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_78	[p2l572t1870r779b1937],
8	Upper	NNP	O	Upper	nn	10	SENT_78	[p2l572t1870r779b1937],
9	Triassic	NNP	O	Triassic	nn	10	SENT_78	[p2l813t1870r1063b1932],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_78	[p2l813t1870r1063b1932],
11	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1102t1884r1228b1922],
12	Milford	NNP	LOCATION	Milford	prep_near	10	SENT_78	[p2l1262t1869r1506b1929],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1262t1869r1506b1929],
14	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	15	SENT_78	[p2l1545t1870r1681b1921],
15	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	appos	1	SENT_78	[p2l1718t1869r1914b1936],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1718t1869r1914b1936],

1	Northeastern	JJ	O	northeastern	amod	2	SENT_79	[p2l1953t1868r2146b1921, p2l76t1956r281b2000],
2	Geology	NN	O	geology	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l310t1946r576b2014],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l310t1946r576b2014],
4	12:156	CD	NUMBER	12:156	num	5	SENT_79	[p2l613t1946r971b1999],
5	-159	CD	NUMBER	-159	appos	2	SENT_79	[p2l613t1946r971b1999],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l613t1946r971b1999],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_80	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_82	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l7t2050r170b2082],
2	AND	CC	O	and	cc	3	SENT_84	[p2l205t2036r329b2074],
3	J.	NNP	O	J.	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l361t2023r404b2074],
4	S.	NNP	O	S.	nn	5	SENT_84	[p2l443t2023r494b2075],
5	PEEL	NNP	O	PEEL	dep	3	SENT_84	[p2l531t2023r691b2074],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l531t2023r691b2074],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l735t2022r888b2074],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l735t2022r888b2074],

1	Trace	NNP	O	Trace	nn	2	SENT_86	[p2l926t2024r1086b2074],
2	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l1120t2022r1305b2074],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l1339t2022r1482b2074],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_86	[p2l1514t2022r1602b2074],
5	Lower	NNP	O	Lower	nn	8	SENT_86	[p2l1635t2023r1828b2074],
6	Cambrian	NNP	O	Cambrian	nn	8	SENT_86	[p2l1859t2022r2147b2074],
7	Bastion	NNP	O	Bastion	nn	8	SENT_86	[p2l76t2101r299b2153],
8	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	2	SENT_86	[p2l333t2100r638b2153],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l672t2100r736b2152],
10	North	NNP	O	North	prep_of	2	SENT_86	[p2l763t2100r1098b2152],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l763t2100r1098b2152],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l763t2100r1098b2152],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l763t2100r1098b2152],

1	East	NNP	MISC	East	nn	2	SENT_88	[p2l763t2100r1098b2152],
2	Greenlans	NNP	MISC	Greenlans	_	0	SENT_88	[p2l1128t2099r1442b2153],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_88	[p2l1128t2099r1442b2153],

1	Gremlands	NNP	PERSON	Gremlands	nn	3	SENT_89	[p2l1476t2099r1781b2159],
2	Geologiske	NNP	PERSON	Geologiske	nn	3	SENT_89	[p2l1813t2099r2147b2167],
3	Undersogelse	NNP	PERSON	Undersogelse	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l76t2176r492b2244],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l76t2176r492b2244],
5	Rapport	NNP	O	Rapport	appos	3	SENT_89	[p2l520t2177r773b2243],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l520t2177r773b2243],
7	147:5	CD	NUMBER	147:5	number	8	SENT_89	[p2l809t2176r1098b2228],
8	?	CD	NUMBER	?	appos	3	SENT_89	[p2l809t2176r1098b2228],
9	43	CD	NUMBER	43	dep	8	SENT_89	[p2l809t2176r1098b2228],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l809t2176r1098b2228],

1	RINDSBERG	NNP	LOCATION	RINDSBERG	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l9t2255r360b2314],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l9t2255r360b2314],
3	A.	NNP	O	A.	nn	4	SENT_90	[p2l383t2255r449b2306],
4	K.	NNP	O	K.	appos	1	SENT_90	[p2l475t2254r541b2306],
5	1994	CD	DATE	1994	dep	4	SENT_90	[p2l574t2254r726b2306],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l574t2254r726b2306],

1	Ichnology	NN	O	ichnology	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l751t2253r1047b2322],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l1070t2253r1134b2306],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_91	[p2l1150t2253r1237b2306],
4	Upper	NNP	MISC	Upper	nn	7	SENT_91	[p2l1259t2254r1443b2321],
5	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	nn	7	SENT_91	[p2l1461t2253r1865b2320],
6	Hartselle	NNP	O	Hartselle	nn	7	SENT_91	[p2l1885t2253r2148b2306],
7	Sandstone	NNP	O	Sandstone	prep_of	1	SENT_91	[p2l78t2329r378b2382],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l414t2329r478b2381],
9	Alabama	NNP	LOCATION	Alabama	prep_of	1	SENT_91	[p2l509t2329r790b2389],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l509t2329r790b2389],
11	with	IN	O	with	dep	1	SENT_91	[p2l830t2329r958b2381],
12	notes	NNS	O	note	pobj	11	SENT_91	[p2l994t2339r1145b2381],
13	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l1184t2346r1255b2382],
14	other	JJ	O	other	amod	16	SENT_91	[p2l1291t2329r1442b2381],
15	Carboniferous	NNP	O	Carboniferous	nn	16	SENT_91	[p2l1477t2329r1895b2381],
16	Formations	NNPS	O	Formations	prep_on	12	SENT_91	[p2l1932t2331r2146b2382, p2l76t2405r232b2458],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l1932t2331r2146b2382, p2l76t2405r232b2458],

1	Geological	JJ	O	geological	amod	2	SENT_92	[p2l263t2404r584b2472],
2	Survey	NN	O	survey	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l613t2405r821b2472],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l849t2405r913b2457],
4	Alabama	NNP	LOCATION	Alabama	nn	5	SENT_92	[p2l936t2405r1201b2458],
5	Bulletin	NNP	O	Bulletin	prep_of	2	SENT_92	[p2l1228t2405r1479b2465],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l1228t2405r1479b2465],
7	158:1	CD	NUMBER	158:1	num	8	SENT_92	[p2l1516t2405r1836b2458],
8	?	NN	O	?	appos	2	SENT_92	[p2l1516t2405r1836b2458],
9	107	CD	NUMBER	107	dep	8	SENT_92	[p2l1516t2405r1836b2458],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l1516t2405r1836b2458],

1	SCHAFER	NNP	LOCATION	SCHAFER	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l10t2483r292b2544],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l10t2483r292b2544],
3	W.	NNP	O	W.	appos	1	SENT_93	[p2l332t2484r406b2536],
4	1972	CD	DATE	1972	num	3	SENT_93	[p2l455t2483r608b2536],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l455t2483r608b2536],

1	Ecology	NNP	O	Ecology	_	0	SENT_94	[p2l650t2483r891b2551],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_94	[p2l932t2483r1036b2536],
3	Palaeoecology	NNP	O	Palaeoecology	conj_and	1	SENT_94	[p2l1075t2483r1501b2552],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_94	[p2l1542t2483r1606b2536],
5	Marine	NNP	O	Marine	nn	6	SENT_94	[p2l1638t2483r1849b2536],
6	Environments	NNS	O	environment	prep_of	1	SENT_94	[p2l1887t2484r2146b2536, p2l77t2570r266b2613],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_94	[p2l1887t2484r2146b2536, p2l77t2570r266b2613],

1	Edited	VBN	O	edit	_	0	SENT_95	[p2l297t2560r487b2613],
2	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_95	[p2l516t2561r585b2627],
3	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	5	SENT_95	[p2l615t2560r681b2613],
4	Y.	NNP	PERSON	Y.	nn	5	SENT_95	[p2l714t2561r770b2613],
5	Craig	NNP	PERSON	Craig	prep_by	1	SENT_95	[p2l801t2560r977b2629],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_95	[p2l801t2560r977b2629],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_96	[p2l1008t2560r1121b2613],
2	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l1150t2560r1456b2628],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l1487t2560r1550b2613],
4	Chicago	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chicago	nn	5	SENT_96	[p2l1574t2560r1818b2628],
5	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Press	prep_of	2	SENT_96	[p2l1846t2562r2015b2621],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l1846t2562r2015b2621],
7	Edinburgh	NNP	LOCATION	Edinburgh	appos	5	SENT_96	[p2l2042t2561r2146b2613, p2l79t2636r320b2705],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l2042t2561r2146b2613, p2l79t2636r320b2705],

1	568	CD	NUMBER	568	num	2	SENT_97	[p2l352t2637r458b2689],
2	p.	NN	O	p.	_	0	SENT_97	[p2l486t2653r537b2705],

1	SEILACHER	NNP	LOCATION	SEILACHER	_	0	SENT_98	[p2l11t2714r350b2774],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p2l11t2714r350b2774],
3	A.	NNP	O	A.	appos	1	SENT_98	[p2l384t2715r451b2766],
4	1955	CD	DATE	1955	num	3	SENT_98	[p2l496t2714r649b2767],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_98	[p2l496t2714r649b2767],

1	Spuren	JJ	O	spuren	amod	3	SENT_99	[p2l686t2714r891b2782],
2	und	NN	O	und	nn	3	SENT_99	[p2l926t2714r1033b2766],
3	Fazies	NNS	O	fazy	nsubj	4	SENT_99	[p2l1068t2714r1251b2767],
4	im	VBP	O	im	_	0	SENT_99	[p2l1288t2714r1363b2766],
5	Unterkambrium	NNP	O	Unterkambrium	dobj	4	SENT_99	[p2l1395t2714r1881b2775],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p2l1395t2714r1881b2775],
7	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	5	SENT_99	[p2l1916t2730r1966b2783],
8	373399	CD	NUMBER	373399	num	7	SENT_99	[p2l2002t2714r2148b2767, p2l78t2791r201b2844],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_99	[p2l2002t2714r2148b2767, p2l78t2791r201b2844],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_100	[p2l241t2793r301b2844],
2	o.	NNP	O	o.	pobj	1	SENT_100	[p2l342t2791r407b2844],
3	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	rcmod	2	SENT_100	[p2l450t2792r516b2844],
4	Schindewolf	NNP	PERSON	Schindewolf	rcmod	3	SENT_100	[p2l560t2791r946b2852],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_100	[p2l560t2791r946b2852],
6	and	CC	O	and	dep	7	SENT_100	[p2l987t2791r1091b2844],
7	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	dep	4	SENT_100	[p2l1129t2793r1195b2844],
8	Seilacher	NNP	PERSON	Seilacher	nn	10	SENT_100	[p2l1240t2791r1513b2844],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_100	[p2l1551t2792r1730b2855],
10	eds	NNS	O	ed	dep	7	SENT_100	[p2l1551t2792r1730b2855],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_100	[p2l1551t2792r1730b2855],
12	)	SYM	O	)	dep	3	SENT_100	[p2l1551t2792r1730b2855],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_101	[p2l1551t2792r1730b2855],
2	Beitrage	NNP	PERSON	Beitrage	nn	6	SENT_101	[p2l1770t2792r2018b2859],
3	zur	NN	PERSON	zur	nn	6	SENT_101	[p2l2056t2808r2149b2844],
4	Kenntnis	NNP	PERSON	Kenntnis	nn	6	SENT_101	[p2l78t2868r339b2921],
5	des	NNP	PERSON	des	nn	6	SENT_101	[p2l375t2868r469b2921],
6	Kambriums	NNP	PERSON	Kambriums	dep	7	SENT_101	[p2l506t2868r848b2921],
7	in	IN	O	in	dep	12	SENT_101	[p2l886t2868r940b2920],
8	der	NNP	O	der	nn	10	SENT_101	[p2l974t2869r1067b2921],
9	Salt	NNP	O	Salt	nn	10	SENT_101	[p2l1101t2868r1213b2921],
10	Range	NNP	O	Range	pobj	7	SENT_101	[p2l1245t2868r1432b2936],
11	(	NNP	O	(	nn	12	SENT_101	[p2l1467t2868r1778b2931],
12	Pakistan	NNP	LOCATION	Pakistan	_	0	SENT_101	[p2l1467t2868r1778b2931],
13	)	IN	O	)	amod	12	SENT_101	[p2l1467t2868r1778b2931],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_101	[p2l1467t2868r1778b2931],

1	Akademiee	NNP	PERSON	Akademiee	nn	3	SENT_102	[p2l1813t2868r2147b2921],
2	der	FW	PERSON	der	nn	3	SENT_102	[p2l77t2943r171b2996],
3	Wissenschaften	NNP	PERSON	Wissenschaften	_	0	SENT_102	[p2l196t2943r654b2996],
4	und	JJ	O	und	amod	8	SENT_102	[p2l682t2943r790b2996],
5	der	NN	O	der	nn	8	SENT_102	[p2l817t2944r911b2995],
6	Literatur	NNP	O	Literatur	nn	8	SENT_102	[p2l937t2944r1194b2996],
7	zu	NNP	O	zu	nn	8	SENT_102	[p2l1219t2960r1286b2995],
8	Mainz	NNP	LOCATION	Mainz	dep	3	SENT_102	[p2l1314t2944r1517b3003],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p2l1314t2944r1517b3003],
10	mathematischnaturwissenschaftliche	NN	O	mathematischnaturwissenschaftliche	nn	11	SENT_102	[p2l1544t2944r2149b2996, p2l77t3021r596b3074],
11	Klasse	NNP	O	Klasse	appos	8	SENT_102	[p2l623t3021r832b3082],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p2l623t3021r832b3082],
13	Abhandlungen	NNP	PERSON	Abhandlungen	appos	8	SENT_102	[p2l860t3021r1309b3089],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p2l860t3021r1309b3089],
15	10	CD	NUMBER	10	appos	8	SENT_102	[p2l1346t3022r1425b3074],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_102	[p2l1346t3022r1425b3074],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_103	[p2l7t3125r169b3149],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_103	[p2l7t3125r169b3149],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_104	[p2l210t3097r363b3150],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_104	[p2l210t3097r363b3150],

1	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	amod	3	SENT_105	[p2l397t3097r680b3150],
2	trace	NN	O	trace	nn	3	SENT_105	[p2l711t3106r852b3150],
3	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_105	[p2l883t3096r1085b3157],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p2l883t3096r1085b3157],
5	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	3	SENT_105	[p2l1116t3112r1167b3164],
6	649-670	CD	NUMBER	649-670	num	5	SENT_105	[p2l1199t3096r1477b3150],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_105	[p2l1199t3096r1477b3150],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1508t3099r1568b3149],
2	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	prep_in	5	SENT_106	[p2l1598t3097r1660b3150],
3	Said	NNP	PERSON	Said	nn	4	SENT_106	[p2l1695t3097r1822b3150],
4	(	NNP	O	(	nsubj	5	SENT_106	[p2l1853t3097r2003b3161],
5	ed	VBD	O	ed	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1853t3097r2003b3161],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1853t3097r2003b3161],
7	)	SYM	O	)	dep	5	SENT_106	[p2l1853t3097r2003b3161],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_107	[p2l1853t3097r2003b3161],
2	The	DT	O	the	_	0	SENT_107	[p2l2034t3098r2146b3150],

1	Geology	NN	O	geology	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l76t3174r328b3243],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l358t3175r421b3227],
3	Egypt	NNP	LOCATION	Egypt	prep_of	1	SENT_108	[p2l443t3176r633b3243],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l443t3176r633b3243],

1	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	nn	2	SENT_109	[p2l663t3176r729b3228],
2	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	_	0	SENT_109	[p2l760t3176r827b3227],
3	Balkema	NNP	PERSON	Balkema	nn	5	SENT_109	[p2l857t3175r1133b3236],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p2l857t3175r1133b3236],
5	Rotterdam	NNP	LOCATION	Rotterdam	dep	2	SENT_109	[p2l1162t3176r1487b3228],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_109	[p2l1162t3176r1487b3228],

1	SUTTNER	NNP	LOCATION	SUTTNER	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l11t3252r292b3313],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l11t3252r292b3313],
3	L.	NNP	O	L.	nn	4	SENT_110	[p2l336t3252r394b3304],
4	J.	NNP	O	J.	appos	1	SENT_110	[p2l440t3253r482b3305],
5	1994	CD	DATE	1994	dep	4	SENT_110	[p2l536t3252r688b3305],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l536t3252r688b3305],

1	Sedimentology	NNP	O	Sedimentology	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l735t3252r1178b3320],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l1223t3253r1326b3305],
3	ichnology	NN	O	ichnology	conj_and	1	SENT_111	[p2l1370t3252r1661b3320],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l1706t3253r1769b3305],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_111	[p2l1807t3253r1894b3306],
6	coarsegrained	JJ	O	coarsegrained	amod	8	SENT_111	[p2l1938t3268r2147b3306, p2l78t3328r297b3395],
7	delta	NN	O	delta	nn	8	SENT_111	[p2l318t3327r460b3380],
8	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_of	3	SENT_111	[p2l479t3328r716b3395],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l741t3329r794b3380],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_111	[p2l815t3327r903b3380],
11	Fountain	NNP	O	Fountain	nn	12	SENT_111	[p2l924t3328r1183b3381],
12	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_in	8	SENT_111	[p2l1204t3329r1510b3381],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_111	[p2l1531t3328r2005b3395],
14	Pennsylvanian	NN	MISC	pennsylvanian	nn	15	SENT_111	[p2l1531t3328r2005b3395],
15	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_111	[p2l1531t3328r2005b3395],
16	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l2024t3344r2151b3381],
17	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	Colorado	nn	18	SENT_111	[p2l77t3405r350b3458],
18	Springs	NNP	LOCATION	Springs	prep_near	15	SENT_111	[p2l376t3405r614b3474],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l376t3405r614b3474],
20	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	Colorado	appos	18	SENT_111	[p2l640t3405r927b3459],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l640t3405r927b3459],

1	WALTER	NNP	PERSON	WALTER	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l10t3559r279b3618],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l10t3559r279b3618],
3	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	4	SENT_113	[p2l310t3560r388b3610],
4	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	appos	1	SENT_113	[p2l419t3558r502b3618],
5	,	,	PERSON	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l419t3558r502b3618],
6	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	7	SENT_113	[p2l532t3559r593b3609],
7	ELPHINSTONE	NNP	PERSON	ELPHINSTONE	appos	4	SENT_113	[p2l625t3559r1040b3618],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l625t3559r1040b3618],
9	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l1071t3572r1192b3611],
10	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	12	SENT_113	[p2l1220t3558r1286b3610],
11	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	12	SENT_113	[p2l1319t3559r1381b3610],
12	HEYS	NNP	PERSON	HEYS	appos	1	SENT_113	[p2l1412t3560r1587b3611],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l1412t3560r1587b3611],

1	1989	CD	DATE	1989	_	0	SENT_114	[p2l1626t3559r1779b3612],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_114	[p2l1626t3559r1779b3612],

1	Proterozoic	JJ	O	proterozoic	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l1811t3560r2148b3612],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l78t3636r181b3688],
3	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	6	SENT_115	[p2l217t3635r373b3702],
4	Cambrian	NNP	MISC	Cambrian	nn	6	SENT_115	[p2l409t3636r698b3689],
5	trace	NN	O	trace	nn	6	SENT_115	[p2l732t3646r874b3689],
6	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	conj_and	1	SENT_115	[p2l908t3636r1093b3689],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l1129t3636r1270b3689],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_115	[p2l1304t3637r1392b3689],
9	Amadeus	NNP	O	Amadeus	nn	12	SENT_115	[p2l1425t3637r1701b3690],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l1737t3637r1840b3689],
11	Georgina	NNP	PERSON	Georgina	nn	12	SENT_115	[p2l1875t3638r2150b3705],
12	Basins	NNP	PERSON	Basins	prep_from	6	SENT_115	[p2l77t3713r288b3773],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l77t3713r288b3773],
14	central	JJ	O	central	appos	1	SENT_115	[p2l317t3713r515b3765],
15	Australia	NNP	LOCATION	Australia	dep	14	SENT_115	[p2l543t3713r826b3766],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l543t3713r826b3766],

1	Alcheringa	NNP	PERSON	Alcheringa	_	0	SENT_116	[p2l855t3713r1197b3781],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_116	[p2l855t3713r1197b3781],
3	13:209	CD	NUMBER	13:209	num	4	SENT_116	[p2l1234t3713r1597b3767],
4	-256	CD	NUMBER	-256	appos	1	SENT_116	[p2l1234t3713r1597b3767],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_116	[p2l1234t3713r1597b3767],

1	WEBBY	NNP	LOCATION	WEBBY	_	0	SENT_117	[p3l10t11r247b71],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_117	[p3l10t11r247b71],
3	B.	NNP	O	B.	nn	4	SENT_117	[p3l282t12r344b62],
4	D.	NNP	O	D.	appos	1	SENT_117	[p3l379t12r445b63],
5	1970	CD	DATE	1970	dep	4	SENT_117	[p3l490t11r642b63],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_117	[p3l490t11r642b63],

1	Late	RB	O	late	advmod	3	SENT_118	[p3l678t12r808b63],
2	Precambrian	JJ	MISC	precambrian	amod	3	SENT_118	[p3l840t11r1211b63],
3	trace	NN	O	trace	_	0	SENT_118	[p3l1244t21r1385b64],
4	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	dep	3	SENT_118	[p3l1418t12r1602b64],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_118	[p3l1636t12r1777b64],
6	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	7	SENT_118	[p3l1808t13r1945b64],
7	South	NNP	LOCATION	South	prep_from	4	SENT_118	[p3l1979t12r2147b64],

1	Wales	NNP	LOCATION	Wales	_	0	SENT_119	[p3l77t86r268b138],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_119	[p3l77t86r268b138],

1	Lethaia	NNP	LOCATION	Lethaia	_	0	SENT_120	[p3l299t86r535b147],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_120	[p3l299t86r535b147],
3	3279-109	CD	NUMBER	3279-109	appos	1	SENT_120	[p3l564t86r860b139],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_120	[p3l564t86r860b139],

1	YAO	NNP	O	YAO	_	0	SENT_121	[p3l10t162r155b222],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p3l10t162r155b222],
3	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	1	SENT_121	[p3l192t162r231b214],
4	1993	CD	DATE	1993	num	3	SENT_121	[p3l276t161r422b215],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_121	[p3l276t161r422b215],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_122	[p3l458t163r510b214],
2	new	JJ	O	new	amod	3	SENT_122	[p3l544t177r660b214],
3	trace	NN	O	trace	_	0	SENT_122	[p3l694t170r829b215],
4	fossil	NN	O	fossil	nn	5	SENT_122	[p3l863t162r1011b215],
5	genus	NNS	O	genus	dep	3	SENT_122	[p3l1046t178r1207b237],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_122	[p3l1244t162r1380b215],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_122	[p3l1412t163r1496b216],
8	Lower	NNP	O	Lower	prep_from	5	SENT_122	[p3l1530t164r1716b216],
9	Cretaceous	JJ	O	cretaceous	dep	3	SENT_122	[p3l1746t163r2056b217],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_122	[p3l2090t164r2153b217],
11	Tibet	NNP	LOCATION	Tibet	prep_of	9	SENT_122	[p3l76t239r234b292],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_122	[p3l76t239r234b292],

1	Professional	JJ	O	professional	amod	2	SENT_123	[p3l259t239r603b293],
2	Papers	NNP	O	Papers	_	0	SENT_123	[p3l624t241r809b308],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_123	[p3l831t240r892b293],
4	Stratigraphy	NNP	O	Stratigraphy	prep_of	2	SENT_123	[p3l908t240r1251b308],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_123	[p3l1272t241r1371b293],
6	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	conj_and	4	SENT_123	[p3l1391t241r1773b309],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_123	[p3l1391t241r1773b309],
8	24	CD	NUMBER	24	num	10	SENT_123	[p3l1794t241r1877b294],
9	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_123	[p3l1794t241r1877b294],
10	180-185	CD	NUMBER	180-185	appos	2	SENT_123	[p3l1890t241r2145b295],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_123	[p3l1890t241r2145b295],

1	ACCEPTED	VBN	O	accept	_	0	SENT_124	[p3l9t376r316b427],
2	10	CD	DATE	10	dobj	1	SENT_124	[p3l352t375r416b426],
3	NOVEMBER	NNP	DATE	NOVEMBER	tmod	1	SENT_124	[p3l443t376r776b427],
4	1997	CD	DATE	1997	num	3	SENT_124	[p3l810t375r946b427],

1	THE	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_125	[p3l162t502r278b545],
2	EARLIEST	JJS	O	earliest	amod	3	SENT_125	[p3l300t502r585b546],
3	GASTROCHAENOLITES	NN	O	gastrochaenolite	_	0	SENT_125	[p3l608t502r1226b547],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	3	SENT_125	[p3l1246t503r1461b556],
5	EARLY	NNP	O	EARLY	nn	10	SENT_125	[p3l1246t503r1461b556],
6	PENNSYLVANIAN	NNP	O	PENNSYLVANIAN	nn	10	SENT_125	[p3l1483t503r1998b555],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_125	[p3l1483t503r1998b555],
8	ARKANSAS	NNP	LOCATION	ARKANSAS	appos	10	SENT_125	[p3l210t569r546b620],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_125	[p3l210t569r546b620],
10	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	dep	3	SENT_125	[p3l570t569r723b622],
11	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	10	SENT_125	[p3l570t569r723b622],
12	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_125	[p3l570t569r723b622],
13	AN	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_125	[p3l748t569r834b612],
14	UPPER	NNP	O	UPPER	nn	17	SENT_125	[p3l856t569r1043b613],
15	PALEOZOIC	NNP	O	PALEOZOIC	nn	17	SENT_125	[p3l1065t570r1394b614],
16	BIVALVE	NNP	O	BIVALVE	nn	17	SENT_125	[p3l1416t570r1674b613],
17	BORING	NNP	O	BORING	dep	3	SENT_125	[p3l1695t571r1951b615],
18	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_125	[p3l1695t571r1951b615],

1	MARK	NNP	PERSON	MARK	nn	3	SENT_126	[p3l669t663r788b692],
2	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	3	SENT_126	[p3l801t664r837b692],
3	WILSON	NNP	PERSON	WILSON	_	0	SENT_126	[p3l853t663r1006b692],
4	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_126	[p3l1020t671r1088b692],
5	TIMOTHY	NNP	PERSON	TIMOTHY	conj_and	3	SENT_126	[p3l1102t663r1283b693],
6	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	7	SENT_126	[p3l1296t664r1319b692],
7	PALMER	NNP	PERSON	PALMER	dep	3	SENT_126	[p3l1335t664r1493b693],

1	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	nn	3	SENT_127	[p3l530t712r697b745],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	amod	3	SENT_127	[p3l709t711r740b737],
3	Geology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geology	_	0	SENT_127	[p3l750t711r878b745],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_127	[p3l750t711r878b745],
5	The	NNP	ORGANIZATION	The	nn	6	SENT_127	[p3l891t712r945b738],
6	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	appos	3	SENT_127	[p3l958t711r1067b745],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_127	[p3l1080t712r1111b738],
8	Wooster	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wooster	prep_of	6	SENT_127	[p3l1121t712r1243b742],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_127	[p3l1121t712r1243b742],
10	Wooster	NNP	LOCATION	Wooster	appos	3	SENT_127	[p3l1256t712r1377b743],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_127	[p3l1256t712r1377b743],
12	Ohio	NNP	LOCATION	Ohio	appos	3	SENT_127	[p3l1391t712r1460b739],
13	44691	CD	NUMBER	44691	num	12	SENT_127	[p3l1472t712r1568b743],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_127	[p3l1472t712r1568b743],
15	and	CC	O	and	advmod	3	SENT_127	[p3l1582t712r1632b739],

1	Institute	NNP	O	Institute	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l213t754r328b780],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l341t754r373b780],
3	Geography	NNP	O	Geography	nn	6	SENT_128	[p3l383t754r539b787],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l552t754r602b780],
5	Earth	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Earth	nn	6	SENT_128	[p3l615t754r690b780],
6	Sciences	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Sciences	prep_of	1	SENT_128	[p3l704t754r834b784],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l704t754r834b784],
8	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	6	SENT_128	[p3l847t754r995b787],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l1008t754r1040b780],
10	Wales	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Wales	nn	12	SENT_128	[p3l1049t754r1142b785],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l1049t754r1142b785],
12	Aberystwyth	NNP	O	Aberystwyth	prep_of	8	SENT_128	[p3l1156t755r1346b788],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l1156t755r1346b788],
14	Ceredigion	NNP	O	Ceredigion	nn	16	SENT_128	[p3l1360t755r1515b788],
15	SY23	NN	O	sy23	nn	16	SENT_128	[p3l1528t755r1606b781],
16	3DB	NN	O	3db	dep	1	SENT_128	[p3l1621t755r1694b785],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_128	[p3l1621t755r1694b785],
18	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	19	SENT_128	[p3l1708t756r1803b782],
19	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	appos	16	SENT_128	[p3l1816t756r1948b789],

1	ABsTRACT	NNP	O	ABsTRACT	_	0	SENT_129	[p3l108t879r407b913],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_129	[p3l108t879r407b913],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_130	[p3l108t879r407b913],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_130	[p3l108t879r407b913],

1	Borings	NNS	O	boring	nsubjpass	8	SENT_131	[p3l108t879r407b913],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l418t879r450b905],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_131	[p3l457t879r500b905],
4	ichnogenus	NN	O	ichnogenus	nn	5	SENT_131	[p3l510t879r669b913],
5	Gastrochaenolites	NNS	MISC	gastrochaenolite	prep_of	1	SENT_131	[p3l681t880r938b906],
6	have	VBP	O	have	aux	8	SENT_131	[p3l948t879r1014b906],
7	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_131	[p3l1024t880r1090b906],
8	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l1101t880r1182b906],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l1193t880r1218b906],
10	limestone	NN	O	limestone	nn	11	SENT_131	[p3l1229t880r1365b907],
11	cobbles	NNS	O	cobble	prep_in	8	SENT_131	[p3l1375t880r1481b907],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l1492t880r1523b907],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_131	[p3l1530t881r1572b907],
14	Morrowan	NNP	O	Morrowan	nn	17	SENT_131	[p3l1581t881r1730b908],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_131	[p3l1740t881r1827b915],
16	Early	JJ	O	early	amod	17	SENT_131	[p3l1740t881r1827b915],
17	Pennsylvanian	NN	O	pennsylvanian	prep_of	11	SENT_131	[p3l1836t881r2052b915],
18	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	21	SENT_131	[p3l1836t881r2052b915],
19	Cane	NNP	O	Cane	nn	21	SENT_131	[p3l108t916r180b942],
20	Hill	NNP	O	Hill	nn	21	SENT_131	[p3l191t916r245b942],
21	Member	NNP	O	Member	dobj	8	SENT_131	[p3l256t916r376b943],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l386t916r418b942],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_131	[p3l426t916r468b943],
24	Hale	NNP	O	Hale	nn	25	SENT_131	[p3l479t916r544b943],
25	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_of	21	SENT_131	[p3l555t916r702b943],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l713t916r739b942],
27	northwestem	NN	O	northwestem	nn	28	SENT_131	[p3l750t917r933b943],
28	Arkansas	NNP	LOCATION	Arkansas	prep_in	25	SENT_131	[p3l945t917r1082b944],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_131	[p3l945t917r1082b944],

1	They	PRP	O	they	nsubj	3	SENT_132	[p3l1094t917r1166b951],
2	were	VBD	O	be	cop	3	SENT_132	[p3l1177t925r1244b944],
3	likely	JJ	O	likely	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l1255t917r1334b951],
4	excavated	VBN	O	excavate	dep	3	SENT_132	[p3l1345t918r1485b944],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l1495t918r1530b951],
6	lithophagid	NN	O	lithophagid	nn	7	SENT_132	[p3l1541t918r1700b952],
7	bivalves	NNS	O	bivalve	prep_by	4	SENT_132	[p3l1710t918r1835b949],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l1710t918r1835b949],
9	thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	10	SENT_132	[p3l1846t919r1903b945],
10	extending	VBG	O	extend	ccomp	3	SENT_132	[p3l1914t919r2052b953],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_132	[p3l108t953r151b979],
12	earliest	JJS	O	earliest	amod	13	SENT_132	[p3l165t953r266b979],
13	record	NN	O	record	dobj	10	SENT_132	[p3l279t953r369b979],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l383t953r415b979],
15	obligate	JJ	O	obligate	amod	17	SENT_132	[p3l425t953r538b987],
16	bivalve	NN	O	bivalve	nn	17	SENT_132	[p3l552t953r655b980],
17	boring	NN	O	boring	prep_of	13	SENT_132	[p3l668t953r760b987],
18	back	RB	O	back	advmod	10	SENT_132	[p3l774t954r840b980],
19	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l854t953r922b980],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_132	[p3l935t954r977b980],
21	Triassic	NNP	MISC	Triassic	prep_from	10	SENT_132	[p3l990t954r1099b980],
22	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l1114t954r1167b980],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_132	[p3l1181t954r1223b981],
24	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	25	SENT_132	[p3l1237t962r1317b988],
25	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	prep_into	10	SENT_132	[p3l1330t955r1473b981],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_132	[p3l1330t955r1473b981],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	2	SENT_133	[p3l1488t955r1572b981],
2	borings	NNS	O	boring	nsubjpass	5	SENT_133	[p3l1585t955r1689b989],
3	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_133	[p3l1704t963r1746b982],
4	herein	RB	O	herein	advmod	5	SENT_133	[p3l1759t955r1847b982],
5	referred	VBN	O	refer	_	0	SENT_133	[p3l1860t956r1971b982],
6	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_133	[p3l1984t961r2011b983],
7	as	IN	O	as	amod	11	SENT_133	[p3l2024t964r2051b983],
8	G.	NNP	O	G.	nn	11	SENT_133	[p3l109t991r139b1017],
9	anauchen	NN	O	anauchen	nn	11	SENT_133	[p3l151t991r288b1017],
10	n.	NN	O	n.	nn	11	SENT_133	[p3l299t999r323b1016],
11	ichnosp	NN	O	ichnosp	prep_to	5	SENT_133	[p3l335t991r451b1024],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_133	[p3l335t991r451b1024],

1	Lithophagid	JJ	O	lithophagid	amod	2	SENT_134	[p3l463t991r635b1024],
2	borings	NNS	O	boring	nsubj	5	SENT_134	[p3l645t991r749b1024],
3	may	MD	O	may	aux	5	SENT_134	[p3l760t999r820b1024],
4	be	VB	O	be	cop	5	SENT_134	[p3l830t991r863b1017],
5	rare	JJ	O	rare	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l872t999r927b1017],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l937t991r963b1017],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_134	[p3l974t992r1016b1017],
8	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	9	SENT_134	[p3l1025t999r1106b1025],
9	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	prep_in	5	SENT_134	[p3l1115t992r1251b1018],
10	because	IN	O	because	mark	11	SENT_134	[p3l1261t992r1372b1018],
11	of	IN	O	of	advcl	5	SENT_134	[p3l1382t992r1414b1018],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_134	[p3l1421t993r1463b1018],
13	absence	NN	O	absence	pobj	11	SENT_134	[p3l1472t993r1583b1019],
14	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l1592t1001r1622b1019],
15	scarcity	NN	O	scarcity	pobj	11	SENT_134	[p3l1631t994r1740b1026],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l1749t993r1781b1019],
17	suitable	JJ	O	suitable	amod	18	SENT_134	[p3l1788t994r1896b1020],
18	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	prep_of	13	SENT_134	[p3l1906t994r2052b1024],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l1906t994r2052b1024],
20	such	JJ	O	such	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l109t1027r172b1053],
21	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l187t1035r215b1053],
22	scleractinian	JJ	O	scleractinian	amod	23	SENT_134	[p3l231t1027r409b1054],
23	corals	NNS	O	coral	prep_such_as	13	SENT_134	[p3l423t1027r506b1054],
24	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l522t1035r552b1054],
25	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	26	SENT_134	[p3l565t1027r702b1054],
26	hardgrounds	NNS	O	hardground	prep_such_as	13	SENT_134	[p3l716t1027r899b1061],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_134	[p3l716t1027r899b1061],

1	Additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	5	SENT_135	[p3l916t1028r1065b1054],
2	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	5	SENT_135	[p3l1081t1036r1161b1062],
3	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	amod	5	SENT_135	[p3l1175t1028r1310b1055],
4	bivalve	NN	O	bivalve	nn	5	SENT_135	[p3l1325t1029r1428b1055],
5	borings	NNS	O	boring	nsubjpass	9	SENT_135	[p3l1443t1029r1547b1063],
6	will	MD	O	will	aux	9	SENT_135	[p3l1563t1029r1617b1055],
7	likely	RB	O	likely	advmod	9	SENT_135	[p3l1632t1029r1711b1063],
8	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_135	[p3l1725t1030r1758b1056],
9	discovered	VBN	O	discover	_	0	SENT_135	[p3l1772t1030r1925b1057],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_135	[p3l1940t1030r1966b1056],
11	other	JJ	O	other	amod	15	SENT_135	[p3l1980t1031r2053b1057],
12	carbonate-rich	JJ	O	carbonate-rich	amod	15	SENT_135	[p3l108t1066r312b1092],
13	rocky	JJ	O	rocky	amod	15	SENT_135	[p3l324t1066r404b1099],
14	shore	NN	O	shore	nn	15	SENT_135	[p3l418t1066r493b1092],
15	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_in	9	SENT_135	[p3l505t1066r628b1099],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_135	[p3l505t1066r628b1099],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_136	[p3l414t1211r651b1233],

1	GASTROCHAENOLITES	NNP	LOCATION	GASTROCHAENOLITES	nsubj	8	SENT_137	[p3l12t1261r362b1331],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l12t1261r362b1331],
3	1842	CD	DATE	1842	appos	1	SENT_137	[p3l382t1260r466b1293],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l382t1260r466b1293],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	8	SENT_137	[p3l480t1260r505b1288],
6	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_137	[p3l517t1269r535b1288],
7	clavate	NN	O	clavate	nn	8	SENT_137	[p3l546t1260r659b1289],
8	boring	NN	O	boring	dep	18	SENT_137	[p3l671t1260r775b1297],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l787t1261r818b1289],
10	rock	NN	O	rock	nn	13	SENT_137	[p3l829t1261r901b1289],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l912t1261r969b1289],
12	shell	NN	O	shell	conj_and	10	SENT_137	[p3l981t1261r1055b1289],
13	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	prep_in	8	SENT_137	[p3l102t1301r260b1330],
14	attributed	VBN	O	attribute	partmod	13	SENT_137	[p3l287t1301r441b1330],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l467t1306r498b1330],
16	endolithic	JJ	O	endolithic	amod	17	SENT_137	[p3l524t1301r684b1330],
17	bivalves	NNS	O	bivalve	prep_to	14	SENT_137	[p3l711t1301r844b1330],
18	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l871t1301r972b1338],
19	Kelly	NNP	PERSON	Kelly	nsubj	18	SENT_137	[p3l871t1301r972b1338],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l998t1302r1056b1331],
21	Bromley	NNP	PERSON	Bromley	conj_and	19	SENT_137	[p3l7t1343r155b1379],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l7t1343r155b1379],
23	1984	CD	DATE	1984	num	24	SENT_137	[p3l176t1343r273b1377],
24	)	NN	O	)	appos	19	SENT_137	[p3l176t1343r273b1377],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_137	[p3l176t1343r273b1377],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_138	[p3l290t1343r361b1371],
2	ichnogenus	NN	O	ichnogenus	nsubjpass	5	SENT_138	[p3l377t1343r559b1380],
3	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_138	[p3l575t1352r636b1371],
4	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	5	SENT_138	[p3l651t1343r821b1380],
5	thought	VBN	O	think	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l836t1344r959b1380],
6	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_138	[p3l973t1348r1003b1372],
7	be	VB	O	be	cop	8	SENT_138	[p3l1018t1344r1055b1372],
8	Mesozoic	JJ	MISC	mesozoic	ccomp	5	SENT_138	[p3l7t1384r163b1412],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l178t1384r236b1413],
10	Cenozoic	JJ	MISC	cenozoic	ccomp	5	SENT_138	[p3l251t1384r402b1413],
11	only	RB	O	only	advmod	8	SENT_138	[p3l417t1384r496b1421],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l417t1384r496b1421],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l513t1385r570b1413],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_138	[p3l584t1389r615b1413],
15	be	VB	O	be	cop	16	SENT_138	[p3l629t1385r667b1413],
16	one	CD	NUMBER	one	ccomp	5	SENT_138	[p3l682t1393r739b1413],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l754t1385r789b1413],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_138	[p3l801t1385r850b1413],
19	classic	JJ	O	classic	amod	22	SENT_138	[p3l864t1385r970b1413],
20	hard	JJ	O	hard	amod	22	SENT_138	[p3l984t1385r1056b1414],
21	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	22	SENT_138	[p3l8t1425r150b1453],
22	manifestations	NNS	O	manifestation	prep_of	16	SENT_138	[p3l170t1425r405b1453],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l426t1425r461b1453],
24	invertebrate	JJ	O	invertebrate	amod	25	SENT_138	[p3l479t1425r671b1454],
25	infaunalization	NN	O	infaunalization	prep_of	22	SENT_138	[p3l691t1425r932b1454],
26	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l951t1426r1055b1462],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_138	[p3l7t1466r55b1494],
28	Mesozoic	JJ	O	mesozoic	amod	32	SENT_138	[p3l71t1466r227b1494],
29	Marine	NNP	O	Marine	nn	32	SENT_138	[p3l244t1466r360b1494],
30	Revolution	NNP	O	Revolution	nn	32	SENT_138	[p3l376t1466r555b1495],
31	(	NNP	O	(	nn	32	SENT_138	[p3l572t1466r704b1501],
32	Palmer	NNP	PERSON	Palmer	prep_during	16	SENT_138	[p3l572t1466r704b1501],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l572t1466r704b1501],
34	1982	CD	DATE	1982	num	35	SENT_138	[p3l725t1466r823b1501],
35	)	NN	O	)	appos	32	SENT_138	[p3l725t1466r823b1501],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_138	[p3l725t1466r823b1501],

1	Webb	NNP	PERSON	Webb	nsubj	18	SENT_139	[p3l840t1467r933b1495],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	1	SENT_139	[p3l949t1467r1054b1501],
3	1994	CD	DATE	1994	num	4	SENT_139	[p3l949t1467r1054b1501],
4	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	5	SENT_139	[p3l949t1467r1054b1501],
5	?gured	VBD	O	?gured	rcmod	1	SENT_139	[p3l7t1508r121b1545],
6	typical	JJ	O	typical	amod	7	SENT_139	[p3l137t1508r245b1545],
7	Gastrochaenolites	NNS	MISC	gastrochaenolite	nsubj	8	SENT_139	[p3l263t1508r557b1537],
8	excavated	VBN	O	excavate	xcomp	5	SENT_139	[p3l573t1509r734b1538],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l750t1509r780b1537],
10	limestone	NN	O	limestone	nn	11	SENT_139	[p3l796t1509r952b1538],
11	clasts	NNS	O	clast	prep_in	8	SENT_139	[p3l967t1509r1055b1538],
12	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1106t1205r1208b1234],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_139	[p3l1222t1214r1240b1235],
14	transgressive	JJ	O	transgressive	amod	17	SENT_139	[p3l1253t1205r1462b1243],
15	rocky	JJ	O	rocky	amod	17	SENT_139	[p3l1475t1206r1566b1243],
16	shore	NN	O	shore	nn	17	SENT_139	[p3l1581t1206r1666b1236],
17	deposit	NN	O	deposit	prep_within	11	SENT_139	[p3l1680t1207r1796b1244],
18	(	VBD	O	(	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1810t1207r1871b1243],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_139	[p3l1810t1207r1871b1243],
20	Cane	NNP	O	Cane	nn	22	SENT_139	[p3l1884t1208r1966b1237],
21	Hill	NNP	O	Hill	nn	22	SENT_139	[p3l1980t1208r2041b1237],
22	Member	NNP	O	Member	dobj	18	SENT_139	[p3l2053t1208r2151b1238, p3l1105t1251r1157b1280],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1173t1251r1209b1279],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_139	[p3l1222t1251r1270b1280],
25	Hale	NNP	O	Hale	nn	27	SENT_139	[p3l1287t1251r1362b1280],
26	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	27	SENT_139	[p3l1378t1252r1558b1286],
27	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	22	SENT_139	[p3l1378t1252r1558b1286],
28	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1576t1252r1606b1281],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_139	[p3l1622t1252r1671b1281],
30	Lower	NNP	O	Lower	nn	34	SENT_139	[p3l1687t1253r1792b1281],
31	Pennsylvanian	NNP	O	Pennsylvanian	nn	34	SENT_139	[p3l1808t1253r2042b1289],
32	(	NNP	O	(	nn	34	SENT_139	[p3l2059t1254r2151b1288, p3l1106t1295r1218b1330],
33	Morrowan	NNP	O	Morrowan	nn	34	SENT_139	[p3l2059t1254r2151b1288, p3l1106t1295r1218b1330],
34	)	NN	O	)	prep_in	18	SENT_139	[p3l2059t1254r2151b1288, p3l1106t1295r1218b1330],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1236t1295r1271b1324],
36	northwestern	JJ	O	northwestern	amod	37	SENT_139	[p3l1284t1296r1494b1324],
37	Arkansas	NNP	LOCATION	Arkansas	prep_of	34	SENT_139	[p3l1510t1296r1668b1330],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1510t1296r1668b1330],
39	USA	NNP	LOCATION	USA	appos	37	SENT_139	[p3l1685t1296r1773b1325],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_139	[p3l1685t1296r1773b1325],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	3	SENT_140	[p3l1791t1297r1887b1325],
2	Paleozoic	JJ	O	paleozoic	amod	3	SENT_140	[p3l1903t1297r2058b1326],
3	Gastrochaenolites	NNS	O	gastrochaenolite	nsubj	5	SENT_140	[p3l2075t1298r2150b1327, p3l1106t1339r1335b1368],
4	are	VBP	O	be	aux	5	SENT_140	[p3l1353t1348r1401b1368],
5	about	IN	DURATION	about	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1419t1340r1508b1368],
6	100	CD	DURATION	100	number	7	SENT_140	[p3l1528t1340r1584b1368],
7	million	CD	DURATION	million	num	8	SENT_140	[p3l1602t1340r1717b1369],
8	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	tmod	9	SENT_140	[p3l1735t1349r1818b1377],
9	older	JJR	O	older	dep	5	SENT_140	[p3l1837t1341r1919b1369],
10	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1936t1341r2004b1369],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_140	[p3l2022t1342r2070b1370],
12	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	13	SENT_140	[p3l2087t1350r2151b1378, p3l1106t1383r1224b1419],
13	oldest	JJS	O	oldest	amod	14	SENT_140	[p3l1240t1383r1336b1411],
14	record	NN	O	record	prep_than	9	SENT_140	[p3l1351t1383r1453b1412],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1469t1383r1505b1411],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_140	[p3l1518t1383r1567b1412],
17	ichnogenus	NN	O	ichnogenus	prep_of	14	SENT_140	[p3l1583t1383r1774b1420],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1583t1383r1774b1420],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1792t1384r1849b1413],
20	thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	5	SENT_140	[p3l1865t1384r1931b1413],
21	considerably	RB	O	considerably	advmod	22	SENT_140	[p3l1947t1385r2152b1422],
22	predate	VB	O	predate	dep	5	SENT_140	[p3l1105t1426r1223b1462],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_140	[p3l1242t1426r1290b1454],
24	initial	JJ	O	initial	amod	25	SENT_140	[p3l1308t1426r1401b1455],
25	events	NNS	O	event	dobj	22	SENT_140	[p3l1419t1431r1521b1455],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1539t1427r1575b1455],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_140	[p3l1590t1427r1638b1455],
28	Mesozoic	JJ	ORGANIZATION	mesozoic	amod	30	SENT_140	[p3l1657t1428r1812b1456],
29	Marine	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Marine	nn	30	SENT_140	[p3l1830t1428r1946b1456],
30	Revolution	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Revolution	prep_of	25	SENT_140	[p3l1964t1428r2151b1462],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1964t1428r2151b1462],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1106t1468r1163b1496],
33	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	35	SENT_140	[p3l1178t1468r1247b1504],
34	also	RB	O	also	advmod	35	SENT_140	[p3l1263t1468r1326b1496],
35	represent	VBP	O	represent	conj_and	5	SENT_140	[p3l1342t1473r1489b1505],
36	a	DT	O	a	det	38	SENT_140	[p3l1504t1477r1522b1496],
37	new	JJ	O	new	amod	38	SENT_140	[p3l1536t1477r1602b1497],
38	ichnospecies	NNS	O	ichnospecy	dobj	35	SENT_140	[p3l1619t1469r1832b1505],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_140	[p3l1619t1469r1832b1505],

1	No	DT	O	no	det	4	SENT_141	[p3l1849t1470r1897b1498],
2	identi?able	JJ	O	identi?able	amod	4	SENT_141	[p3l1913t1470r2093b1499],
3	bivalve	NN	O	bivalve	nn	4	SENT_141	[p3l2107t1471r2151b1499, p3l1106t1510r1192b1539],
4	shells	NNS	O	shell	nsubjpass	6	SENT_141	[p3l1211t1510r1300b1539],
5	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_141	[p3l1319t1519r1367b1539],
6	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_141	[p3l1385t1510r1478b1540],
7	associated	VBN	O	associate	dep	6	SENT_141	[p3l1496t1511r1661b1540],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_141	[p3l1679t1511r1749b1540],
9	these	DT	O	these	det	10	SENT_141	[p3l1767t1512r1849b1541],
10	borings	NNS	O	boring	prep_with	7	SENT_141	[p3l1867t1512r1996b1549],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_141	[p3l1867t1512r1996b1549],
12	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_141	[p3l2015t1513r2066b1542],
13	they	PRP	O	they	conj_but	6	SENT_141	[p3l2083t1513r2151b1550],

1	JOURNAL	NN	O	journal	_	0	SENT_143	[p3l952t1770r1125b1799],
2	OF	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_143	[p3l1139t1770r1193b1799],
3	PALEONTOLOGY	NNP	O	PALEONTOLOGY	nn	5	SENT_143	[p3l1204t1770r1511b1802],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_143	[p3l1204t1770r1511b1802],
5	V.	NNP	O	V.	prep_of	1	SENT_143	[p3l1530t1771r1558b1798],
6	72	CD	NUMBER	72	num	5	SENT_143	[p3l1578t1770r1621b1802],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_143	[p3l1578t1770r1621b1802],
8	No.	NN	O	no.	appos	5	SENT_143	[p3l1637t1770r1699b1799],
9	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	8	SENT_143	[p3l1716t1770r1742b1802],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_143	[p3l1716t1770r1742b1802],
11	I998	NN	O	i998	dep	1	SENT_143	[p3l1762t1770r1839b1798],

1	FIGURE	NN	O	figure	_	0	SENT_144	[p4l10t28r225b80],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_144	[p4l254t27r729b94],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_144	[p4l254t27r729b94],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_145	[p4l254t27r729b94],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_145	[p4l254t27r729b94],

1	Longitudinal	JJ	O	longitudinal	amod	2	SENT_146	[p4l254t27r729b94],
2	cross-section	NN	O	cross-section	_	0	SENT_146	[p4l755t28r1130b80],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_146	[p4l1155t26r1219b80],
4	Gastrochaenolites	NNP	O	Gastrochaenolites	prep_of	2	SENT_146	[p4l1239t27r1763b80],
5	anauchen	NN	O	anauchen	nn	7	SENT_146	[p4l1786t27r2065b79],
6	n.	NN	O	n.	nn	7	SENT_146	[p4l2090t42r2139b78],
7	ichnosp	NN	O	ichnosp	dep	4	SENT_146	[p4l78t103r316b168],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_146	[p4l78t103r316b168],

1	holotype	NN	O	holotype	_	0	SENT_147	[p4l344t103r612b169],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_147	[p4l344t103r612b169],
3	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_147	[p4l640t118r672b155],
4	cylindrical	JJ	O	cylindrical	amod	5	SENT_147	[p4l695t103r1002b169],
5	Trypanites	NNPS	O	Trypanites	nsubj	6	SENT_147	[p4l1030t103r1334b168],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	dep	1	SENT_147	[p4l1359t103r1404b155],
7	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_147	[p4l1430t111r1485b155],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_147	[p4l1509t102r1595b154],
9	left	VBN	O	leave	prep_to	6	SENT_147	[p4l1622t101r1732b162],
10	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_147	[p4l1622t101r1732b162],
11	OU	NNP	ORGANIZATION	OU	dep	9	SENT_147	[p4l1759t101r1862b155],
12	10731-1	CD	NUMBER	10731-1	num	11	SENT_147	[p4l1892t102r2140b161],
13	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_147	[p4l1892t102r2140b161],
14	X4	NN	O	x4	dep	11	SENT_147	[p4l85t178r241b231],
15	.0	CD	NUMBER	.0	num	14	SENT_147	[p4l85t178r241b231],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_147	[p4l85t178r241b231],

1	are	VBP	O	be	cop	3	SENT_148	[p4l10t418r109b459],
2	ichnogenerically	RB	O	ichnogenerically	advmod	3	SENT_148	[p4l145t399r691b475],
3	indistinguishable	JJ	O	indistinguishable	_	0	SENT_148	[p4l729t398r1289b476],
4	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_148	[p4l1324t399r1483b459],
5	later	JJ	O	later	amod	6	SENT_148	[p4l1516t401r1663b459],
6	Gastrochaenolites	NNS	O	gastrochaenolite	prep_from	3	SENT_148	[p4l1696t399r2141b459, p4l9t484r200b550],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_148	[p4l1696t399r2141b459, p4l9t484r200b550],
8	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	11	SENT_148	[p4l243t483r444b541],
9	were	VBD	O	be	cop	11	SENT_148	[p4l479t501r637b542],
10	clearly	RB	O	clearly	advmod	11	SENT_148	[p4l672t485r893b558],
11	bivalve-excavated	JJ	O	bivalve-excavated	rcmod	6	SENT_148	[p4l930t484r1542b542],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_148	[p4l930t484r1542b542],

1	Lithophagids	NNS	O	lithophagid	nsubj	8	SENT_149	[p4l1580t482r2010b558],
2	are	VBP	O	be	cop	8	SENT_149	[p4l2045t500r2143b541],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_149	[p4l11t567r109b625],
4	only	JJ	O	only	amod	8	SENT_149	[p4l132t567r275b641],
5	extant	JJ	O	extant	amod	8	SENT_149	[p4l298t576r501b625],
6	boring	JJ	O	boring	amod	8	SENT_149	[p4l519t566r734b641],
7	bivalve	NN	O	bivalve	nn	8	SENT_149	[p4l755t566r997b625],
8	clade	NN	O	clade	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l1018t567r1190b625],
9	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l1212t566r1356b625],
10	known	JJ	O	known	amod	13	SENT_149	[p4l1377t567r1601b625],
11	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	13	SENT_149	[p4l1620t584r1809b641],
12	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	amod	13	SENT_149	[p4l1827t566r2143b625],
13	members	NNS	O	member	prep_with	8	SENT_149	[p4l10t650r329b716],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l10t650r329b716],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l376t650r493b709],
16	thus	RB	O	thus	advmod	20	SENT_149	[p4l538t649r671b708],
17	these	DT	O	these	det	19	SENT_149	[p4l716t649r883b708],
18	Pennsylvanian	NN	MISC	pennsylvanian	nn	19	SENT_149	[p4l926t648r1404b723],
19	borings	NNS	O	boring	nsubj	20	SENT_149	[p4l1446t648r1691b723],
20	suggest	VBP	O	suggest	conj_and	8	SENT_149	[p4l1737t658r1982b723],
21	that	IN	O	that	complm	30	SENT_149	[p4l2023t649r2146b707],
22	some	DT	O	some	det	25	SENT_149	[p4l11t750r183b791],
23	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	amod	25	SENT_149	[p4l211t732r530b791],
24	lithophagid	NN	O	lithophagid	nn	25	SENT_149	[p4l560t732r933b807],
25	bivalves	NNS	O	bivalve	nsubj	30	SENT_149	[p4l960t733r1231b791],
26	may	MD	O	may	aux	30	SENT_149	[p4l1260t750r1399b807],
27	have	VB	O	have	aux	30	SENT_149	[p4l1428t733r1582b791],
28	been	VBN	O	be	cop	30	SENT_149	[p4l1609t733r1764b791],
29	actual	JJ	O	actual	amod	30	SENT_149	[p4l1791t733r1985b791],
30	borers	NNS	O	borer	ccomp	20	SENT_149	[p4l2010t733r2142b791, p4l10t833r104b874],
31	rather	RB	O	rather	advmod	30	SENT_149	[p4l137t816r331b874],
32	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l362t816r503b873],
33	nestlers	NNS	O	nestler	prep_than	30	SENT_149	[p4l535t816r784b874],
34	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l817t832r886b873],
35	soft	JJ	O	soft	amod	37	SENT_149	[p4l918t815r1040b873],
36	substrate	NN	O	substrate	nn	37	SENT_149	[p4l1073t817r1361b874],
37	dwellers	NNS	O	dweller	conj_or	33	SENT_149	[p4l1392t816r1669b874],
38	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l1702t832r1767b873],
39	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	42	SENT_149	[p4l1798t815r2143b889],
40	suggested	VBN	O	suggest	amod	42	SENT_149	[p4l11t899r335b973],
41	(	NNP	O	(	nn	42	SENT_149	[p4l364t898r642b968],
42	Wilson	NNP	PERSON	Wilson	prep_as	30	SENT_149	[p4l364t898r642b968],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l364t898r642b968],
44	1965	CD	DATE	1965	appos	42	SENT_149	[p4l681t899r856b966],
45	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l681t899r856b966],
46	Kelly	NNP	PERSON	Kelly	dep	42	SENT_149	[p4l888t899r1066b972],
47	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l1097t899r1213b957],
48	Bromley	NNP	PERSON	Bromley	conj_and	46	SENT_149	[p4l1240t899r1542b972],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l1240t899r1542b972],
50	1984	CD	DATE	1984	num	51	SENT_149	[p4l1580t899r1779b968],
51	)	NN	O	)	appos	46	SENT_149	[p4l1580t899r1779b968],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_149	[p4l1580t899r1779b968],

1	Hence	RB	O	hence	advmod	10	SENT_150	[p4l1810t899r2017b957],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_150	[p4l2046t898r2144b957],
3	obligate	JJ	O	obligate	amod	6	SENT_150	[p4l11t983r274b1056],
4	bivalve	NN	O	bivalve	nn	6	SENT_150	[p4l305t983r547b1041],
5	macroboring	NN	O	macroboring	nn	6	SENT_150	[p4l578t982r997b1056],
6	habit	NN	O	habit	nsubjpass	10	SENT_150	[p4l1028t981r1194b1040],
7	may	MD	O	may	aux	10	SENT_150	[p4l1221t999r1359b1056],
8	have	VB	O	have	aux	10	SENT_150	[p4l1391t982r1546b1040],
9	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_150	[p4l1576t982r1732b1040],
10	established	VBN	O	establish	_	0	SENT_150	[p4l1762t981r2142b1049],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_150	[p4l1762t981r2142b1049],
12	albeit	IN	O	albeit	dep	16	SENT_150	[p4l11t1064r194b1123],
13	locally	RB	O	locally	advmod	16	SENT_150	[p4l221t1065r460b1139],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_150	[p4l221t1065r460b1139],
15	long	RB	O	long	advmod	16	SENT_150	[p4l491t1066r636b1139],
16	before	IN	O	before	dep	10	SENT_150	[p4l665t1065r874b1123],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_150	[p4l903t1065r1002b1123],
18	Mesozoic	JJ	O	mesozoic	amod	20	SENT_150	[p4l1031t1064r1348b1123],
19	Marine	NNP	O	Marine	nn	20	SENT_150	[p4l1377t1064r1613b1123],
20	Revolution	NNP	O	Revolution	pobj	16	SENT_150	[p4l1642t1065r2021b1124],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_150	[p4l1642t1065r2021b1124],

1	SYSTEMATIC	JJ	O	systematic	amod	2	SENT_151	[p4l608t1217r1009b1261],
2	PALEONTOLOGY	NN	O	paleontology	_	0	SENT_151	[p4l1038t1217r1552b1261],

1	Specimens	NNS	O	specimen	nsubj	2	SENT_152	[p4l94t1311r447b1386],
2	described	VBN	O	describe	dep	5	SENT_152	[p4l479t1310r795b1370],
3	here	RB	O	here	advmod	2	SENT_152	[p4l825t1311r966b1369],
4	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_152	[p4l998t1327r1096b1369],
5	deposited	VBN	O	deposit	_	0	SENT_152	[p4l1127t1310r1441b1386],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_152	[p4l1471t1310r1535b1368],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_152	[p4l1566t1310r1664b1369],
8	collections	NNS	O	collection	prep_in	5	SENT_152	[p4l1694t1309r2047b1368],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_152	[p4l2078t1310r2150b1368],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_152	[p4l10t1395r109b1453],
11	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	nn	12	SENT_152	[p4l139t1394r482b1452],
12	Museum	NNP	LOCATION	Museum	prep_of	8	SENT_152	[p4l509t1395r799b1453],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_152	[p4l826t1394r900b1452],
14	Natural	NNP	O	Natural	nn	15	SENT_152	[p4l922t1394r1167b1452],
15	History	NN	O	history	prep_of	12	SENT_152	[p4l1196t1393r1443b1467],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_152	[p4l1474t1394r1794b1464],
17	OMNH	NN	O	omnh	nn	18	SENT_152	[p4l1474t1394r1794b1464],
18	)	NN	O	)	nsubjpass	5	SENT_152	[p4l1474t1394r1794b1464],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_152	[p4l1474t1394r1794b1464],

1	Ichnogenus	NNP	O	Ichnogenus	nn	3	SENT_153	[p4l242t1532r620b1605],
2	GASTROCHAENOLITES	NNP	O	GASTROCHAENOLITES	nn	3	SENT_153	[p4l650t1531r1361b1590],
3	Leymerie	NNP	O	Leymerie	_	0	SENT_153	[p4l1388t1530r1720b1604],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_153	[p4l1388t1530r1720b1604],
5	1842	CD	DATE	1842	appos	3	SENT_153	[p4l1758t1531r1912b1589],

1	Gastrochaenolites	NNP	LOCATION	Gastrochaenolites	nn	2	SENT_154	[p4l12t1633r550b1685],
2	LEYMERIE	NNP	LOCATION	LEYMERIE	nsubj	12	SENT_154	[p4l582t1634r900b1693],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l582t1634r900b1693],
4	1842	CD	DATE	1842	appos	2	SENT_154	[p4l941t1633r1097b1693],
5	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l941t1633r1097b1693],
6	KELLY	NNP	PERSON	KELLY	dep	2	SENT_154	[p4l1132t1634r1329b1685],
7	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l1361t1645r1483b1684],
8	BROMLEY	NNP	LOCATION	BROMLEY	dep	2	SENT_154	[p4l1515t1634r1821b1692],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l1515t1634r1821b1692],
10	1984	CD	DATE	1984	appos	6	SENT_154	[p4l1863t1632r2018b1693],
11	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l1863t1632r2018b1693],
12	see	VB	O	see	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l2053t1648r2144b1685],
13	p.	NN	O	p.	dobj	12	SENT_154	[p4l78t1723r127b1774],
14	797	CD	NUMBER	797	num	13	SENT_154	[p4l159t1708r266b1760],
15	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l295t1708r382b1760],
16	complete	JJ	O	complete	amod	17	SENT_154	[p4l406t1709r676b1774],
17	synonymy	NN	O	synonymy	prep_for	13	SENT_154	[p4l703t1722r1026b1775],
18	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l703t1722r1026b1775],
19	WEBB	NNP	ORGANIZATION	WEBB	dep	13	SENT_154	[p4l1054t1708r1252b1767],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l1054t1708r1252b1767],
21	1993	CD	DATE	1993	appos	19	SENT_154	[p4l1288t1707r1442b1767],
22	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l1288t1707r1442b1767],
23	1994	CD	DATE	1994	appos	19	SENT_154	[p4l1478t1707r1630b1760],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_154	[p4l1478t1707r1630b1760],

1	Unnamed	JJ	O	unnamed	amod	3	SENT_155	[p4l11t1782r296b1835],
2	boring	JJ	O	boring	amod	3	SENT_155	[p4l321t1782r513b1847],
3	KLEEMANN	NNP	LOCATION	KLEEMANN	_	0	SENT_155	[p4l542t1782r891b1841],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_155	[p4l542t1782r891b1841],
5	1994	CD	DATE	1994	appos	3	SENT_155	[p4l927t1782r1081b1841],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_155	[p4l927t1782r1081b1841],
7	?gs	NNS	O	?gs	appos	5	SENT_155	[p4l1111t1781r1230b1847],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_155	[p4l1111t1781r1230b1847],

1	1-9	CD	NUMBER	1-9	_	0	SENT_156	[p4l1268t1781r1384b1833],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_156	[p4l1268t1781r1384b1833],

1	Diagnosis	NN	O	diagnosis	_	0	SENT_157	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_157	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_158	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_159	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_159	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],

1	?	NN	O	?	nn	3	SENT_160	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],
2	Clavate	NN	O	clavate	nn	3	SENT_160	[p4l89t1897r829b1970],
3	borings	NNS	O	boring	_	0	SENT_160	[p4l863t1897r1110b1971],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_160	[p4l1145t1896r1208b1955],
5	lithic	JJ	O	lithic	amod	6	SENT_160	[p4l1243t1896r1410b1955],
6	substrates	NNS	O	substrate	prep_in	3	SENT_160	[p4l1446t1897r1784b1955],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_160	[p4l1446t1897r1784b1955],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_161	[p4l1820t1896r1947b1955],
2	apertural	JJ	O	apertural	amod	3	SENT_161	[p4l1982t1913r2143b1971, p4l11t1979r158b2038],
3	region	NN	O	region	nsubj	16	SENT_161	[p4l195t1979r405b2054],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l441t1979r515b2037],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_161	[p4l547t1980r646b2038],
6	boring	NN	O	boring	prep_of	3	SENT_161	[p4l681t1979r896b2054],
7	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	8	SENT_161	[p4l933t1978r986b2037],
8	narrower	JJR	O	narrower	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l1023t1996r1321b2037],
9	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l1355t1980r1495b2037],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_161	[p4l1532t1980r1630b2037],
11	main	JJ	O	main	amod	12	SENT_161	[p4l1665t1978r1829b2037],
12	chamber	NN	O	chamber	prep_than	8	SENT_161	[p4l1864t1979r2146b2037],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l11t2064r128b2122],
14	may	MD	O	may	aux	16	SENT_161	[p4l164t2080r305b2137],
15	be	VB	O	be	cop	16	SENT_161	[p4l342t2063r419b2121],
16	circular	JJ	O	circular	conj_and	8	SENT_161	[p4l456t2063r719b2130],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l456t2063r719b2130],
18	oval	JJ	O	oval	conj_or	16	SENT_161	[p4l757t2063r917b2130],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l757t2063r917b2130],
20	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l956t2080r1024b2121],
21	dumb-bell	JJ	O	dumb-bell	amod	22	SENT_161	[p4l1058t2063r1396b2122],
22	shaped	JJ	O	shaped	conj_and	8	SENT_161	[p4l1434t2063r1676b2138],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_161	[p4l1434t2063r1676b2138],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_162	[p4l1714t2063r1842b2121],
2	aperture	NN	O	aperture	nsubjpass	5	SENT_162	[p4l1880t2071r2146b2137],
3	may	MD	O	may	aux	5	SENT_162	[p4l9t2163r149b2219],
4	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_162	[p4l193t2146r270b2204],
5	separated	VBN	O	separate	_	0	SENT_162	[p4l314t2146r622b2221],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_162	[p4l667t2146r826b2205],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_162	[p4l868t2146r967b2204],
8	main	JJ	O	main	amod	9	SENT_162	[p4l1010t2145r1175b2204],
9	chamber	NN	O	chamber	prep_from	5	SENT_162	[p4l1216t2145r1499b2204],
10	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_162	[p4l1540t2146r1620b2219],
11	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_162	[p4l1664t2163r1700b2204],
12	neck	NN	O	neck	nn	13	SENT_162	[p4l1741t2146r1897b2204],
13	region	NN	O	region	agent	5	SENT_162	[p4l1937t2144r2146b2220],
14	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	21	SENT_162	[p4l11t2228r210b2287],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_162	[p4l243t2229r306b2287],
16	some	DT	O	some	det	17	SENT_162	[p4l338t2245r509b2287],
17	cases	NNS	O	case	prep_in	21	SENT_162	[p4l540t2245r711b2287],
18	may	MD	O	may	aux	21	SENT_162	[p4l743t2245r883b2302],
19	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	21	SENT_162	[p4l914t2228r992b2286],
20	widely	RB	O	widely	advmod	21	SENT_162	[p4l1024t2228r1246b2301],
21	?ared	VBN	O	?ared	rcmod	13	SENT_162	[p4l1279t2228r1480b2287],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_162	[p4l1279t2228r1480b2287],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_163	[p4l1513t2228r1641b2286],
2	main	JJ	O	main	amod	3	SENT_163	[p4l1671t2228r1836b2286],
3	chamber	NN	O	chamber	nsubj	5	SENT_163	[p4l1864t2228r2147b2286],
4	may	MD	O	may	aux	5	SENT_163	[p4l10t2329r150b2385],
5	vary	VB	O	vary	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l184t2329r332b2385],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l366t2312r526b2371],
7	subspherical	JJ	O	subspherical	amod	45	SENT_163	[p4l559t2311r967b2387],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_163	[p4l1001t2321r1063b2370],
9	elongate	VB	O	elongate	xcomp	7	SENT_163	[p4l1095t2312r1392b2386],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1095t2312r1392b2386],
11	having	VBG	O	have	xcomp	9	SENT_163	[p4l1424t2311r1648b2386],
12	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_163	[p4l1681t2328r1717b2369],
13	parabolic	JJ	O	parabolic	amod	17	SENT_163	[p4l1747t2310r2051b2386],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	15	SENT_163	[p4l2083t2320r2145b2369],
15	rounded	VBN	O	round	xcomp	13	SENT_163	[p4l10t2395r281b2453],
16	truncated	VBN	O	truncate	dep	15	SENT_163	[p4l303t2395r608b2453],
17	base	NN	O	base	dobj	11	SENT_163	[p4l629t2395r775b2453],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l799t2395r916b2453],
19	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_163	[p4l939t2411r975b2452],
20	circular	JJ	O	circular	conj_and	17	SENT_163	[p4l996t2394r1248b2453],
21	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1268t2404r1330b2453],
22	oval	JJ	O	oval	amod	24	SENT_163	[p4l1352t2394r1490b2452],
23	cross	NN	O	cross	nn	24	SENT_163	[p4l1513t2411r1680b2452],
24	section	NN	O	section	prep_to	20	SENT_163	[p4l1703t2393r1951b2460],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1703t2393r1951b2460],
26	modi?ed	VBN	O	modi?ed	partmod	24	SENT_163	[p4l1973t2394r2144b2452, p4l11t2478r157b2536],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l178t2477r242b2536],
28	some	DT	O	some	det	29	SENT_163	[p4l265t2495r436b2536],
29	forms	NNS	O	form	prep_in	26	SENT_163	[p4l457t2478r648b2536],
30	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l669t2479r749b2551],
31	a	DT	O	a	det	33	SENT_163	[p4l773t2495r809b2536],
32	longitudinal	JJ	O	longitudinal	amod	33	SENT_163	[p4l829t2476r1224b2552],
33	ridge	NN	O	ridge	agent	26	SENT_163	[p4l1245t2476r1414b2551],
34	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1435t2494r1504b2535],
35	grooves	NNS	O	groove	conj_or	33	SENT_163	[p4l1523t2494r1780b2551],
36	to	TO	O	to	aux	37	SENT_163	[p4l1801t2486r1863b2535],
37	produce	VB	O	produce	xcomp	26	SENT_163	[p4l1882t2477r2146b2552],
38	an	DT	O	a	det	39	SENT_163	[p4l13t2579r88b2619],
39	almond	NN	O	almond	dobj	37	SENT_163	[p4l118t2561r365b2620],
40	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l394t2578r463b2619],
41	heart-shaped	JJ	O	heart-shaped	amod	43	SENT_163	[p4l490t2561r910b2637],
42	section	NN	O	section	nn	43	SENT_163	[p4l940t2561r1213b2619],
43	?	NN	O	?	dobj	37	SENT_163	[p4l940t2561r1213b2619],
44	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_163	[p4l1250t2561r1457b2634],
45	Kelly	NNP	PERSON	Kelly	prep_from	5	SENT_163	[p4l1250t2561r1457b2634],
46	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1487t2561r1604b2619],
47	Bromley	NNP	PERSON	Bromley	prep_from	5	SENT_163	[p4l1632t2561r1934b2634],
48	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1632t2561r1934b2634],
49	1984	CD	DATE	1984	appos	47	SENT_163	[p4l1971t2561r2144b2627],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l1971t2561r2144b2627],
51	p.	NN	O	p.	nn	53	SENT_163	[p4l10t2662r69b2719],
52	797	CD	NUMBER	797	num	53	SENT_163	[p4l102t2644r269b2713],
53	)	NN	O	)	appos	47	SENT_163	[p4l102t2644r269b2713],
54	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_163	[p4l102t2644r269b2713],

1	Type	NN	O	type	nn	2	SENT_164	[p4l98t2730r253b2801],
2	ichnospecies	NNS	O	ichnospecy	_	0	SENT_164	[p4l284t2728r877b2801],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_164	[p4l284t2728r877b2801],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_165	[p4l284t2728r877b2801],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_166	[p4l284t2728r877b2801],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_166	[p4l284t2728r877b2801],

1	G.	NNP	O	G.	nn	3	SENT_167	[p4l284t2728r877b2801],
2	lapidicus	NNP	O	lapidicus	nn	3	SENT_167	[p4l913t2727r1213b2800],
3	Kelly	NNP	PERSON	Kelly	_	0	SENT_167	[p4l1242t2728r1421b2800],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_167	[p4l1452t2727r1569b2785],
5	Bromley	NNP	PERSON	Bromley	conj_and	3	SENT_167	[p4l1597t2727r1899b2799],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_167	[p4l1597t2727r1899b2799],
7	1984	CD	DATE	1984	appos	3	SENT_167	[p4l1938t2727r2110b2786],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_167	[p4l1938t2727r2110b2786],

1	Remarks	NNS	O	remark	_	0	SENT_168	[p4l92t2810r613b2869],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_168	[p4l92t2810r613b2869],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_169	[p4l92t2810r613b2869],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_170	[p4l92t2810r613b2869],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_170	[p4l92t2810r613b2869],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_171	[p4l92t2810r613b2869],
2	ichnogenus	NN	O	ichnogenus	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l644t2809r1016b2884],
3	Gastrochaenolites	NNP	PERSON	Gastrochaenolites	nn	4	SENT_171	[p4l1049t2810r1649b2869],
4	Leymerie	NNP	PERSON	Leymerie	nsubjpass	9	SENT_171	[p4l1678t2809r1991b2884],
5	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_171	[p4l2020t2826r2146b2866],
6	thoroughly	RB	O	thoroughly	advmod	7	SENT_171	[p4l13t2893r372b2967],
7	assessed	VBN	O	assess	rcmod	2	SENT_171	[p4l398t2892r677b2951],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l701t2892r818b2950],
9	rede?ned	VBN	O	rede?ned	conj_and	7	SENT_171	[p4l840t2892r1146b2951],
10	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l1169t2893r1251b2965],
11	Kelly	NNP	PERSON	Kelly	agent	7	SENT_171	[p4l1277t2892r1456b2965],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l1482t2892r1599b2950],
13	Bromley	NNP	PERSON	Bromley	conj_and	11	SENT_171	[p4l1622t2892r1907b2965],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_171	[p4l1930t2892r2144b2962],
15	1984	CD	DATE	1984	num	16	SENT_171	[p4l1930t2892r2144b2962],
16	)	NN	O	)	dep	2	SENT_171	[p4l1930t2892r2144b2962],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l12t2976r76b3034],
18	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	19	SENT_171	[p4l98t2976r250b3034],
19	review	NN	O	review	prep_in	16	SENT_171	[p4l269t2975r491b3034],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l515t2976r588b3034],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_171	[p4l605t2977r704b3034],
22	ichnotaxonomy	NN	O	ichnotaxonomy	prep_of	19	SENT_171	[p4l725t2975r1236b3049],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l1258t2975r1331b3033],
24	clavate	NN	O	clavate	nn	25	SENT_171	[p4l1347t2976r1579b3034],
25	borings	NNS	O	boring	prep_of	22	SENT_171	[p4l1597t2975r1844b3050],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l1865t2975r1928b3033],
27	which	WDT	O	which	rel	32	SENT_171	[p4l1947t2975r2146b3033],
28	six	CD	NUMBER	six	num	30	SENT_171	[p4l13t3059r108b3117],
29	distinct	JJ	O	distinct	amod	30	SENT_171	[p4l137t3059r379b3118],
30	ichnospecies	NNS	O	ichnospecy	nsubjpass	32	SENT_171	[p4l407t3059r826b3133],
31	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	32	SENT_171	[p4l854t3076r1013b3117],
32	de?ned	VBN	O	de?ned	rcmod	16	SENT_171	[p4l1041t3059r1299b3117],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_171	[p4l1041t3059r1299b3117],
