1	Downloaded	VBN	O	download	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l285t81r488b110],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l501t81r573b110],
3	gsabul	NN	O	gsabul	nn	5	SENT_1	[p1l587t81r980b117],
4	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	5	SENT_1	[p1l587t81r980b117],
5	etin.gsapubs.org	NN	O	etin.gsapubs.org	prep_from	1	SENT_1	[p1l587t81r980b117],
6	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l994t88r1032b110],
7	May	NNP	DATE	May	prep_on	5	SENT_1	[p1l1047t81r1115b117],
8	8	CD	DATE	8	num	7	SENT_1	[p1l1127t82r1154b114],
9	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l1127t82r1154b114],
10	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	7	SENT_1	[p1l1169t82r1249b110],

1	Geological	JJ	ORGANIZATION	geological	amod	2	SENT_2	[p1l284t173r576b229],
2	Society	NN	ORGANIZATION	society	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l598t173r803b229],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l822t174r874b218],
4	America	NNP	ORGANIZATION	America	nn	5	SENT_2	[p1l893t174r1120b218],
5	Bulletin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bulletin	prep_of	2	SENT_2	[p1l1142t174r1348b218],

1	Lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	2	SENT_3	[p1l286t304r428b342],
2	Llandovery	NN	O	llandovery	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l447t304r709b352],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l725t304r770b342],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_3	[p1l785t304r858b342],
5	Northern	NNP	O	Northern	nn	6	SENT_3	[p1l877t304r1082b342],
6	Appalachians	NNPS	O	Appalachians	prep_of	2	SENT_3	[p1l1100t304r1422b352],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1439t304r1524b342],
8	Adjacent	NNP	O	Adjacent	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l1542t304r1750b352],
9	Regions	NNPS	O	Regions	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l286t354r478b402],
10	WILLIAM	NNP	PERSON	WILLIAM	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l283t418r451b449],
11	G	NNP	PERSON	G	nn	12	SENT_3	[p1l467t418r495b450],
12	AYRTON	NNP	PERSON	AYRTON	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l509t418r691b455],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l509t418r691b455],
14	WILLIAM	NNP	PERSON	WILLIAM	nn	17	SENT_3	[p1l707t418r874b449],
15	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	17	SENT_3	[p1l892t418r925b449],
16	N	NNP	PERSON	N	nn	17	SENT_3	[p1l942t418r967b449],
17	BERRY	NNP	PERSON	BERRY	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l984t418r1133b455],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l984t418r1133b455],
19	ARTHUR	NNP	PERSON	ARTHUR	nn	21	SENT_3	[p1l1149t418r1320b450],
20	J	NNP	PERSON	J	nn	21	SENT_3	[p1l1334t418r1351b450],
21	BOUCOT	NNP	PERSON	BOUCOT	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l1369t418r1552b455],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1369t418r1552b455],
23	JEAN	NNP	PERSON	JEAN	nn	24	SENT_3	[p1l1567t418r1670b450],
24	LAJOIE	NNP	PERSON	LAJOIE	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l1688t418r1837b455],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1688t418r1837b455],
26	PIERRE	NNP	PERSON	PIERRE	nn	28	SENT_3	[p1l286t459r435b491],
27	J	NNP	PERSON	J	nn	28	SENT_3	[p1l449t459r467b492],
28	LESPERANCE	NNP	PERSON	LESPERANCE	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l484t459r769b497],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l484t459r769b497],
30	LOUIS	NNP	O	LOUIS	nn	31	SENT_3	[p1l787t459r908b492],
31	PAVLIDES	NNP	PERSON	PAVLIDES	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l925t459r1123b492],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1138t459r1204b492],
33	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	37	SENT_3	[p1l1218t459r1265b491],
34	BRIAN	NNP	PERSON	BRIAN	nn	37	SENT_3	[p1l1283t459r1404b491],
35	SKIDMORE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	SKIDMORE	nn	37	SENT_3	[p1l1421t459r1639b492],
36	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	37	SENT_3	[p1l286t517r482b557],
37	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	conj_and	2	SENT_3	[p1l494t517r631b557],
38	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l642t517r679b549],
39	America	NNP	ORGANIZATION	America	nn	40	SENT_3	[p1l686t517r838b549],
40	Bulletin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bulletin	prep_of	37	SENT_3	[p1l852t517r987b549],
41	1969	CD	DATE	1969	num	40	SENT_3	[p1l1001t518r1156b554],
42	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1001t518r1156b554],
43	80	CD	NUMBER	80	dep	2	SENT_3	[p1l1001t518r1156b554],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1001t518r1156b554],
45	no.	RB	O	no.	advmod	46	SENT_3	[p1l1174t525r1226b549],
46	3	CD	NUMBER	3	rcmod	43	SENT_3	[p1l1242t518r1427b554],
47	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1242t518r1427b554],
48	459-484	CD	NUMBER	459-484	dep	2	SENT_3	[p1l1242t518r1427b554],
49	doi	FW	O	doi	dep	48	SENT_3	[p1l283t570r347b602],
50	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l283t570r347b602],
51	10.1130	CD	NUMBER	10.1130	dep	2	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
52	/	:	O	/	punct	56	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
53	0016	CD	DATE	0016	number	54	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
54	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	56	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
55	7606	CD	NUMBER	7606	number	56	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
56	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	51	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
57	1969	CD	DATE	1969	num	58	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
58	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	56	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
59	80	CD	NUMBER	80	num	60	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
60	[	NN	O	[	dep	56	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
61	459	CD	NUMBER	459	dep	51	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
62	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
63	LLOTNA	NN	O	llotna	dep	2	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
64	]	CD	NUMBER	]	number	65	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
65	2.0	CD	NUMBER	2.0	dep	63	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
66	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l365t570r1320b610],

1	CO	NN	O	co	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
2	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l365t570r1320b610],
3	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	1	SENT_4	[p1l365t570r1320b610],

1	Notes	NNS	O	note	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l284t1683r385b1712],

1	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l284t1868r460b1908],
2	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	3	SENT_15	[p1l471t1868r503b1900],
3	1969	CD	DATE	1969	dep	1	SENT_15	[p1l518t1869r615b1905],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l518t1869r615b1905],
5	The	DT	ORGANIZATION	the	det	8	SENT_15	[p1l631t1868r700b1900],
6	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	8	SENT_15	[p1l715t1868r907b1908],
7	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	nn	8	SENT_15	[p1l924t1868r1057b1908],
8	F	NN	ORGANIZATION	f	appos	3	SENT_15	[p1l1587t1866r1703b1950],
9	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l283t1910r316b1942],
10	America	NNP	ORGANIZATION	America	nn	12	SENT_15	[p1l329t1910r489b1947],
11	,	,	ORGANIZATION	,	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l329t1910r489b1947],
12	Inc.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Inc.	prep_of	8	SENT_15	[p1l508t1910r568b1942],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l508t1910r568b1942],

1	GEOLOGICAL	NN	O	geological	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1587t2054r1855b2088],

1	Downloaded	VBN	O	download	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l333t2207r536b2236],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l549t2207r621b2236],
3	gsabul	NN	O	gsabul	nn	5	SENT_19	[p1l635t2207r1028b2243],
4	|	CD	NUMBER	|	num	5	SENT_19	[p1l635t2207r1028b2243],
5	etin.gsapubs.org	NN	O	etin.gsapubs.org	prep_from	1	SENT_19	[p1l635t2207r1028b2243],
6	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1042t2214r1080b2236],
7	May	NNP	DATE	May	prep_on	5	SENT_19	[p1l1095t2207r1163b2243],
8	8	CD	DATE	8	num	7	SENT_19	[p1l1175t2208r1202b2240],
9	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1175t2208r1202b2240],
10	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	7	SENT_19	[p1l1217t2208r1297b2236],

1	WILLIAM	NNP	PERSON	WILLIAM	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l304t2319r468b2345],
2	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l487t2319r522b2345],
3	AYRTON1	NNP	PERSON	AYRTON1	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l541t2318r712b2345],
4	Pan	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pan	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l748t2319r800b2345],
5	American	NNP	ORGANIZATION	American	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l814t2318r947b2345],
6	Petroleum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Petroleum	nn	7	SENT_20	[p1l960t2318r1098b2345],
7	Corporation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Corporation	dep	39	SENT_20	[p1l1113t2319r1285b2354],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1113t2319r1285b2354],
9	Calgary	NNP	LOCATION	Calgary	appos	7	SENT_20	[p1l1301t2319r1414b2355],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1301t2319r1414b2355],
11	Alberta	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Alberta	nn	16	SENT_20	[p1l1428t2319r1531b2346],
12	WILLIAM	NNP	ORGANIZATION	WILLIAM	nn	16	SENT_20	[p1l305t2364r468b2390],
13	B.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	B.	nn	16	SENT_20	[p1l488t2364r518b2390],
14	N.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	N.	nn	16	SENT_20	[p1l539t2364r574b2390],
15	BERRY	NNP	ORGANIZATION	BERRY	nn	16	SENT_20	[p1l595t2363r722b2390],
16	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	7	SENT_20	[p1l762t2363r899b2397],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l910t2364r945b2398],
18	California	NNP	ORGANIZATION	California	nn	24	SENT_20	[p1l952t2363r1099b2399],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l952t2363r1099b2399],
20	Berkeley	NNP	LOCATION	Berkeley	appos	24	SENT_20	[p1l1113t2363r1235b2399],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1113t2363r1235b2399],
22	California	NNP	LOCATION	California	appos	24	SENT_20	[p1l1250t2364r1390b2399],
23	94720	CD	NUMBER	94720	num	24	SENT_20	[p1l1403t2365r1487b2391],
24	ARTHUR	NNP	O	ARTHUR	prep_of	16	SENT_20	[p1l303t2408r460b2434],
25	I.	NNP	O	I.	nn	27	SENT_20	[p1l473t2408r493b2439],
26	BOUCOT	NNP	ORGANIZATION	BOUCOT	nn	27	SENT_20	[p1l508t2407r665b2434],
27	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	24	SENT_20	[p1l703t2407r839b2442],
28	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l852t2407r886b2443],
29	Pennsylvania	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pennsylvania	prep_of	27	SENT_20	[p1l890t2408r1076b2443],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l890t2408r1076b2443],
31	Philadelphia	NNP	LOCATION	Philadelphia	nn	33	SENT_20	[p1l1089t2408r1269b2444],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1089t2408r1269b2444],
33	Pennsylvania	NNP	LOCATION	Pennsylvania	appos	7	SENT_20	[p1l1283t2409r1459b2444],
34	19104	CD	NUMBER	19104	dep	39	SENT_20	[p1l1474t2409r1557b2436],
35	IEAN	NNP	O	IEAN	nn	39	SENT_20	[p1l302t2454r393b2485],
36	LAIOIE	NNP	O	LAIOIE	nn	39	SENT_20	[p1l411t2454r537b2485],
37	Uniuersil?	NNP	O	Uniuersil?	nn	39	SENT_20	[p1l577t2452r712b2480],
38	de	IN	O	de	amod	39	SENT_20	[p1l723t2453r754b2479],
39	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l766t2453r903b2483],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l766t2453r903b2483],
41	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l917t2453r1054b2484],
42	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l917t2453r1054b2484],
43	Quebec	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Quebec	nn	49	SENT_20	[p1l1069t2454r1171b2487],
44	PIERRE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	PIERRE	nn	49	SENT_20	[p1l303t2499r439b2525],
45	I.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	I.	nn	49	SENT_20	[p1l458t2500r478b2531],
46	LESPERANCE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	LESPERANCE	nn	49	SENT_20	[p1l498t2495r741b2526],
47	Universit?	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universit?	nn	49	SENT_20	[p1l781t2498r915b2525],
48	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	amod	49	SENT_20	[p1l926t2499r957b2525],
49	Montreal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Montreal	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l969t2498r1105b2529],
50	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l969t2498r1105b2529],
51	Montreal	NNP	LOCATION	Montreal	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l1119t2500r1254b2530],
52	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1119t2500r1254b2530],
53	Quebec	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Quebec	nn	58	SENT_20	[p1l1270t2499r1372b2533],
54	LOUIS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	LOUIS	nn	58	SENT_20	[p1l302t2544r411b2570],
55	PAVLIDES	NNP	ORGANIZATION	PAVLIDES	nn	58	SENT_20	[p1l431t2544r609b2570],
56	U.S.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	U.S.	nn	58	SENT_20	[p1l649t2544r707b2570],
57	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	58	SENT_20	[p1l723t2543r872b2578],
58	Survey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Survey	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l882t2544r982b2578],
59	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l882t2544r982b2578],
60	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	Washington	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l999t2543r1168b2578],
61	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l999t2543r1168b2578],
62	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	65	SENT_20	[p1l1182t2545r1218b2570],
63	C.	NNP	O	C.	nn	65	SENT_20	[p1l1232t2545r1261b2570],
64	20242	CD	NUMBER	20242	num	65	SENT_20	[p1l1275t2545r1359b2570],
65	W.	NNP	O	W.	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l303t2589r343b2615],
66	BRIAN	NNP	O	BRIAN	nn	68	SENT_20	[p1l364t2589r481b2615],
67	SKIDMORE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	SKIDMORE	nn	68	SENT_20	[p1l500t2589r701b2615],
68	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	dep	65	SENT_20	[p1l738t2589r902b2623],
69	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l914t2590r949b2624],
70	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	71	SENT_20	[p1l953t2589r1066b2615],
71	Resources	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Resources	prep_of	68	SENT_20	[p1l1075t2590r1215b2619],
72	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1075t2590r1215b2619],
73	Quebec	NNP	LOCATION	Quebec	nn	75	SENT_20	[p1l1231t2589r1339b2623],
74	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1231t2589r1339b2623],
75	Quebec	NNP	LOCATION	Quebec	appos	39	SENT_20	[p1l1354t2589r1456b2623],

1	Lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	2	SENT_21	[p1l303t2701r502b2755],
2	Llandovery	NN	O	llandovery	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l525t2699r863b2769],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l886t2699r957b2754],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_21	[p1l976t2701r1072b2754],
5	Northern	NNP	O	Northern	nn	6	SENT_21	[p1l1095t2700r1378b2756],
6	Appalachians	NNPS	O	Appalachians	prep_of	2	SENT_21	[p1l301t2805r697b2880],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l723t2805r825b2860],
8	Adjacent	NNP	O	Adjacent	nn	9	SENT_21	[p1l850t2804r1109b2876],
9	Regions	NNPS	O	Regions	prep_of	2	SENT_21	[p1l1134t2806r1376b2880],

1	Abstract	JJ	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l302t2957r454b2987],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l302t2957r454b2987],
3	Rocks	NNS	O	rock	dep	1	SENT_22	[p1l491t2957r588b2986],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l603t2955r638b2986],
5	clearly	RB	O	clearly	advmod	6	SENT_22	[p1l651t2956r755b2996],
6	dated	VBN	O	date	dep	44	SENT_22	[p1l772t2955r861b2986],
7	early	JJ	O	early	amod	9	SENT_22	[p1l878t2956r955b2997],
8	Llandovery	NNP	O	Llandovery	nn	9	SENT_22	[p1l972t2956r1157b2996],
9	age	NN	O	age	nsubj	28	SENT_22	[p1l1174t2968r1233b2995],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1174t2968r1233b2995],
11	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1252t2969r1280b2987],
12	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1296t2956r1359b2987],
13	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1376t2968r1404b2987],
14	rocks	NNS	O	rock	conj_and	9	SENT_22	[p1l1422t2956r1502b2987],
15	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	19	SENT_22	[p1l1520t2957r1584b2987],
16	can	MD	O	can	aux	19	SENT_22	[p1l1602t2968r1654b2986],
17	logically	RB	O	logically	advmod	19	SENT_22	[p1l1670t2956r1802b2997],
18	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	19	SENT_22	[p1l1820t2956r1855b2986],
19	classed	VBN	O	class	rcmod	14	SENT_22	[p1l304t2998r407b3030],
20	as	RB	O	as	advmod	22	SENT_22	[p1l420t3010r449b3029],
21	early	JJ	O	early	amod	22	SENT_22	[p1l462t2998r539b3038],
22	Llandovery	NN	O	llandovery	dobj	19	SENT_22	[p1l552t2997r737b3038],
23	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l750t2998r827b3029],
24	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	26	SENT_22	[p1l841t2998r916b3029],
25	regional	JJ	O	regional	amod	26	SENT_22	[p1l930t2998r1055b3037],
26	relationships	NNS	O	relationship	prep_from	19	SENT_22	[p1l1069t2998r1275b3039],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1069t2998r1275b3039],
28	appear	VBP	O	appear	ccomp	6	SENT_22	[p1l1290t3010r1395b3039],
29	to	TO	O	to	aux	32	SENT_22	[p1l1409t3007r1440b3028],
30	be	VB	O	be	cop	32	SENT_22	[p1l1455t2998r1489b3028],
31	more	RBR	O	more	advmod	32	SENT_22	[p1l1503t3010r1582b3030],
32	widespread	JJ	O	widespread	xcomp	28	SENT_22	[p1l1595t2998r1770b3039],
33	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1785t2998r1854b3029],
34	recognized	VBN	O	recognize	prep_than	32	SENT_22	[p1l304t3040r480b3080],
35	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l304t3040r480b3080],
36	heretofore	RB	O	heretofore	dep	34	SENT_22	[p1l505t3040r676b3076],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l505t3040r676b3076],
38	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l700t3041r730b3070],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_22	[p1l754t3040r804b3072],
40	northern	JJ	O	northern	amod	41	SENT_22	[p1l826t3040r966b3072],
41	Appalachians	NNPS	MISC	Appalachians	prep_in	34	SENT_22	[p1l988t3040r1198b3082],
42	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1219t3040r1275b3071],
43	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	conj_and	6	SENT_22	[p1l1298t3040r1431b3080],
44	regions	NNS	O	region	prep_of	3	SENT_22	[p1l1454t3041r1572b3080],
45	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1454t3041r1572b3080],

1	Their	PRP$	O	they	poss	3	SENT_23	[p1l1595t3040r1684b3072],
2	areal	JJ	O	areal	amod	3	SENT_23	[p1l1706t3041r1779b3072],
3	distribution	NN	O	distribution	nsubj	6	SENT_23	[p1l1801t3040r1854b3071, p1l305t3083r448b3113],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l464t3082r520b3113],
5	lithology	NN	O	lithology	conj_and	3	SENT_23	[p1l537t3082r679b3123],
6	permit	VBP	O	permit	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l696t3083r803b3123],
7	a	DT	O	a	nsubj	8	SENT_23	[p1l820t3094r835b3114],
8	generalized	VBN	O	generalize	dep	6	SENT_23	[p1l850t3081r1029b3122],
9	reconstruction	NN	O	reconstruction	dobj	8	SENT_23	[p1l1046t3083r1275b3113],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1291t3082r1325b3112],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_23	[p1l1340t3081r1388b3114],
12	paleogcography	NN	O	paleogcography	prep_of	9	SENT_23	[p1l1404t3082r1660b3123],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1404t3082r1660b3123],
14	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	15	SENT_23	[p1l1678t3082r1772b3113],
15	consisted	VBD	O	consist	rcmod	12	SENT_23	[p1l1790t3094r1855b3114, p1l303t3123r397b3160],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1790t3094r1855b3114, p1l303t3123r397b3160],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l415t3126r445b3154],
18	general	JJ	O	general	prep_in	8	SENT_23	[p1l460t3125r582b3164],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l460t3125r582b3164],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l601t3123r634b3155],
21	three	CD	NUMBER	three	num	23	SENT_23	[p1l649t3125r729b3155],
22	source	NN	O	source	nn	23	SENT_23	[p1l745t3136r844b3155],
23	areas	NNS	O	area	prep_of	18	SENT_23	[p1l860t3136r936b3155],
24	alternating	VBG	O	alternate	partmod	23	SENT_23	[p1l951t3125r1124b3164],
25	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1139t3123r1215b3155],
26	east	JJ	O	east	amod	31	SENT_23	[p1l1231t3133r1289b3155],
27	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1307t3134r1338b3155],
28	west	NN	O	west	prep_to	26	SENT_23	[p1l1354t3133r1423b3155],
29	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1439t3125r1510b3155],
30	three	CD	NUMBER	three	prep_with	28	SENT_23	[p1l1528t3123r1608b3156],
31	belts	NNS	O	belt	prep_from	24	SENT_23	[p1l1625t3125r1697b3155],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1713t3123r1747b3155],
33	clastic	JJ	O	clastic	amod	34	SENT_23	[p1l1760t3125r1855b3156],
34	sedimentation	NN	O	sedimentation	prep_of	31	SENT_23	[p1l303t3167r536b3197],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l303t3167r536b3197],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_24	[p1l549t3166r613b3198],
2	westernmost	JJ	O	westernmost	amod	5	SENT_24	[p1l626t3176r824b3198],
3	clastic	JJ	O	clastic	amod	5	SENT_24	[p1l837t3167r932b3198],
4	belt	NN	O	belt	nn	5	SENT_24	[p1l945t3167r1005b3197],
5	grades	NNS	O	grade	nsubj	6	SENT_24	[p1l1016t3167r1115b3207],
6	laterally	RB	O	laterally	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1127t3167r1256b3207],
7	westward	RB	O	westward	dep	6	SENT_24	[p1l1269t3166r1416b3197],
8	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1428t3168r1491b3197],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_24	[p1l1505t3167r1553b3197],
10	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	11	SENT_24	[p1l1566t3166r1719b3198],
11	rocks	NNS	O	rock	prep_into	6	SENT_24	[p1l1732t3168r1814b3197],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1825t3167r1858b3197],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_24	[p1l305t3273r354b3304],
14	North	JJ	MISC	north	amod	16	SENT_24	[p1l369t3273r468b3303],
15	American	JJ	MISC	american	amod	16	SENT_24	[p1l484t3274r637b3304],
16	platform	NN	O	platform	prep_of	11	SENT_24	[p1l654t3273r800b3312],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l654t3273r800b3312],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_25	[p1l817t3273r881b3304],
2	Central	NNP	O	Central	nn	4	SENT_25	[p1l896t3273r1016b3303],
3	Clastic	NNP	O	Clastic	nn	4	SENT_25	[p1l1031t3273r1138b3303],
4	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nsubj	5	SENT_25	[p1l1155t3273r1221b3303],
5	encloses	VBZ	O	enclose	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1238t3273r1361b3303],
6	a	DT	O	a	det	7	SENT_25	[p1l1376t3286r1392b3303],
7	belt	NN	O	belt	dobj	5	SENT_25	[p1l1409t3272r1469b3303],
8	containing	VBG	O	contain	partmod	7	SENT_25	[p1l1485t3274r1651b3312],
9	impure	JJ	O	impure	amod	10	SENT_25	[p1l1667t3274r1779b3313],
10	carbonates	NNS	O	carbonate	dobj	8	SENT_25	[p1l1797t3284r1854b3303, p1l305t3315r424b3346],
11	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l443t3315r514b3346],
12	clastic	JJ	O	clastic	amod	13	SENT_25	[p1l534t3315r630b3346],
13	detritus	NN	O	detritus	prep_with	8	SENT_25	[p1l648t3315r772b3345],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l790t3314r847b3345],
15	clastic	JJ	O	clastic	amod	16	SENT_25	[p1l867t3316r961b3346],
16	interbeds	NNS	O	interbed	conj_and	13	SENT_25	[p1l980t3315r1134b3350],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l980t3315r1134b3350],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1154t3315r1219b3350],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1154t3315r1219b3350],
20	locally	RB	O	locally	advmod	13	SENT_25	[p1l1240t3315r1350b3355],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1240t3315r1350b3355],
22	relatively	RB	O	relatively	advmod	23	SENT_25	[p1l1371t3315r1518b3355],
23	clean	JJ	O	clean	amod	25	SENT_25	[p1l1538t3315r1616b3345],
24	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	25	SENT_25	[p1l1635t3314r1788b3346],
25	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_with	8	SENT_25	[p1l1807t3314r1854b3345, p1l304t3359r400b3398],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1807t3314r1854b3345, p1l304t3359r400b3398],

1	Llandovery	JJ	O	llandovery	amod	3	SENT_26	[p1l340t3399r524b3438],
2	age	NN	O	age	nn	3	SENT_26	[p1l544t3411r595b3438],
3	rocks	NNS	O	rock	nsubj	7	SENT_26	[p1l614t3400r696b3429],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l714t3399r748b3429],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_26	[p1l764t3398r813b3429],
6	platform	NN	O	platform	prep_of	3	SENT_26	[p1l833t3399r971b3438],
7	include	VBP	O	include	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l989t3399r1104b3429],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_26	[p1l1124t3399r1173b3429],
9	Manitoulin	NNP	LOCATION	Manitoulin	nn	10	SENT_26	[p1l1192t3399r1372b3429],
10	Dolomite	NNP	LOCATION	Dolomite	dobj	7	SENT_26	[p1l1390t3398r1540b3429],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1559t3398r1615b3429],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_26	[p1l1636t3399r1685b3429],
13	Ellis	NNP	LOCATION	Ellis	nn	15	SENT_26	[p1l1703t3398r1774b3428],
14	Bay	NNP	LOCATION	Bay	nn	15	SENT_26	[p1l1792t3400r1855b3438],
15	Formation	NN	O	formation	conj_and	10	SENT_26	[p1l303t3440r482b3469],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l303t3440r482b3469],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l499t3441r533b3469],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_27	[p1l549t3439r599b3469],
3	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_in	10	SENT_27	[p1l614t3439r741b3478],
4	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l757t3448r788b3469],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_27	[p1l804t3439r852b3469],
6	east	JJ	O	east	prep_to	3	SENT_27	[p1l867t3448r935b3473],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l867t3448r935b3473],
8	coeval	JJ	O	coeval	amod	9	SENT_27	[p1l952t3439r1050b3469],
9	rocks	NNS	O	rock	nsubj	10	SENT_27	[p1l1066t3439r1147b3469],
10	occur	VBP	O	occur	conj_and	10	SENT_27	[p1l1161t3450r1255b3473],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1161t3450r1255b3473],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1272t3440r1301b3468],
13	part	NN	O	part	prep_in	10	SENT_27	[p1l1316t3447r1381b3478],
14	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1395t3449r1428b3469],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1442t3440r1472b3468],
16	whole	JJ	O	whole	conj_or	13	SENT_27	[p1l1486t3438r1586b3473],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1486t3438r1586b3473],
18	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1603t3439r1705b3469],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_27	[p1l1722t3439r1770b3469],
20	limy	JJ	O	limy	amod	23	SENT_27	[p1l1785t3439r1855b3478],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l304t3480r360b3512],
22	clastic	JJ	O	clastic	conj_and	20	SENT_27	[p1l378t3480r474b3512],
23	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_within	10	SENT_27	[p1l490t3479r617b3521],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l633t3479r667b3510],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_27	[p1l681t3480r730b3511],
26	Carys	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Carys	nn	28	SENT_27	[p1l746t3482r838b3521],
27	Mills	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mills	nn	28	SENT_27	[p1l854t3480r934b3511],
28	Formation	NN	ORGANIZATION	formation	prep_of	23	SENT_27	[p1l949t3481r1119b3511],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1135t3479r1192b3511],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_27	[p1l1210t3479r1259b3511],
31	Matapedia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Matapedia	nn	32	SENT_27	[p1l1276t3480r1445b3520],
32	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	prep_of	23	SENT_27	[p1l1461t3481r1575b3520],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1461t3481r1575b3520],
34	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1592t3491r1621b3511],
35	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1636t3479r1699b3511],
36	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1716t3491r1744b3511],
37	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1760t3480r1789b3510],
38	the	DT	O	the	prep_in	10	SENT_27	[p1l1808t3479r1857b3511],
39	following	VBG	O	follow	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l302t3522r450b3561],
40	clastic	JJ	O	clastic	amod	42	SENT_27	[p1l476t3522r572b3553],
41	rock	NN	O	rock	nn	42	SENT_27	[p1l598t3522r667b3552],
42	formations	NNS	O	formation	prep_following	38	SENT_27	[p1l692t3521r873b3552],
43	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l692t3521r873b3552],
44	Grimsby	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Grimsby	nn	64	SENT_27	[p1l900t3522r1048b3562],
45	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l900t3522r1048b3562],
46	Shawangunk	NNP	LOCATION	Shawangunk	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l1076t3521r1286b3561],
47	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1076t3521r1286b3561],
48	Tuscarora	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Tuscarora	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l1312t3523r1477b3557],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1312t3523r1477b3557],
50	Massanutten	NNP	LOCATION	Massanutten	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l1504t3523r1714b3556],
51	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1504t3523r1714b3556],
52	Clinch	NNP	O	Clinch	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l1740t3521r1854b3556],
53	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1740t3521r1854b3556],
54	Smyrna	NNP	LOCATION	Smyrna	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l302t3564r426b3603],
55	Mills	NNP	LOCATION	Mills	nn	64	SENT_27	[p1l440t3563r528b3597],
56	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l440t3563r528b3597],
57	Perham	NNP	PERSON	Perham	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l544t3563r677b3597],
58	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l544t3563r677b3597],
59	Cabano	NNP	O	Cabano	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l692t3563r820b3598],
60	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l692t3563r820b3598],
61	Weir	NNP	PERSON	Weir	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l837t3564r923b3597],
62	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l837t3564r923b3597],
63	Beechhill	NNP	PERSON	Beechhill	appos	64	SENT_27	[p1l938t3563r1086b3593],
64	Cove	NNP	PERSON	Cove	conj_and	42	SENT_27	[p1l1099t3564r1190b3598],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1099t3564r1190b3598],
66	Ross	NNP	PERSON	Ross	nn	67	SENT_27	[p1l1206t3565r1277b3593],
67	Brook	NNP	PERSON	Brook	conj_and	42	SENT_27	[p1l1291t3563r1397b3598],
68	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1291t3563r1397b3598],
69	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1413t3562r1469b3593],
70	White	NNP	LOCATION	White	nn	71	SENT_27	[p1l1484t3562r1582b3593],
71	Rock	NNP	LOCATION	Rock	conj_and	42	SENT_27	[p1l1595t3563r1687b3593],
72	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1595t3563r1687b3593],

1	CONTENTS	NNS	O	contents	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l983t3678r1185b3705],

1	Introduction	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l9t66r495b140],
2	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	3	SENT_29	[p2l924t128r933b140],[p2l569t128r581b140],
3	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	dep	1	SENT_29	[p2l1368t128r1377b137],[p2l1012t128r1024b137],
4	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	dep	3	SENT_29	[p2l1811t128r1823b140],[p2l1459t128r1468b140],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p2l1900t126r1912b137],

1	460	CD	NUMBER	460	num	2	SENT_30	[p2l2022t74r2153b140],
2	Acknowledgments	NNS	O	acknowledgment	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l9t162r706b253],
3	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	4	SENT_30	[p2l1103t224r1115b233],[p2l748t224r757b236],
4	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	dep	2	SENT_30	[p2l1547t221r1559b233],[p2l1192t221r1203b233],
5	. . . .	NN	O	. . . .	dep	4	SENT_30	[p2l1903t221r1912b231],[p2l1635t224r1647b233],
6	460	CD	NUMBER	460	num	7	SENT_30	[p2l2022t167r2150b233],
7	Lithofacies	NNPS	O	Lithofacies	dep	2	SENT_30	[p2l6t256r424b333],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l452t259r586b330],
9	paleogeography	NN	O	paleogeography	dep	2	SENT_30	[p2l620t259r1215b350],
10	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	9	SENT_30	[p2l1635t321r1644b330],[p2l1280t321r1292b330],
11	. . .	NN	O	. . .	nn	14	SENT_30	[p2l1903t318r1912b327],[p2l1723t321r1735b330],
12	460	CD	NUMBER	460	num	14	SENT_30	[p2l2019t264r2150b330],
13	Carbonate	NNP	O	Carbonate	nn	14	SENT_30	[p2l97t355r490b427],
14	Rocks	NNP	O	Rocks	dep	2	SENT_30	[p2l526t356r757b427],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l785t356r865b424],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_30	[p2l890t358r1007b424],
17	Platform	NNP	O	Platform	nn	18	SENT_30	[p2l1044t353r1383b424],
18	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	prep_of	14	SENT_30	[p2l1814t415r1826b427],[p2l1459t415r1468b424],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p2l1902t413r1914b424],

1	460	CD	NUMBER	460	nsubj	13	SENT_31	[p2l2022t358r2153b424],
2	Sandstone	NNP	O	Sandstone	nn	6	SENT_31	[p2l100t450r481b521],
3	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nn	6	SENT_31	[p2l518t450r675b521],
4	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	6	SENT_31	[p2l1103t512r1115b524],[p2l748t512r760b524],
5	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	6	SENT_31	[p2l1547t512r1559b521],[p2l1192t512r1203b521],
6	. . . .	NNP	O	. . . .	dep	1	SENT_31	[p2l1903t510r1912b521],[p2l1638t512r1647b521],
7	463	CD	NUMBER	463	dep	1	SENT_31	[p2l2019t455r2148b521],
8	Central	NNP	O	Central	nn	12	SENT_31	[p2l100t552r384b620],
9	Clastic	NNP	O	Clastic	nn	12	SENT_31	[p2l415t549r669b620],
10	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nn	12	SENT_31	[p2l705t549r862b620],
11	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	12	SENT_31	[p2l1283t608r1292b620],[p2l924t608r939b620],
12	. . .	NNP	O	. . .	dep	7	SENT_31	[p2l1550t608r1559b617],[p2l1371t608r1383b617],
13	_	VBD	O	_	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1638t608r1647b620],
14	. . .	CD	NUMBER	. . .	number	15	SENT_31	[p2l1903t606r1914b620],[p2l1726t606r1735b617],
15	463	CD	NUMBER	463	dobj	13	SENT_31	[p2l2022t552r2148b617],
16	Port	NNP	LOCATION	Port	nn	18	SENT_31	[p2l191t653r359b716],
17	Daniel	NNP	LOCATION	Daniel	nn	18	SENT_31	[p2l392t645r640b716],
18	area	NN	O	area	dep	15	SENT_31	[p2l671t667r845b725],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l671t667r845b725],
20	Quebec	NNP	LOCATION	Quebec	appos	15	SENT_31	[p2l882t642r1169b730],
21	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	20	SENT_31	[p2l1638t704r1647b713],[p2l1283t704r1292b713],
22	. . .	CD	NUMBER	. . .	number	23	SENT_31	[p2l1903t701r1912b713],[p2l1726t701r1735b713],
23	463	CD	NUMBER	463	dep	20	SENT_31	[p2l2019t645r2148b710],
24	Cabano	NNP	O	Cabano	nn	25	SENT_31	[p2l188t741r475b812],
25	area	NN	O	area	dep	23	SENT_31	[p2l506t766r680b824],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l506t766r680b824],
27	Quebec	NNP	LOCATION	Quebec	nn	32	SENT_31	[p2l717t741r1002b829],
28	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	32	SENT_31	[p2l1462t803r1471b812],[p2l1103t803r1115b812],
29	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	32	SENT_31	[p2l1905t800r1914b812],[p2l1550t800r1559b812],
30	464	CD	NUMBER	464	num	32	SENT_31	[p2l2022t746r2150b812],
31	Seigas	NNP	O	Seigas	nn	32	SENT_31	[p2l188t839r419b925],
32	Quarry	NNP	O	Quarry	appos	15	SENT_31	[p2l447t842r746b925],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l447t842r746b925],
34	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	36	SENT_31	[p2l782t842r959b908],
35	Brunswick	NNP	LOCATION	Brunswick	nn	36	SENT_31	[p2l990t834r1391b905],
36	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	appos	32	SENT_31	[p2l1814t896r1823b905],[p2l1462t896r1471b905],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p2l1903t896r1912b905],

1	470	CD	NUMBER	470	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l2019t839r2150b905],
2	Central	NNP	O	Central	nn	4	SENT_32	[p2l191t933r473b1004],
3	New	NNP	O	New	nn	4	SENT_32	[p2l506t941r683b1004],
4	Brunswick	NNP	O	Brunswick	dep	1	SENT_32	[p2l714t933r1115b1004],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p2l1194t992r1203b1004],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p2l1280t995r1292b1004],

1	470	CD	NUMBER	470	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l2022t938r2150b1001],
2	Northeast	NNP	LOCATION	Northeast	nn	3	SENT_34	[p2l188t1032r566b1100],
3	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	Maine	dep	1	SENT_34	[p2l592t1035r828b1100],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l853t1035r987b1103],
5	western	JJ	O	western	amod	9	SENT_34	[p2l1015t1052r1300b1103],
6	New	NNP	MISC	New	nn	9	SENT_34	[p2l1325t992r1499b1100],
7	Brunswiclc	NNP	MISC	Brunswiclc	nn	9	SENT_34	[p2l1524t992r1926b1100],
8	470	CD	NUMBER	470	num	9	SENT_34	[p2l2019t1035r2150b1098],
9	Southern	NNP	MISC	Southern	conj_and	3	SENT_34	[p2l191t1127r538b1196],
10	extension	NN	O	extension	dep	1	SENT_34	[p2l563t1125r916b1196],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l941t1122r1021b1196],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_34	[p2l1041t1125r1158b1196],
13	Central	NNP	O	Central	nn	20	SENT_34	[p2l1180t1125r1465b1196],
14	Clastic	NNP	O	Clastic	nn	20	SENT_34	[p2l1490t1125r1744b1196],
15	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nn	20	SENT_34	[p2l1772t1125r1929b1193],
16	473	CD	NUMBER	473	num	20	SENT_34	[p2l2022t1127r2145b1193],
17	Aroostook-Matapedia	NNP	O	Aroostook-Matapedia	nn	20	SENT_34	[p2l100t1224r922b1315],
18	Carbonate	NNP	O	Carbonate	nn	20	SENT_34	[p2l950t1224r1346b1295],
19	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nn	20	SENT_34	[p2l1382t1224r1536b1293],
20	. . . .	NNP	O	. . . .	prep_of	10	SENT_34	[p2l1903t1283r1912b1293],[p2l1635t1283r1647b1292],
21	473	CD	NUMBER	473	num	23	SENT_34	[p2l2022t1224r2145b1292],
22	General	NNP	O	General	nn	23	SENT_34	[p2l191t1317r487b1388],
23	statement	NN	O	statement	dep	1	SENT_34	[p2l520t1337r893b1388],
24	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	25	SENT_34	[p2l1371t1376r1380b1385],[p2l1015t1376r1027b1388],
25	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	dep	23	SENT_34	[p2l1814t1376r1823b1388],[p2l1459t1379r1468b1388],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p2l1903t1379r1912b1388],

1	473	CD	NUMBER	473	num	4	SENT_35	[p2l2022t1320r2148b1385],
2	Carys	NNP	O	Carys	nn	4	SENT_35	[p2l188t1418r404b1504],
3	Mills	NNP	O	Mills	nn	4	SENT_35	[p2l435t1413r629b1484],
4	Formation	NN	O	formation	_	0	SENT_35	[p2l657t1416r1056b1482],
5	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	6	SENT_35	[p2l1456t1472r1468b1481],[p2l1103t1472r1112b1484],
6	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	dep	4	SENT_35	[p2l1900t1472r1912b1484],[p2l1547t1472r1556b1484],
7	474	CD	NUMBER	474	dep	4	SENT_35	[p2l2019t1416r2148b1482],

1	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	3	SENT_36	[p2l119t1728r140b1771],
2	Alphabetical	JJ	O	alphabetical	amod	3	SENT_36	[p2l168t1728r643b1822],
3	listing	NN	O	listing	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l674t1728r902b1819],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l936t1728r1013b1797],
5	authors	NNS	O	author	prep_of	3	SENT_36	[p2l1035t1731r1340b1802],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p2l1035t1731r1340b1802],

1	Unnamed	JJ	O	unnamed	amod	3	SENT_37	[p2l186t2254r552b2325],
2	ribbon	NN	O	ribbon	nn	3	SENT_37	[p2l582t2254r831b2325],
3	limestones	NNS	O	limestone	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l865t2257r1256b2325],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_37	[p2l1284t2254r1364b2322],
5	northern	JJ	O	northern	amod	6	SENT_37	[p2l1386t2254r1717b2325],
6	New	NNP	O	New	prep_of	3	SENT_37	[p2l1751t2262r1928b2325],

1	Brunswick	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brunswick	_	0	SENT_38	[p2l277t2348r680b2419],
2	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	3	SENT_38	[p2l1101t2407r1113b2416],[p2l745t2407r757b2416],
3	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	dep	1	SENT_38	[p2l1546t2407r1555b2419],[p2l1189t2407r1201b2419],
4	. . . .	NN	O	. . . .	dep	3	SENT_38	[p2l1899t2407r1911b2419],[p2l1634t2410r1646b2419],
5	475	CD	NUMBER	475	num	4	SENT_38	[p2l2019t2351r2148b2419],

1	Matapedia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Matapedia	nn	2	SENT_39	[p2l186t2445r589b2533],
2	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l639t2450r888b2536],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l936t2445r1005b2511],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_39	[p2l1061t2442r1179b2513],
5	vicinity	NN	O	vicinity	prep_in	2	SENT_39	[p2l1232t2445r1523b2533],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1574t2442r1655b2513],
7	Matapedia	NNP	LOCATION	Matapedia	prep_of	5	SENT_39	[p2l1700t2450r1925b2513, p2l275t2536r495b2630],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1700t2450r1925b2513, p2l275t2536r495b2630],

1	Quebec	NNP	O	Quebec	nn	3	SENT_40	[p2l534t2536r822b2625],
2	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	3	SENT_40	[p2l1281t2596r1293b2607],[p2l924t2596r936b2607],
3	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1725t2598r1737b2607],[p2l1372t2596r1381b2607],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1816t2598r1826b2610],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1902t2596r1914b2607],

1	475	CD	NUMBER	475	num	3	SENT_42	[p2l2022t2539r2150b2607],
2	Pabos	NNP	O	Pabos	nn	3	SENT_42	[p2l186t2633r409b2704],
3	Formation	NN	O	formation	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l440t2633r842b2701],
4	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	5	SENT_42	[p2l1278t2690r1290b2704],[p2l924t2690r936b2701],
5	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	3	SENT_42	[p2l1722t2692r1731b2701],[p2l1366t2692r1378b2701],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1811t2692r1820b2704],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1896t2692r1908b2701],

1	475	CD	NUMBER	475	num	6	SENT_44	[p2l2019t2636r2148b2701],
2	White	NNP	O	White	nn	6	SENT_44	[p2l189t2727r420b2795],
3	Head	NNP	O	Head	nn	6	SENT_44	[p2l454t2727r651b2798],
4	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	6	SENT_44	[p2l685t2727r1087b2795],
5	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	6	SENT_44	[p2l1549t2784r1558b2795],[p2l1192t2786r1201b2795],
6	. . . .	NN	O	. . . .	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1902t2784r1911b2795],[p2l1637t2786r1646b2795],
7	475	CD	NUMBER	475	dep	6	SENT_44	[p2l2022t2727r2150b2795],
8	Arisaig	NNP	O	Arisaig	nn	12	SENT_44	[p2l95t2821r358b2915],
9	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nn	12	SENT_44	[p2l394t2824r549b2892],
10	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	12	SENT_44	[p2l924t2881r936b2892],[p2l571t2881r580b2892],
11	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	12	SENT_44	[p2l1366t2881r1375b2890],[p2l1013t2881r1025b2892],
12	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	dep	7	SENT_44	[p2l1811t2881r1820b2892],[p2l1455t2881r1466b2892],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1899t2881r1908b2890],

1	477	CD	NUMBER	477	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l2019t2824r2148b2890],
2	Annapolis	NNP	LOCATION	Annapolis	nn	6	SENT_45	[p2l95t2915r475b3006],
3	Valley	NNP	LOCATION	Valley	nn	6	SENT_45	[p2l506t2915r745b3006],
4	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	nn	6	SENT_45	[p2l782t2915r936b2984],
5	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	6	SENT_45	[p2l1369t2974r1378b2983],[p2l1013t2974r1025b2984],
6	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	dep	1	SENT_45	[p2l1811t2974r1823b2984],[p2l1457t2974r1466b2986],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1899t2972r1911b2983],

1	478	CD	NUMBER	478	num	3	SENT_46	[p2l2019t2918r2145b2981],
2	Source	NN	O	source	nn	3	SENT_46	[p2l95t3017r349b3080],
3	Areas	NNS	O	area	nsubj	4	SENT_46	[p2l386t3015r594b3080],
4	. . . . .	VBP	O	. . . . .	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1013t3066r1022b3080],[p2l659t3068r671b3080],
5	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	nn	11	SENT_46	[p2l1455t3071r1466b3080],[p2l1101t3066r1113b3080],
6	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	7	SENT_46	[p2l1899t3066r1911b3077],[p2l1543t3068r1555b3080],
7	479	CD	NUMBER	479	dep	5	SENT_46	[p2l2019t3012r2148b3077],
8	Western	JJ	MISC	western	amod	11	SENT_46	[p2l186t3108r500b3174],
9	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	10	SENT_46	[p2l922t3160r933b3171],[p2l568t3162r580b3171],
10	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	dep	8	SENT_46	[p2l1366t3162r1375b3171],[p2l1013t3162r1022b3171],
11	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	dobj	4	SENT_46	[p2l1808t3162r1817b3171],[p2l1452t3162r1464b3171],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1896t3160r1908b3169],

1	479	CD	NUMBER	479	num	2	SENT_47	[p2l2016t3103r2148b3169],
2	Central	NNP	O	Central	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l183t3197r469b3268],
3	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	2	SENT_47	[p2l919t3256r931b3265],[p2l565t3256r577b3268],
4	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	5	SENT_47	[p2l1363t3256r1372b3265],[p2l1007t3256r1019b3268],
5	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	dep	2	SENT_47	[p2l1808t3256r1817b3265],[p2l1452t3256r1461b3268],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1896t3254r1908b3263],

1	480	CD	NUMBER	480	num	2	SENT_48	[p2l2016t3200r2145b3263],
2	Eastern	NNP	MISC	Eastern	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l183t3296r472b3362],
3	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	2	SENT_48	[p2l919t3348r931b3362],[p2l565t3348r577b3359],
4	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	5	SENT_48	[p2l1363t3350r1372b3359],[p2l1007t3350r1019b3359],
5	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	dep	2	SENT_48	[p2l1805t3350r1814b3359],[p2l1452t3350r1461b3359],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1896t3348r1908b3359],

1	480	CD	NUMBER	480	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l2016t3291r2148b3357],
2	Summary	NNP	O	Summary	dep	1	SENT_49	[p2l7t3390r375b3479],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l406t3388r540b3456],
4	conclusions	NNS	O	conclusion	dep	1	SENT_49	[p2l574t3385r1005b3456],
5	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	6	SENT_49	[p2l1457t3447r1466b3456],[p2l1104t3445r1113b3456],
6	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	dep	1	SENT_49	[p2l1899t3445r1908b3454],[p2l1546t3445r1555b3454],
7	480	CD	NUMBER	480	dep	6	SENT_49	[p2l2019t3388r2153b3454],
8	Addendum	NNP	MISC	Addendum	dep	1	SENT_49	[p2l10t3479r489b3550],
9	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	10	SENT_49	[p2l924t3536r933b3547],[p2l10t3479r489b3550],
10	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	11	SENT_49	[p2l1369t3536r1378b3547],[p2l1013t3538r1022b3547],
11	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	dep	8	SENT_49	[p2l1814t3536r1823b3547],[p2l1457t3538r1466b3547],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1902t3536r1911b3545],

1	431	CD	NUMBER	431	num	2	SENT_50	[p2l2022t3481r2145b3545],
2	References	NNS	O	reference	nsubj	3	SENT_50	[p2l10t3573r418b3644],
3	cited	VBD	O	cite	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l446t3538r668b3644],
4	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	5	SENT_50	[p2l1016t3632r1028b3644],[p2l446t3538r668b3644],
5	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	6	SENT_50	[p2l1455t3632r1466b3644],[p2l1104t3632r1116b3644],
6	. . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . .	dobj	3	SENT_50	[p2l1814t3632r1826b3644],[p2l1543t3632r1558b3641],
7	N	NN	O	n	prep	3	SENT_50	[p2l1902t3630r1914b3641],
8	481	CD	NUMBER	481	dep	7	SENT_50	[p2l2022t3576r2142b3641],

1	Geological	JJ	ORGANIZATION	geological	amod	2	SENT_51	[p2l459t3721r611b3756],
2	Society	NN	ORGANIZATION	society	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l625t3721r730b3757],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l744t3720r774b3747],
4	America	NNP	ORGANIZATION	America	nn	5	SENT_51	[p2l784t3721r904b3748],
5	Bulletin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bulletin	prep_of	2	SENT_51	[p2l919t3720r1044b3752],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l919t3720r1044b3752],
7	V.	NNP	O	V.	appos	5	SENT_51	[p2l1059t3731r1083b3747],
8	80	CD	NUMBER	80	num	7	SENT_51	[p2l1099t3723r1138b3752],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1099t3723r1138b3752],
10	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	5	SENT_51	[p2l1153t3731r1179b3756],
11	459-484	CD	NUMBER	459-484	num	10	SENT_51	[p2l1193t3722r1319b3752],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1193t3722r1319b3752],
13	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	14	SENT_51	[p2l1333t3722r1348b3746],
14	?gs.	NN	O	?gs.	appos	5	SENT_51	[p2l1361t3720r1425b3756],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1361t3720r1425b3756],
16	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	17	SENT_51	[p2l1444t3723r1452b3747],
17	pl.	NN	O	pl.	appos	5	SENT_51	[p2l1468t3719r1513b3755],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1468t3719r1513b3755],
19	March	NNP	DATE	March	appos	5	SENT_51	[p2l1527t3719r1621b3746],
20	1969	CD	DATE	1969	num	19	SENT_51	[p2l1639t3721r1701b3746],

1	Downloaded	VBN	O	download	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l337t17r540b46],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l553t17r625b46],
3	gsabu	FW	O	gsabu	nn	6	SENT_52	[p3l639t17r1032b53],
4	|	FW	O	|	nn	6	SENT_52	[p3l639t17r1032b53],
5	|	FW	O	|	nn	6	SENT_52	[p3l639t17r1032b53],
6	etin.gsapubs.org	FW	O	etin.gsapubs.org	prep_from	1	SENT_52	[p3l639t17r1032b53],
7	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1046t24r1084b46],
8	May	NNP	DATE	May	prep_on	6	SENT_52	[p3l1099t17r1167b53],
9	8	CD	DATE	8	num	8	SENT_52	[p3l1179t18r1206b50],
10	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_52	[p3l1179t18r1206b50],
11	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	8	SENT_52	[p3l1221t18r1301b46],

1	460	CD	NUMBER	460	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l403t65r458b95],
2	AYRTON	NNP	MISC	AYRTON	dep	1	SENT_53	[p3l533t71r678b94],
3	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l695t71r769b94],
4	OTHERS	NNS	O	other	dep	1	SENT_53	[p3l786t71r1079b95],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p3l786t71r1079b95],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l786t71r1079b95],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p3l786t71r1079b95],

1	LOWER	RBR	O	lower	advmod	2	SENT_55	[p3l786t71r1079b95],
2	LLANDOVERY	JJ	O	llandovery	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1095t71r1338b99],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l1095t71r1338b99],
4	NORTHERN	NNP	O	NORTHERN	dep	2	SENT_55	[p3l1355t71r1551b95],
5	APPALACHIANS	NNPS	O	APPALACHIANS	dep	4	SENT_55	[p3l1567t72r1822b96],

1	Figure	NN	O	figure	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l7t260r252b349],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l15t381r71b445],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l15t381r71b445],

1	Early	RB	O	early	advmod	3	SENT_58	[p3l118t373r324b462],
2	Llandovery	JJ	O	llandovery	amod	3	SENT_58	[p3l349t373r774b462],
3	paleogeography	NN	O	paleogeography	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l802t373r1380b462],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1405t376r1475b440],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_58	[p3l1502t373r1617b443],
6	northern	JJ	O	northern	prep_in	3	SENT_58	[p3l1644t373r1878b443, p3l268t492r388b534],

1	Appalachians	NNPS	MISC	Appalachians	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l418t464r905b556],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l935t467r1066b534],
3	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	amod	4	SENT_59	[p3l1099t467r1411b556],
4	regions	NNS	O	region	conj_and	1	SENT_59	[p3l1444t467r1708b556],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1766t525r1775b537],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1853t525r1861b537],

1	461	CD	NUMBER	461	num	2	SENT_61	[p3l1966t473r2084b537],
2	2	CD	NUMBER	2	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l10t566r74b631],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l10t566r74b631],

1	Outcrop	NNP	O	Outcrop	nn	2	SENT_62	[p3l123t563r438b650],
2	area	NN	O	area	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l468t583r616b628],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l643t558r724b628],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_62	[p3l746t558r861b628],
5	Cabano	NNP	O	Cabano	nn	7	SENT_62	[p3l891t558r1172b628],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	7	SENT_62	[p3l1199t561r1594b628],
7	. . .	NN	O	. . .	prep_of	2	SENT_62	[p3l1850t616r1864b631],[p3l1677t619r1689b631],
8	467	CD	NUMBER	467	number	9	SENT_62	[p3l1967t563r2095b631],
9	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	7	SENT_62	[p3l10t660r74b725],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l10t660r74b725],

1	Generalized	NNP	O	Generalized	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l123t652r563b722],
2	geologic	JJ	O	geologic	amod	3	SENT_63	[p3l602t652r902b741],
3	map	NN	O	map	dep	1	SENT_63	[p3l944t677r1102b741],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1144t655r1222b722],
5	northeast	JJ	O	northeast	prep_of	3	SENT_63	[p3l1258t655r1603b722],
6	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	Maine	dep	1	SENT_63	[p3l1647t655r1878b722],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l271t745r402b814],
8	western	JJ	O	western	amod	11	SENT_63	[p3l435t761r713b814],
9	New	NNP	O	New	nn	11	SENT_63	[p3l743t750r916b814],
10	Brunswick	NNP	O	Brunswick	nn	11	SENT_63	[p3l949t745r1342b815],
11	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	dep	1	SENT_63	[p3l1766t803r1778b814],[p3l1419t803r1433b814],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l1850t803r1864b814],

1	471	CD	NUMBER	471	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1966t748r2087b817],

1	4	LS	NUMBER	4	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l10t847r71b909],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l10t847r71b909],

1	Schematic	JJ	MISC	schematic	amod	3	SENT_66	[p3l121t836r499b906],
2	local	JJ	O	local	amod	3	SENT_66	[p3l571t836r741b906],
3	relationship	NN	O	relationship	dep	18	SENT_66	[p3l818t839r1253b928],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1327t836r1408b906],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_66	[p3l1477t836r1592b909],
6	Carys	NNP	O	Carys	nn	7	SENT_66	[p3l1666t844r1884b928],
7	Mills	NNP	O	Mills	prep_of	3	SENT_66	[p3l271t930r458b1000],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l488t930r619b1000],
9	Smyrna	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Smyrna	nn	11	SENT_66	[p3l657t935r944b1019],
10	Mills	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mills	nn	11	SENT_66	[p3l980t930r1166b1000],
11	Formations	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Formations	conj_and	3	SENT_66	[p3l1199t933r1625b1000],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1655t933r1725b997],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_66	[p3l1764t930r1878b1000],
14	Houlton-Smyrna	NNP	O	Houlton-Smyrna	nn	15	SENT_66	[p3l268t1021r900b1110],
15	Mills	NNP	O	Mills	prep_in	11	SENT_66	[p3l921t1024r1108b1094],
16	areaof	JJ	O	areaof	amod	17	SENT_66	[p3l1127t1024r1369b1091],
17	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	Maine	dep	18	SENT_66	[p3l1386t1026r1617b1091],
18	. . .	NN	O	. . .	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1850t1082r1861b1094],[p3l1677t1082r1692b1094],
19	473	CD	NUMBER	473	dep	18	SENT_66	[p3l1967t1029r2092b1094],

1	Plate	NN	O	plate	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l10t1133r196b1202],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l18t1257r68b1319],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l18t1257r68b1319],

1	Generalized	NNP	O	Generalized	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l121t1249r560b1319],
2	geologic	JJ	O	geologic	amod	3	SENT_69	[p3l616t1249r916b1338],
3	map	NN	O	map	dep	1	SENT_69	[p3l971t1277r1127b1338],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1183t1249r1261b1319],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_69	[p3l1313t1249r1425b1319],
6	Matapedia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Matapedia	nn	7	SENT_69	[p3l1486t1249r1875b1338],
7	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	prep_of	3	SENT_69	[p3l271t1348r513b1432],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l543t1343r674b1410],
9	Weir	NNP	O	Weir	nn	10	SENT_69	[p3l710t1346r891b1410],
10	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_of	3	SENT_69	[p3l924t1346r1336b1424],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l924t1346r1336b1424],
12	Gasp?	NNP	LOCATION	Gasp?	nn	15	SENT_69	[p3l1372t1343r1597b1432],
13	Peninsula	NNP	LOCATION	Peninsula	nn	15	SENT_69	[p3l1633t1346r1872b1413, p3l271t1436r410b1505],
14	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	15	SENT_69	[p3l813t1494r827b1505],[p3l468t1491r483b1505],
15	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	appos	7	SENT_69	[p3l1244t1494r1255b1505],[p3l899t1494r911b1505],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1330t1494r1342b1505],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1416t1494r1428b1505],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1486t1441r1567b1505],
2	Plate	NNP	O	Plate	nn	3	SENT_71	[p3l1600t1436r1786b1505],
3	Section	NNP	O	Section	pobj	1	SENT_71	[p3l1819t1439r2092b1505],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_72	[p3l10t1821r908b1902],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_73	[p3l112t2049r310b2136],
2	report	NN	O	report	nsubj	3	SENT_73	[p3l346t2074r616b2163],
3	represents	VBZ	O	represent	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l654t2074r1094b2161],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	5	SENT_73	[p3l1127t2085r1172b2136],
5	synthesis	NN	O	synthesis	dobj	3	SENT_73	[p3l1205t2052r1595b2163],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l1627t2049r1722b2133],
7	regional	JJ	O	regional	amod	8	SENT_73	[p3l1750t2052r2098b2161],
8	mapping	NN	O	mapping	prep_of	5	SENT_73	[p3l12t2171r396b2277],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l468t2166r627b2250],
10	paleontologic	JJ	O	paleontologic	amod	11	SENT_73	[p3l699t2166r1289b2277],
11	information	NN	O	information	conj_and	5	SENT_73	[p3l1360t2166r1884b2252],
12	obtained	VBN	O	obtain	partmod	11	SENT_73	[p3l1955t2168r2095b2250, p3l15t2282r285b2366],
13	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l346t2282r452b2394],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_73	[p3l515t2282r652b2366],
15	various	JJ	O	various	amod	16	SENT_73	[p3l710t2285r1025b2369],
16	co-authors	NNS	O	co-author	agent	12	SENT_73	[p3l1083t2282r1542b2366],
17	working	VBG	O	work	partmod	16	SENT_73	[p3l1594t2285r1959b2391],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l2014t2288r2098b2366],
19	different	JJ	O	different	amod	20	SENT_73	[p3l12t2400r391b2484],
20	parts	NNS	O	part	prep_in	17	SENT_73	[p3l449t2425r669b2511],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l724t2397r819b2484],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_73	[p3l874t2400r1011b2484],
23	northern	JJ	O	northern	amod	24	SENT_73	[p3l1071t2400r1458b2486],
24	Appalachians	NNPS	MISC	Appalachians	prep_of	20	SENT_73	[p3l1516t2400r2095b2514],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l12t2516r171b2602],
26	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	amod	27	SENT_73	[p3l224t2516r594b2627],
27	areas	NNS	O	area	prep_of	20	SENT_73	[p3l646t2546r877b2602],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p3l646t2546r877b2602],

1	Ayrton	NNP	PERSON	Ayrton	nsubj	2	SENT_74	[p3l932t2521r1255b2630],
2	mapped	VBD	O	map	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1308t2516r1653b2627],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_74	[p3l1711t2516r1845b2602],
4	Port	NNP	O	Port	nn	6	SENT_74	[p3l1897t2521r2095b2602],
5	Daniel	NNP	PERSON	Daniel	nn	6	SENT_74	[p3l12t2633r305b2719],
6	region	NN	O	region	dobj	2	SENT_74	[p3l365t2635r635b2741],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l691t2630r786b2716],
8	Gasp?	NNP	LOCATION	Gasp?	nn	9	SENT_74	[p3l832t2638r1105b2744],
9	Peninsula	NNP	LOCATION	Peninsula	prep_of	6	SENT_74	[p3l1160t2633r1583b2719],
10	under	IN	O	under	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1641t2633r1900b2716],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_74	[p3l1958t2635r2095b2719],
12	auspices	NNS	O	auspices	prep_under	2	SENT_74	[p3l10t2751r360b2862],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l393t2748r485b2831],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_74	[p3l515t2748r652b2834],
15	Quebec	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Quebec	nn	16	SENT_74	[p3l688t2748r1022b2851],
16	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_of	12	SENT_74	[p3l1055t2756r1600b2862],
17	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1633t2748r1728b2831],
18	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	19	SENT_74	[p3l1750t2751r2095b2834],
19	Resources	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Resources	prep_of	16	SENT_74	[p3l15t2873r477b2962],
20	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l15t2873r477b2962],
21	he	PRP	O	he	nsubj	22	SENT_74	[p3l518t2864r619b2951],
22	recognized	VBD	O	recognize	parataxis	2	SENT_74	[p3l660t2864r1128b2973],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_74	[p3l1169t2867r1305b2951],
24	Weir	NNP	O	Weir	nn	25	SENT_74	[p3l1344t2867r1561b2948],
25	Formation	NN	O	formation	dobj	22	SENT_74	[p3l1594t2870r2089b2962],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1594t2870r2089b2962],
27	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	28	SENT_74	[p3l12t2986r113b3065],
28	relationships	NNS	O	relationship	appos	25	SENT_74	[p3l168t2981r716b3092],
29	to	TO	O	to	infmod	28	SENT_74	[p3l771t3003r858b3065],
30	both	CC	O	both	preconj	28	SENT_74	[p3l910t2981r1114b3065],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_74	[p3l1169t2981r1305b3067],
32	overlying	JJ	O	overlying	amod	34	SENT_74	[p3l1358t2981r1775b3092],
33	Clemville	NNP	O	Clemville	nn	34	SENT_74	[p3l1825t2981r2092b3067, p3l12t3096r199b3183],
34	Formation	NN	O	formation	conj	28	SENT_74	[p3l226t3099r699b3183],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l727t3096r886b3180],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	39	SENT_74	[p3l919t3096r1058b3183],
37	underlying	VBG	O	underlie	amod	39	SENT_74	[p3l1088t3096r1567b3209],
38	Ordovician	JJ	MISC	ordovician	amod	39	SENT_74	[p3l1597t3096r2095b3183],
39	rocks	NNS	O	rock	conj	28	SENT_74	[p3l12t3214r260b3311],
40	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l12t3214r260b3311],
41	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l354t3214r513b3297],
42	found	VBD	O	find	conj_and	22	SENT_74	[p3l599t3211r858b3297],
43	fossil	NN	O	fossil	nn	44	SENT_74	[p3l944t3211r1155b3297],
44	localities	NNS	O	locality	dobj	42	SENT_74	[p3l1241t3214r1620b3297],
45	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1705t3211r1800b3297],
46	early	JJ	O	early	amod	48	SENT_74	[p3l1878t3214r2092b3328],
47	Llandovery	NNP	O	Llandovery	nn	48	SENT_74	[p3l10t3327r519b3441],
48	age	NN	O	age	prep_of	44	SENT_74	[p3l549t3360r691b3439],
49	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l718t3333r805b3411],
50	the	DT	O	the	det	51	SENT_74	[p3l838t3330r975b3416],
51	area	NN	O	area	prep_in	42	SENT_74	[p3l1002t3360r1203b3416],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p3l1002t3360r1203b3416],

1	Berry	NNP	PERSON	Berry	nsubj	8	SENT_75	[p3l1235t3335r1492b3441],
2	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	3	SENT_75	[p3l1522t3333r1583b3414],
3	responsible	JJ	O	responsible	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1613t3330r2095b3441],
4	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l10t3444r138b3530],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_75	[p3l199t3447r335b3533],
6	identi?cation	NN	O	identi?cation	prep_for	3	SENT_75	[p3l393t3444r980b3530],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1038t3444r1194b3530],
8	dating	VBG	O	date	conj_and	3	SENT_75	[p3l1255t3447r1533b3555],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1591t3444r1686b3530],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_75	[p3l1739t3447r1875b3533],
11	Ondovician	NN	MISC	ondovician	prep_of	8	SENT_75	[p3l1933t3452r2089b3533, p3l10t3564r383b3648],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l418t3561r577b3650],
13	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	14	SENT_75	[p3l616t3561r958b3648],
14	graptolites	NNS	O	graptolite	conj_and	11	SENT_75	[p3l994t3564r1461b3678],
15	referred	VBN	O	refer	partmod	14	SENT_75	[p3l1499t3564r1845b3650],
16	to	TO	O	to	xcomp	15	SENT_75	[p3l1886t3589r1973b3650],
17	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l2008t3566r2095b3648],
18	this	DT	O	this	det	19	SENT_75	[p3l18t3680r171b3764],
19	report	NN	O	report	prep_in	15	SENT_75	[p3l210t3705r502b3791],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l210t3705r502b3791],
21	unless	IN	O	unless	mark	23	SENT_75	[p3l543t3680r802b3766],
22	otherwise	RB	O	otherwise	advmod	23	SENT_75	[p3l835t3680r1253b3766],
23	noted	VBN	O	note	advcl	3	SENT_75	[p3l1288t3680r1561b3764],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p3l1288t3680r1561b3764],

1	Boucot	NNP	PERSON	Boucot	nsubj	5	SENT_76	[p3l1602t3685r1920b3764],
2	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	3	SENT_76	[p3l1958t3680r2095b3766],
3	examined	VBN	O	examine	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l12t11r427b97],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l485t11r644b94],
5	dated	VBN	O	date	conj_and	3	SENT_76	[p4l702t8r947b97],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_76	[p4l1007t11r1144b94],
7	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	9	SENT_76	[p4l1202t11r1542b94],
8	brachiopod	NN	O	brachiopod	nn	9	SENT_76	[p4l1602t11r2092b125],
9	faunas	NNS	O	fauna	dobj	3	SENT_76	[p4l10t127r307b211],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l10t127r307b211],

1	He	PRP	O	he	nsubj	2	SENT_77	[p4l368t133r496b211],
2	?rst	VBD	O	?rst	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l549t127r719b211],
3	suggested	VBD	O	suggest	ccomp	2	SENT_77	[p4l774t124r1191b236],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_77	[p4l1249t127r1386b214],
5	broad	JJ	O	broad	amod	7	SENT_77	[p4l1444t124r1689b211],
6	regional	JJ	O	regional	amod	7	SENT_77	[p4l1747t127r2095b236],
7	relationships	NNS	O	relationship	dobj	3	SENT_77	[p4l15t244r560b355],
8	presented	VBN	O	present	partmod	7	SENT_77	[p4l624t241r1047b355],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1110t246r1194b325],
10	this	DT	O	this	det	11	SENT_77	[p4l1266t244r1419b327],
11	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_in	8	SENT_77	[p4l1480t277r1750b355],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1480t277r1750b355],

1	Lajoie	NNP	PERSON	Lajoie	nsubj	2	SENT_78	[p4l1816t246r2095b355],
2	mapped	VBD	O	map	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l12t360r360b472],
3	the	DT	O	the	dep	6	SENT_78	[p4l396t363r533b444],
4	Lac	NNP	MISC	Lac	nn	6	SENT_78	[p4l560t366r722b444],
5	des	FW	MISC	des	nn	6	SENT_78	[p4l752t360r891b444],
6	Baies	NNP	MISC	Baies	dobj	2	SENT_78	[p4l919t363r1150b444],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1177t360r1336b444],
8	Lac	NNP	O	Lac	nn	10	SENT_78	[p4l1363t366r1525b444],
9	Prime	NNP	O	Prime	nn	10	SENT_78	[p4l1555t363r1825b447],
10	areas	NNS	O	area	dobj	2	SENT_78	[p4l1853t391r2089b458],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1853t391r2089b458],
12	Quebec	NNP	LOCATION	Quebec	appos	10	SENT_78	[p4l15t477r374b580],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l15t477r374b580],
14	under	IN	O	under	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l446t477r705b561],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_78	[p4l777t477r911b561],
16	auspices	NNS	O	auspices	prep_under	2	SENT_78	[p4l980t480r1330b588],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1397t477r1489b560],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_78	[p4l1552t477r1689b561],
19	Quebec	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Quebec	nn	20	SENT_78	[p4l1761t477r2095b577],
20	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_of	16	SENT_78	[p4l12t598r555b704],
21	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l591t590r683b677],
22	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	23	SENT_78	[p4l702t593r1050b677],
23	Resources	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Resources	prep_of	20	SENT_78	[p4l1083t598r1539b677],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1083t598r1539b677],

1	Lesp?rance	NNP	O	Lesp?rance	nsubj	30	SENT_79	[p4l1575t598r2089b704],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1575t598r2089b704],
3	also	RB	O	also	dep	4	SENT_79	[p4l12t709r171b793],
4	under	IN	O	under	dep	1	SENT_79	[p4l210t709r466b793],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_79	[p4l507t709r644b793],
6	auspices	NNS	O	auspices	pobj	4	SENT_79	[p4l682t712r1033b821],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1069t707r1161b793],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_79	[p4l1194t709r1333b796],
9	Quebec	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Quebec	nn	10	SENT_79	[p4l1374t709r1708b813],
10	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_of	6	SENT_79	[p4l1747t715r2092b821, p4l12t849r238b908],
11	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l304t825r399b908],
12	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	13	SENT_79	[p4l451t824r799b908],
13	Resources	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Resources	prep_of	10	SENT_79	[p4l863t830r1319b922],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l863t830r1319b922],
15	mapped	VBN	O	map	partmod	1	SENT_79	[p4l1391t822r1739b936],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1805t827r1889b905],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_79	[p4l1958t825r2098b908],
18	Cabano	NNP	O	Cabano	nn	21	SENT_79	[p4l10t941r346b1025],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l382t938r541b1025],
20	Squateck	NNP	O	Squateck	conj_and	18	SENT_79	[p4l582t941r989b1052],
21	areas	NNS	O	area	prep_in	15	SENT_79	[p4l1027t971r1261b1038],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1027t971r1261b1038],
23	Quebec	NNP	LOCATION	Quebec	appos	21	SENT_79	[p4l1308t941r1664b1041],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1308t941r1664b1041],
25	collected	VBN	O	collect	partmod	1	SENT_79	[p4l1708t938r2095b1025],
26	Cabano	NNP	LOCATION	Cabano	dobj	25	SENT_79	[p4l10t1057r344b1140],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l385t1054r544b1140],
28	Pointe	NNP	O	Pointe	nn	29	SENT_79	[p4l585t1059r875b1140],
29	Aux	NNP	O	Aux	dobj	25	SENT_79	[p4l916t1059r1100b1140],
30	Trembles	VBZ	O	tremble	_	0	SENT_79	[p4l1121t1054r1539b1140],
31	Formations	NNS	O	formation	dobj	30	SENT_79	[p4l1561t1059r2092b1143],
32	?	IN	O	?	prep	30	SENT_79	[p4l1561t1059r2092b1143],

1	fossil	JJ	O	fossil	amod	2	SENT_80	[p4l10t1170r224b1256],
2	localities	NNS	O	locality	nsubj	20	SENT_80	[p4l257t1173r658b1270],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l257t1173r658b1270],
4	and	CC	O	and	cc	5	SENT_80	[p4l696t1170r855b1256],
5	studied	VBD	O	study	dep	2	SENT_80	[p4l888t1170r1208b1256],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_80	[p4l1244t1170r1383b1256],
7	trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	dobj	5	SENT_80	[p4l1419t1173r1809b1256],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l1839t1170r1934b1256],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_80	[p4l1961t1173r2098b1256],
10	White	NNP	O	White	nn	11	SENT_80	[p4l10t1289r285b1372],
11	Head	NNP	O	Head	prep_of	7	SENT_80	[p4l338t1286r597b1386],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l338t1286r597b1386],
13	Weir	NNP	PERSON	Weir	prep_of	7	SENT_80	[p4l652t1291r894b1386],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l652t1291r894b1386],
15	Cabano	NNP	O	Cabano	prep_of	7	SENT_80	[p4l949t1286r1305b1383],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l949t1286r1305b1383],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l1361t1286r1519b1372],
18	Pointe	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Pointe	nn	19	SENT_80	[p4l1572t1291r1861b1372],
19	Aux	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Aux	prep_of	7	SENT_80	[p4l1914t1291r2098b1372],
20	Trembles	VBZ	ORGANIZATION	tremble	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l7t1405r427b1488],
21	Formations	NNS	ORGANIZATION	formation	dobj	20	SENT_80	[p4l465t1405r1002b1502],
22	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l465t1405r1002b1502],
23	he	PRP	O	he	nsubj	25	SENT_80	[p4l1049t1405r1150b1488],
24	also	RB	O	also	advmod	25	SENT_80	[p4l1191t1402r1353b1488],
25	collected	VBD	O	collect	parataxis	20	SENT_80	[p4l1394t1402r1781b1488],
26	faunas	NNS	O	fauna	dobj	25	SENT_80	[p4l1822t1402r2098b1488],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l12t1523r96b1601],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_80	[p4l160t1521r296b1604],
29	White	NNP	O	White	nn	31	SENT_80	[p4l354t1521r630b1604],
30	Head	NNP	O	Head	nn	31	SENT_80	[p4l685t1521r919b1604],
31	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_in	25	SENT_80	[p4l977t1523r1450b1604],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_80	[p4l1508t1518r1603b1604],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	34	SENT_80	[p4l1655t1521r1792b1604],
34	Perc?	NNP	O	Perc?	prep_of	31	SENT_80	[p4l1853t1523r2098b1604],

1	area	NN	O	area	_	0	SENT_81	[p4l12t1667r210b1720],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p4l12t1667r210b1720],

1	Pavlides	NNP	PERSON	Pavlides	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l265t1634r652b1731],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l265t1634r652b1731],
3	under	IN	O	under	dep	1	SENT_82	[p4l704t1634r963b1718],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_82	[p4l1010t1634r1147b1717],
5	auspices	NNS	O	auspices	pobj	3	SENT_82	[p4l1191t1639r1544b1745],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l1586t1634r1681b1718],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_82	[p4l1722t1637r1859b1720],
8	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	U.S.	nn	10	SENT_82	[p4l1900t1639r2092b1718],
9	Geological	NNP	O	Geological	nn	10	SENT_82	[p4l12t1750r477b1861],
10	Survey	NNP	O	Survey	prep_of	5	SENT_82	[p4l527t1750r911b1861],
11	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_82	[p4l527t1750r911b1861],

1	mapped	VBN	O	map	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l957t1747r1308b1861],
2	most	JJS	O	most	dobj	1	SENT_83	[p4l1358t1772r1567b1833],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l1616t1750r1711b1833],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_83	[p4l1755t1750r1892b1833],
5	terrane	NN	O	terrane	prep_of	2	SENT_83	[p4l1944t1772r2095b1833, p4l15t1895r199b1951],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l263t1865r358b1949],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_83	[p4l415t1865r552b1949],
8	Aroostook-Matapedia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Aroostook-Matapedia	nn	10	SENT_83	[p4l613t1865r1578b1976],
9	Carbonate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Carbonate	nn	10	SENT_83	[p4l1639t1865r2098b1951],
10	Belt	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Belt	prep_of	5	SENT_83	[p4l12t1984r199b2065],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l254t1986r338b2064],
12	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	Maine	prep_in	1	SENT_83	[p4l393t1984r697b2078],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l393t1984r697b2078],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l757t1981r916b2065],
15	remapped	VBD	O	remap	conj_and	1	SENT_83	[p4l974t1981r1428b2092],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l974t1981r1428b2092],
17	as	RB	O	as	advmod	18	SENT_83	[p4l1488t2014r1567b2064],
18	well	RB	O	well	dep	20	SENT_83	[p4l1619t1981r1797b2065],
19	as	IN	O	as	mwe	18	SENT_83	[p4l1850t2014r1928b2067],
20	reconnoitered	JJ	O	reconnoitered	ccomp	15	SENT_83	[p4l1986t2011r2095b2064, p4l12t2096r560b2193],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l1986t2011r2095b2064, p4l12t2096r560b2193],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_83	[p4l610t2096r747b2179],
23	strata	NN	O	stratum	npadvmod	20	SENT_83	[p4l788t2121r1033b2182],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l1071t2096r1166b2179],
25	this	DT	O	this	det	26	SENT_83	[p4l1202t2099r1355b2179],
26	belt	NN	O	belt	prep_of	20	SENT_83	[p4l1397t2096r1564b2179],
27	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l1605t2098r1686b2177],
28	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	amod	30	SENT_83	[p4l1727t2096r2098b2204],
29	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	30	SENT_83	[p4l10t2217r219b2295],
30	Brunswick	NNP	LOCATION	Brunswick	prep_in	26	SENT_83	[p4l268t2214r763b2295],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p4l268t2214r763b2295],

1	He	PRP	O	he	nsubj	3	SENT_84	[p4l818t2217r950b2295],
2	also	RB	O	also	advmod	3	SENT_84	[p4l999t2212r1158b2295],
3	mapped	VBD	O	map	_	0	SENT_84	[p4l1210t2212r1556b2323],
4	portions	NNS	O	portion	dobj	3	SENT_84	[p4l1605t2214r1967b2323],
5	of	IN	O	of	prep	4	SENT_84	[p4l2017t2209r2112b2293],

1	2The	JJ	O	2the	amod	3	SENT_85	[p4l104t2495r299b2562],
2	geologic	JJ	O	geologic	amod	3	SENT_85	[p4l349t2495r644b2584],
3	names	NNS	O	name	nsubj	20	SENT_85	[p4l693t2520r919b2562],
4	used	VBN	O	use	partmod	3	SENT_85	[p4l966t2495r1128b2562],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1174t2498r1244b2562],
6	this	DT	O	this	det	7	SENT_85	[p4l1294t2495r1428b2562],
7	report	NN	O	report	prep_in	4	SENT_85	[p4l1475t2514r1700b2584],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1750t2495r1817b2562],
9	northeastern	JJ	O	northeastern	amod	11	SENT_85	[p4l1866t2495r2098b2562, p4l10t2616r269b2667],
10	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	11	SENT_85	[p4l301t2600r560b2667],
11	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	prep_in	7	SENT_85	[p4l596t2605r819b2667],
12	are	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l846t2622r952b2664],
13	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l985t2597r1161b2664],
14	various	JJ	O	various	amod	15	SENT_85	[p4l1194t2600r1458b2664],
15	sources	NNS	O	source	prep_from	12	SENT_85	[p4l1488t2622r1750b2667],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1777t2597r1909b2664],
17	may	MD	O	may	aux	20	SENT_85	[p4l1944t2622r2100b2683],
18	not	RB	O	not	neg	20	SENT_85	[p4l12t2721r135b2769],
19	necessarily	RB	O	necessarily	advmod	20	SENT_85	[p4l196t2702r585b2788],
20	follow	VB	O	follow	conj_and	12	SENT_85	[p4l646t2699r869b2769],
21	usage	NN	O	usage	dobj	20	SENT_85	[p4l927t2727r1125b2788],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1185t2699r1264b2769],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_85	[p4l1319t2702r1431b2769],
24	US	NNP	LOCATION	US	prep_of	21	SENT_85	[p4l1491t2707r1653b2772],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p4l1491t2707r1653b2772],

1	Geological	JJ	O	geological	amod	2	SENT_86	[p4l1716t2702r2100b2785],
2	Survey	NN	O	survey	_	0	SENT_86	[p4l10t2812r291b2893],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_86	[p4l10t2812r291b2893],

1	Table	NNP	O	Table	_	0	SENT_87	[p4l86t2941r293b3013],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_88	[p4l94t3063r147b3124],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_88	[p4l94t3063r147b3124],

1	Correlation	NN	O	correlation	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l193t3055r612b3124],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l669t3055r747b3121],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_89	[p4l802t3055r912b3121],
4	standard	JJ	O	standard	amod	5	SENT_89	[p4l972t3055r1284b3124],
5	section	NN	O	section	prep_of	1	SENT_89	[p4l1344t3057r1598b3124],
6	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l1655t3052r1760b3121],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_89	[p4l1821t3055r1931b3124],
8	Lower	JJR	MISC	lower	amod	11	SENT_89	[p4l344t3153r574b3214],
9	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	11	SENT_89	[p4l617t3145r896b3214],
10	(	NN	O	(	nn	11	SENT_89	[p4l942t3145r1424b3236],
11	Llandovery	NN	O	llandovery	nn	12	SENT_89	[p4l942t3145r1424b3236],
12	)	NN	O	)	prep_for	5	SENT_89	[p4l942t3145r1424b3236],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l1474t3147r1634b3214],
14	respect	NN	O	respect	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l1680t3167r1934b3236],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l347t3260r417b3310],
16	graptolite	NN	O	graptolite	nn	17	SENT_89	[p4l444t3241r799b3329],
17	zonation	NN	O	zonation	prep_with_respect_to	12	SENT_89	[p4l829t3244r1144b3310],
18	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	19	SENT_89	[p4l1564t3301r1573b3313],[p4l1220t3299r1234b3313],
19	. . . .	NN	O	. . . .	dep	1	SENT_89	[p4l1903t3301r1915b3313],[p4l1647t3301r1659b3313],
20	463	CD	NUMBER	463	number	21	SENT_89	[p4l2019t3249r2140b3313],
21	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	19	SENT_89	[p4l88t3342r149b3406],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_89	[p4l88t3342r149b3406],

1	Fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_90	[p4l196t3334r433b3403],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_90	[p4l457t3334r634b3401],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_90	[p4l667t3337r777b3403],
4	Weir	NNP	O	Weir	nn	6	SENT_90	[p4l810t3337r987b3401],
5	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	6	SENT_90	[p4l1016t3337r1402b3401],
6	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	prep_from	1	SENT_90	[p4l1818t3392r1829b3406],[p4l1476t3392r1491b3403],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_90	[p4l1903t3392r1915b3406],

1	465	CD	NUMBER	465	num	2	SENT_91	[p4l2019t3342r2143b3406],
2	3	CD	NUMBER	3	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l88t3433r149b3500],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p4l88t3433r149b3500],

1	Brachiopods	NNS	MISC	brachiopod	_	0	SENT_92	[p4l198t3425r648b3513],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_92	[p4l683t3425r857b3494],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_92	[p4l898t3428r1009b3494],
4	Clemville	NNP	O	Clemville	nn	5	SENT_92	[p4l1047t3427r1397b3494],
5	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	1	SENT_92	[p4l1438t3430r1824b3494],
6	of	IN	O	of	prep	1	SENT_92	[p4l1862t3425r1937b3494],

1	Badgley	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Badgley	nn	4	SENT_93	[p4l344t3518r640b3606],
2	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	4	SENT_93	[p4l1049t3576r1061b3587],[p4l708t3576r722b3587],
3	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	nn	4	SENT_93	[p4l1476t3575r1488b3587],[p4l1135t3576r1146b3587],
4	. . . . .	NNP	O	. . . . .	_	0	SENT_93	[p4l1903t3578r1915b3587],[p4l1559t3578r1570b3587],
5	466	CD	NUMBER	466	number	6	SENT_93	[p4l2019t3523r2143b3590],
6	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	4	SENT_93	[p4l88t3621r149b3682],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_93	[p4l88t3621r149b3682],

1	Fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_94	[p4l196t3612r430b3682],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_94	[p4l455t3610r631b3679],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_94	[p4l661t3612r775b3679],
4	Cabano	NNP	O	Cabano	nn	6	SENT_94	[p4l804t3612r1080b3679],
5	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	6	SENT_94	[p4l1110t3615r1499b3679],
6	. . . . .	NN	O	. . . . .	prep_from	1	SENT_94	[p4l1903t3670r1917b3684],[p4l1562t3670r1573b3682],
7	469	CD	NUMBER	469	dep	1	SENT_94	[p4l2019t3621r2146b3682],

1	5	CD	NUMBER	5	_	0	SENT_95	[p5l88t22r147b89],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_95	[p5l88t22r147b89],

1	Fossils	NNS	O	fossil	_	0	SENT_96	[p5l196t20r430b86],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_96	[p5l449t17r626b86],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_96	[p5l650t20r761b86],
4	Llandoverian	JJ	MISC	llandoverian	amod	5	SENT_96	[p5l788t17r1268b86],
5	part	NN	O	part	prep_from	1	SENT_96	[p5l1295t36r1441b105],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p5l1465t17r1543b86],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_96	[p5l1562t17r1672b86],
8	White	NNP	O	White	prep_of	1	SENT_96	[p5l1699t19r1923b86],

1	Head	NNP	O	Head	nn	2	SENT_97	[p5l344t110r535b179],
2	Formation	NN	O	formation	_	0	SENT_97	[p5l565t113r948b179],
3	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	number	4	SENT_97	[p5l1385t168r1400b179],[p5l1047t168r1058b179],
4	. . . . .	CD	NUMBER	. . . . .	num	2	SENT_97	[p5l1815t168r1827b179],[p5l1474t168r1485b179],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_97	[p5l1900t168r1912b182],

1	478	CD	NUMBER	478	_	0	SENT_98	[p5l2019t115r2140b182],

1	6	CD	NUMBER	6	_	0	SENT_99	[p5l88t208r152b275],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_99	[p5l88t208r152b275],

1	Brachiopods	NNS	MISC	brachiopod	dep	2	SENT_100	[p5l198t205r648b291],
2	useful	JJ	O	useful	_	0	SENT_100	[p5l683t203r896b272],
3	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_100	[p5l931t203r1036b272],
4	dating	VBG	O	date	prepc_for	2	SENT_100	[p5l1071t205r1303b294],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_100	[p5l1344t205r1458b272],
6	lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	7	SENT_100	[p5l1496t206r1694b272],
7	Llandovery	NN	O	llandovery	dobj	4	SENT_100	[p5l1732t205r1926b272, p5l342t296r596b384],

1	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_101	[p5l617t299r686b362],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_101	[p5l713t298r824b365],
3	northern	JJ	O	northern	amod	4	SENT_101	[p5l848t298r1168b365],
4	Appalachians	NNPS	MISC	Appalachians	prep_in	5	SENT_101	[p5l1193t298r1675b387],
5	. . .	VBP	O	. . .	_	0	SENT_101	[p5l1903t356r1915b365],[p5l1732t356r1741b365],
6	481	CD	NUMBER	481	nsubj	5	SENT_101	[p5l2019t301r2135b365],

1	the	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_102	[p5l102t751r238b837],
2	Central	NNP	O	Central	nsubj	17	SENT_102	[p5l273t754r601b837],
3	Clastic	NNP	O	Clastic	nn	4	SENT_102	[p5l636t754r929b839],
4	Belt	NNP	O	Belt	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l964t753r1152b837],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l1187t756r1267b834],
6	Aroostook	NNP	LOCATION	Aroostook	nn	7	SENT_102	[p5l1303t756r1755b839],
7	County	NNP	LOCATION	County	prep_in	4	SENT_102	[p5l1787t759r2146b864],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l1787t759r2146b864],
9	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	Maine	prep_in	4	SENT_102	[p5l97t871r397b965],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l97t871r397b965],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l477t869r634b952],
12	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	amod	14	SENT_102	[p5l708t869r1075b979],
13	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	14	SENT_102	[p5l1149t874r1353b954],
14	Brunswick	NNP	LOCATION	Brunswick	prep_in	4	SENT_102	[p5l1427t872r1915b965],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l1427t872r1915b965],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l1994t869r2152b952],
17	found	VBD	O	find	conj_and	4	SENT_102	[p5l94t981r350b1064],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_102	[p5l402t983r535b1067],
19	fossil	NN	O	fossil	nn	20	SENT_102	[p5l581t984r794b1067],
20	localities	NNS	O	locality	dobj	17	SENT_102	[p5l837t984r1210b1067],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l1256t983r1350b1067],
22	early	JJ	O	early	amod	24	SENT_102	[p5l1385t984r1598b1094],
23	Llandovery	NNP	O	Llandovery	nn	24	SENT_102	[p5l1644t984r2149b1094],
24	age	NN	O	age	prep_of	17	SENT_102	[p5l94t1129r235b1204],
25	in	IN	O	in	prep	17	SENT_102	[p5l311t1101r395b1179],
26	both	CC	O	both	dep	25	SENT_102	[p5l474t1096r675b1179],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_102	[p5l758t1098r890b1182],
28	Aroostook	NNP	LOCATION	Aroostook	conj	25	SENT_102	[p5l967t1098r1917b1209],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_102	[p5l967t1098r1917b1209],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_103	[p5l967t1098r1917b1209],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_103	[p5l967t1098r1917b1209],

1	Matapedia	NNP	LOCATION	Matapedia	nn	5	SENT_104	[p5l967t1098r1917b1209],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l1994t1099r2149b1182],
3	Central	NNP	O	Central	conj_and	1	SENT_104	[p5l91t1211r422b1294],
4	Clastic	NNP	O	Clastic	nn	5	SENT_104	[p5l485t1211r780b1297],
5	Belts	NNP	O	Belts	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l843t1213r1064b1297],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l1127t1211r1221b1294],
7	Aroostook	NNP	LOCATION	Aroostook	nn	8	SENT_104	[p5l1275t1216r1722b1297],
8	County	NNP	LOCATION	County	prep_of	5	SENT_104	[p5l1787t1219r2143b1324],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l1787t1219r2143b1324],
10	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	Maine	prep_of	5	SENT_104	[p5l91t1328r392b1423],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l91t1328r392b1423],
12	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l457t1326r612b1411],
13	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	advmod	8	SENT_104	[p5l675t1326r1039b1436],
14	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	15	SENT_104	[p5l1099t1331r1306b1412],
15	Brunswick	NNP	LOCATION	Brunswick	prep_of	5	SENT_104	[p5l1363t1329r1849b1412],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_104	[p5l1363t1329r1849b1412],

1	Skidrnore	NNP	PERSON	Skidrnore	nsubj	2	SENT_105	[p5l1917t1328r2146b1411, p5l91t1475r312b1528],
2	mapped	VBD	O	map	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l364t1442r706b1555],
3	various	JJ	O	various	amod	4	SENT_105	[p5l760t1444r1069b1528],
4	segments	NNS	O	segment	dobj	2	SENT_105	[p5l1118t1467r1510b1555],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l1559t1442r1650b1528],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_105	[p5l1697t1444r1832b1528],
7	Matapedia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Matapedia	nn	9	SENT_105	[p5l1884t1447r2146b1528, p5l88t1558r320b1668],
8	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	9	SENT_105	[p5l400t1563r686b1671],
9	limestones	NNS	O	limestone	prep_of	4	SENT_105	[p5l766t1560r1212b1644],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l1289t1558r1380b1644],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_105	[p5l1454t1560r1590b1644],
12	Aroostook	NNP	O	Aroostook	nn	15	SENT_105	[p5l1664t1563r2146b1644],
13	?	NNP	O	?	nn	15	SENT_105	[p5l1664t1563r2146b1644],
14	Matapedia	NNP	LOCATION	Matapedia	nn	15	SENT_105	[p5l88t1674r557b1787],
15	Belt	NNP	LOCATION	Belt	prep_of	9	SENT_105	[p5l603t1676r788b1760],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l840t1679r923b1760],
17	eastern	JJ	O	eastern	prep_in	2	SENT_105	[p5l975t1701r1276b1760],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l1328t1674r1482b1760],
19	central	JJ	O	central	amod	20	SENT_105	[p5l1537t1677r1835b1762],
20	Gasp?	NNP	O	Gasp?	prep_in	2	SENT_105	[p5l1884t1679r2151b1787],
21	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l88t1789r213b1872],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_105	[p5l317t1792r452b1875],
23	Quebec	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Quebec	nn	24	SENT_105	[p5l557t1792r887b1891],
24	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Department	prep_for	2	SENT_105	[p5l989t1797r1526b1902],
25	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l1628t1792r1722b1875],
26	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	27	SENT_105	[p5l1810t1791r2151b1875],
27	Resources	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Resources	prep_of	24	SENT_105	[p5l88t1912r538b1989],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_105	[p5l88t1912r538b1989],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_106	[p5l188t2018r367b2103],
2	?nal	JJ	O	?nal	amod	3	SENT_106	[p5l411t2018r598b2103],
3	synthesis	NN	O	synthesis	nsubj	13	SENT_106	[p5l642t2020r1028b2132],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_106	[p5l1071t2018r1226b2103],
5	regional	JJ	O	regional	amod	6	SENT_106	[p5l1275t2021r1617b2130],
6	conclusions	NNS	O	conclusion	conj_and	3	SENT_106	[p5l1664t2018r2149b2103],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_106	[p5l88t2135r180b2218],
8	this	DT	O	this	det	9	SENT_106	[p5l212t2135r364b2218],
9	report	NN	O	report	prep_of	6	SENT_106	[p5l405t2160r673b2248],
10	are	VBP	O	be	cop	13	SENT_106	[p5l713t2168r841b2221],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_106	[p5l884t2137r1017b2221],
12	joint	JJ	O	joint	amod	13	SENT_106	[p5l1055t2140r1265b2245],
13	responsibility	NN	O	responsibility	_	0	SENT_106	[p5l1306t2138r1887b2248],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_106	[p5l1925t2135r2019b2218],
15	all	PDT	O	all	predet	17	SENT_106	[p5l2049t2135r2152b2221],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_106	[p5l94t2250r227b2334],
17	co-authors	NNS	O	co-author	prep_of	13	SENT_106	[p5l267t2250r739b2336],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_106	[p5l267t2250r739b2336],

1	ACKNOWLEDGMENTS	NNS	O	acknowledgment	_	0	SENT_107	[p5l86t2437r1295b2520],

1	Certain	JJ	O	certain	amod	2	SENT_108	[p5l190t2599r518b2680],
2	sections	NNS	O	section	nsubjpass	26	SENT_108	[p5l557t2599r890b2680],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_108	[p5l926t2594r1020b2680],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_108	[p5l1049t2596r1185b2682],
5	unpublished	JJ	O	unpublished	amod	7	SENT_108	[p5l1223t2594r1755b2707],
6	doctoral	JJ	O	doctoral	amod	7	SENT_108	[p5l1793t2596r2151b2680],
7	dissertations	NNS	O	dissertation	prep_of	2	SENT_108	[p5l88t2709r623b2795],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_108	[p5l658t2709r750b2792],
9	Ayrton	NNP	LOCATION	Ayrton	nn	15	SENT_108	[p5l774t2717r1089b2819],
10	(	NNP	O	(	nn	15	SENT_108	[p5l1132t2712r1771b2819],
11	Northwestern	NNP	O	Northwestern	nn	15	SENT_108	[p5l1132t2712r1771b2819],
12	Univer	NNP	O	Univer	nn	15	SENT_108	[p5l1804t2714r2143b2792],
13	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	15	SENT_108	[p5l1804t2714r2143b2792],
14	sity	NN	O	sity	nn	15	SENT_108	[p5l88t2824r309b2937],
15	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	7	SENT_108	[p5l88t2824r309b2937],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p5l88t2824r309b2937],
17	Lajoie	NNP	PERSON	Lajoie	conj_and	15	SENT_108	[p5l358t2827r631b2935],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_108	[p5l678t2824r832b2910],
19	Lesp?rance	NNP	O	Lesp?rance	nn	22	SENT_108	[p5l879t2829r1361b2937],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	22	SENT_108	[p5l1410t2826r1763b2934],
21	McGill	NNP	ORGANIZATION	McGill	nn	22	SENT_108	[p5l1410t2826r1763b2934],
22	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	conj_and	15	SENT_108	[p5l1807t2829r2146b2910, p5l88t2941r276b3052],
23	)	NN	O	)	dep	22	SENT_108	[p5l1807t2829r2146b2910, p5l88t2941r276b3052],
24	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	26	SENT_108	[p5l320t2972r450b3025],
25	herein	RB	O	herein	advmod	26	SENT_108	[p5l485t2942r755b3025],
26	incorporated	VBN	O	incorporate	_	0	SENT_108	[p5l791t2939r1367b3052],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_108	[p5l791t2939r1367b3052],

1	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	4	SENT_109	[p5l1407t2942r1791b3025],
2	Science	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Science	nn	4	SENT_109	[p5l1826t2944r2149b3025],
3	Foundation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Foundation	nn	4	SENT_109	[p5l88t3054r601b3140],
4	grants	NNS	O	grant	nsubjpass	23	SENT_109	[p5l647t3079r915b3164],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l964t3079r1050b3140],
6	Berry	NNP	PERSON	Berry	prep_to	4	SENT_109	[p5l1096t3062r1347b3167],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l1396t3054r1551b3140],
8	Boucot	NNP	PERSON	Boucot	prep_to	4	SENT_109	[p5l1600t3062r1939b3151],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l1600t3062r1939b3151],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l1991t3054r2146b3137],
11	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	13	SENT_109	[p5l86t3171r469b3256],
12	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	nn	13	SENT_109	[p5l504t3171r893b3256],
13	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Council	conj_and	4	SENT_109	[p5l923t3171r1265b3254],
14	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l1295t3171r1386b3254],
15	Canada	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Canada	nn	16	SENT_109	[p5l1407t3171r1733b3256],
16	grants	NNS	O	grant	prep_of	13	SENT_109	[p5l1760t3195r2028b3278],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l2068t3195r2151b3254],
18	Lajoie	NNP	PERSON	Lajoie	prep_to	16	SENT_109	[p5l88t3286r362b3393],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l402t3283r560b3366],
20	Lesp?rance	NNP	O	Lesp?rance	prep_to	16	SENT_109	[p5l601t3288r1080b3393],
21	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	23	SENT_109	[p5l1121t3316r1248b3369],
22	gratefully	RB	O	gratefully	advmod	23	SENT_109	[p5l1289t3283r1714b3393],
23	acknowledged	VBN	O	acknowledge	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l1754t3283r2146b3366, p5l91t3397r364b3504],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_109	[p5l1754t3283r2146b3366, p5l91t3397r364b3504],

1	Iacques	NNP	O	Iacques	nn	6	SENT_110	[p5l196t3518r518b3625],
2	B?land	NNP	O	B?land	nn	6	SENT_110	[p5l590t3515r896b3598],
3	(	NNP	O	(	nn	6	SENT_110	[p5l972t3517r1458b3625],
4	Universit?	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Universit?	nn	6	SENT_110	[p5l972t3517r1458b3625],
5	de	IN	ORGANIZATION	de	amod	6	SENT_110	[p5l1531t3515r1631b3598],
6	Montreal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Montreal	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l1705t3515r2143b3623],
7	)	NNP	O	)	nn	11	SENT_110	[p5l1705t3515r2143b3623],
8	Hugo	NNP	PERSON	Hugo	nn	11	SENT_110	[p5l88t3632r334b3737],
9	Greiner	NNP	PERSON	Greiner	nn	11	SENT_110	[p5l366t3632r706b3713],
10	(	NNP	O	(	nn	11	SENT_110	[p5l741t3632r1237b3740],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	dep	6	SENT_110	[p5l741t3632r1237b3740],
12	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l1270t3627r1361b3713],
13	New	NNP	ORGANIZATION	New	nn	15	SENT_110	[p5l1383t3635r1590b3713],
14	Brunswick	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Brunswick	nn	15	SENT_110	[p5l1619t3629r2146b3738],
15	)	NN	O	)	prep_of	11	SENT_110	[p5l1619t3629r2146b3738],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p5l1619t3629r2146b3738],

1	and	CC	O	and	dep	6	SENT_111	[p6l88t8r246b94],
2	Ely	NNP	PERSON	Ely	nn	6	SENT_111	[p6l281t11r439b121],
3	Mencher	NNP	PERSON	Mencher	nn	6	SENT_111	[p6l477t11r868b94],
4	(	NNP	O	(	nn	6	SENT_111	[p6l906t10r1135b121],
5	City	NNP	ORGANIZATION	City	nn	6	SENT_111	[p6l906t10r1135b121],
6	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	College	_	0	SENT_111	[p6l1171t10r1493b119],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_111	[p6l1529t8r1620b91],
8	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	10	SENT_111	[p6l1644t16r1854b94],
9	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	nn	10	SENT_111	[p6l1887t13r2143b119],
10	)	NN	O	)	npadvmod	12	SENT_111	[p6l1887t13r2143b119],
11	kindly	RB	O	kindly	advmod	10	SENT_111	[p6l91t125r370b236],
12	furnished	JJ	O	furnished	amod	14	SENT_111	[p6l457t125r863b211],
13	unpublished	JJ	O	unpublished	amod	14	SENT_111	[p6l950t123r1480b236],
14	data	NNS	O	datum	prep_of	6	SENT_111	[p6l1567t123r1752b209],
15	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_111	[p6l1840t148r1926b209],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_111	[p6l2013t126r2149b209],
17	writers	NNS	O	writer	prep_to	6	SENT_111	[p6l91t243r411b323],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_111	[p6l91t243r411b323],

1	LITHOFACIES	NNPS	O	LITHOFACIES	_	0	SENT_112	[p6l88t474r824b554],
2	AND	CC	O	and	cc	3	SENT_112	[p6l879t474r1124b552],
3	PALEOGEOGRAPHY	NN	O	paleogeography	dep	1	SENT_112	[p6l94t587r1174b667],

1	Carbonate	NNP	O	Carbonate	nn	2	SENT_113	[p6l99t771r521b851],
2	Rock	NNP	O	Rock	_	0	SENT_113	[p6l551t771r797b876],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_113	[p6l551t771r797b876],
4	of	IN	O	of	dep	2	SENT_113	[p6l829t771r932b876],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_113	[p6l945t771r1066b849],
6	Pfagform	NN	O	pfagform	pobj	4	SENT_113	[p6l1099t771r1458b876],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_114	[p6l193t901r370b987],
2	early	JJ	O	early	amod	6	SENT_114	[p6l427t901r637b1011],
3	Llandovery	NNP	O	Llandovery	nn	6	SENT_114	[p6l691t901r1196b1011],
4	age	NN	O	age	nn	6	SENT_114	[p6l1251t934r1394b1011],
5	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	6	SENT_114	[p6l1452t904r1873b987],
6	rocks	NNS	O	rock	nsubjpass	16	SENT_114	[p6l1931t904r2154b984],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_114	[p6l97t1013r188b1099],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_114	[p6l243t1016r378b1101],
9	North	JJ	MISC	north	amod	11	SENT_114	[p6l438t1016r711b1099],
10	American	JJ	MISC	american	amod	11	SENT_114	[p6l771t1018r1188b1099],
11	platform	NN	O	platform	prep_of	6	SENT_114	[p6l1248t1015r1626b1126],
12	have	VBP	O	have	aux	16	SENT_114	[p6l1688t1015r1890b1099],
13	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_114	[p6l1953t1016r2149b1099],
14	most	RBS	O	most	advmod	15	SENT_114	[p6l97t1155r304b1214],
15	recently	RB	DATE	recently	advmod	16	SENT_114	[p6l353t1131r703b1238],
16	discussed	VBN	O	discuss	_	0	SENT_114	[p6l749t1128r1138b1214],
17	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_114	[p6l1187t1130r1292b1238],
18	Berry	NNP	PERSON	Berry	agent	16	SENT_114	[p6l1339t1136r1590b1238],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_114	[p6l1636t1128r1791b1214],
20	Boucot	NNP	PERSON	Boucot	agent	16	SENT_114	[p6l1837t1136r2152b1211],
21	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_114	[p6l102t1246r218b1350],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_114	[p6l102t1246r218b1350],
23	press	NN	O	press	nn	24	SENT_114	[p6l267t1243r535b1353],
24	)	NN	O	)	prep_in	16	SENT_114	[p6l267t1243r535b1353],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_114	[p6l267t1243r535b1353],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_115	[p6l587t1243r764b1329],
2	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	3	SENT_115	[p6l813t1243r1234b1329],
3	rocks	NNS	O	rock	nsubj	11	SENT_115	[p6l1286t1245r1507b1326],
4	closest	JJS	O	closest	advmod	3	SENT_115	[p6l1556t1243r1829b1326],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_115	[p6l1881t1268r1967b1326],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_115	[p6l2019t1243r2152b1326],
7	Appalachian	NNP	MISC	Appalachian	nn	8	SENT_115	[p6l97t1359r637b1469],
8	Region	NNP	MISC	Region	prep_to	4	SENT_115	[p6l722t1361r1031b1467],
9	are	VBP	O	be	cop	11	SENT_115	[p6l1116t1392r1243b1442],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_115	[p6l1333t1359r1469b1442],
11	exposures	NNS	O	exposure	_	0	SENT_115	[p6l1553t1389r1964b1469],
12	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_115	[p6l2049t1389r2154b1439],
13	Anticosti	NNP	LOCATION	Anticosti	nn	16	SENT_115	[p6l99t1477r496b1555],
14	Island	NNP	LOCATION	Island	nn	16	SENT_115	[p6l551t1472r810b1555],
15	(	NNP	O	(	nn	16	SENT_115	[p6l873t1474r1080b1579],
16	area	NN	O	area	prep_on	11	SENT_115	[p6l873t1474r1080b1579],
17	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	16	SENT_115	[p6l1146t1477r1207b1568],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_115	[p6l1146t1477r1207b1568],
19	Fig	NN	O	fig	appos	16	SENT_115	[p6l1267t1477r1435b1579],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_115	[p6l1267t1477r1435b1579],

1	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	2	SENT_116	[p6l1507t1474r1576b1579],
2	)	NN	O	)	nn	18	SENT_116	[p6l1507t1474r1576b1579],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l1642t1472r1796b1555],
4	on	IN	O	on	conj_and	2	SENT_116	[p6l1854t1505r1959b1552],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_116	[p6l2022t1472r2154b1555],
6	northeast	JJ	O	northeast	amod	7	SENT_116	[p6l105t1587r510b1670],
7	side	NN	O	side	pobj	4	SENT_116	[p6l598t1587r761b1670],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l848t1587r943b1667],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_116	[p6l1025t1587r1160b1670],
10	Michigan	NNP	LOCATION	Michigan	nn	11	SENT_116	[p6l1250t1587r1661b1692],
11	Basin	NNP	LOCATION	Basin	prep_of	7	SENT_116	[p6l1749t1590r1986b1667],
12	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l2077t1590r2154b1665],
13	Ontario	NNP	LOCATION	Ontario	prep_in	11	SENT_116	[p6l105t1705r450b1786],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l501t1700r656b1783],
15	adjacent	JJ	O	adjacent	amod	17	SENT_116	[p6l708t1700r1072b1810],
16	Michigan	NNP	LOCATION	Michigan	nn	17	SENT_116	[p6l1127t1700r1537b1807],
17	(	NN	O	(	conj_and	13	SENT_116	[p6l1595t1702r1804b1808],
18	area	NN	O	area	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l1595t1702r1804b1808],
19	2	CD	NUMBER	2	dep	18	SENT_116	[p6l1854t1703r1926b1797],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l1854t1703r1926b1797],
21	Fig	NN	O	fig	appos	19	SENT_116	[p6l1980t1702r2149b1807],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_116	[p6l1980t1702r2149b1807],

1	EARLY	JJ	O	early	amod	2	SENT_117	[p6l121t1966r267b2001],
2	_	NN	O	_	_	0	SENT_117	[p6l311t1966r622b2001],
3	l_ANDOVERY	NN	O	l_andovery	nn	4	SENT_117	[p6l311t1966r622b2001],
4	PALEOGEOGRAPHY	NN	O	paleogeography	dep	2	SENT_117	[p6l664t1966r1098b2001],
