1	Paleontological	NNP	O	Paleontological	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l17t81r380b129],
2	Society	NNP	O	Society	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l398t81r574b129],

1	Early	RB	O	early	advmod	3	SENT_2	[p1l15t270r130b313],
2	Devonian	JJ	O	devonian	amod	3	SENT_2	[p1l151t270r347b302],
3	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l367t266r558b315],
4	Pragian	NN	O	pragian	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l367t266r558b315],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	6	SENT_2	[p1l367t266r558b315],
6	Gastropods	NNS	O	gastropod	dep	4	SENT_2	[p1l579t270r820b313],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l841t270r957b302],
8	Kyrgyzstan	NNP	LOCATION	Kyrgyzstan	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l978t270r1235b315],
9	(	NNP	O	(	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l1256t266r1431b306],
10	Central	NNP	LOCATION	Central	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l1256t266r1431b306],
11	Asia	NNP	LOCATION	Asia	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l1452t266r1553b306],
12	)	NNP	O	)	nn	13	SENT_2	[p1l1452t266r1553b306],
13	Author	NN	O	author	prep_from	6	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
15	s	NNS	O	s	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	15	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
17	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
18	Alexander	NNP	PERSON	Alexander	nn	20	SENT_2	[p1l255t324r476b355],
19	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	20	SENT_2	[p1l497t324r531b355],
20	Gubanov	NNP	PERSON	Gubanov	dep	15	SENT_2	[p1l554t324r753b360],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l554t324r753b360],
22	Robert	NNP	PERSON	Robert	nn	24	SENT_2	[p1l779t324r929b355],
23	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	24	SENT_2	[p1l950t324r987b355],
24	Blodgett	NNP	PERSON	Blodgett	conj_and	20	SENT_2	[p1l1010t324r1196b368],
25	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1217t324r1292b355],
26	Vladimir	NNP	PERSON	Vladimir	nn	29	SENT_2	[p1l1313t323r1506b355],
27	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	29	SENT_2	[p1l1527t324r1570b355],
28	Lytochkin	NNP	PERSON	Lytochkin	nn	29	SENT_2	[p1l1593t323r1821b366],
29	Source	NNP	O	Source	conj_and	20	SENT_2	[p1l15t377r166b409],
30	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l15t377r166b409],
31	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	dep	15	SENT_2	[p1l190t377r363b409],
32	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l383t377r433b409],
33	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	nn	35	SENT_2	[p1l449t377r739b422],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l449t377r739b422],
35	Vol	NNP	O	Vol	prep_of	31	SENT_2	[p1l765t377r845b409],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l765t377r845b409],

1	This	DT	O	this	nsubj	3	SENT_11	[p1l494t1468r552b1492],
2	content	JJ	O	content	amod	1	SENT_11	[p1l562t1472r660b1492],
3	downloaded	VBN	O	download	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l669t1468r831b1492],
4	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l840t1468r904b1492],
5	144.92.142	CD	NUMBER	144.92.142	prep_from	3	SENT_11	[p1l916t1468r1119b1492],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_11	[p1l916t1468r1119b1492],

1	l58	NN	O	l58	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l916t1468r1119b1492],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1130t1476r1162b1492],
3	Wed	NNP	TIME	Wed	prep_on	1	SENT_12	[p1l1171t1468r1241b1496],
4	,	,	TIME	,	_	0	SENT_12	[p1l1171t1468r1241b1496],
5	8	CD	TIME	8	appos	3	SENT_12	[p1l1252t1468r1266b1492],
6	May	NNP	DATE	May	tmod	5	SENT_12	[p1l1276t1469r1336b1499],
7	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	6	SENT_12	[p1l1346t1468r1410b1492],
8	16:27:48	CD	TIME	16:27:48	num	9	SENT_12	[p1l1424t1468r1537b1492],
9	PM	NN	TIME	pm	dep	1	SENT_12	[p1l1547t1469r1594b1492],

1	MASTANDREA	NNP	PERSON	MASTANDREA	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l242t1613r516b1642],
2	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l529t1613r613b1641],
3	RUSSO	NNP	PERSON	RUSSO	conj_and	1	SENT_13	[p1l625t1612r1082b1641],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l625t1612r1082b1641],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l625t1612r1082b1641],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l625t1612r1082b1641],

1	DEMOSPONGE	NNP	O	DEMOSPONGE	nn	2	SENT_15	[p1l625t1612r1082b1641],
2	MICROS	NNP	O	MICROS	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l1093t1612r1255b1641],
3	TR	NN	O	tr	nn	5	SENT_15	[p1l1258t1613r1307b1640],
4	UC	NN	O	uc	nn	5	SENT_15	[p1l1313t1612r1367b1641],
5	TURE	NN	O	ture	dep	2	SENT_15	[p1l1369t1612r1475b1641],
6	431	CD	NUMBER	431	dep	2	SENT_15	[p1l1861t1612r1917b1640],

1	SIMKISS	NNP	LOCATION	SIMKISS	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l16t1773r257b1834],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l16t1773r257b1834],
3	K.	NNP	O	K.	appos	1	SENT_16	[p1l284t1774r351b1824],
4	1986	CD	DATE	1986	num	3	SENT_16	[p1l413t1773r568b1825],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l413t1773r568b1825],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_17	[p1l622t1774r739b1824],
2	processes	NNS	O	process	nsubj	10	SENT_17	[p1l762t1788r1042b1835],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1066t1771r1133b1824],
4	biomineralization	NN	O	biomineralization	prep_of	2	SENT_17	[p1l1146t1772r1681b1824],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1706t1772r1762b1822],
6	lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	7	SENT_17	[p1l1786t1773r1951b1823],
7	plants	NNS	O	plant	prep_in	4	SENT_17	[p1l1972t1774r2151b1835],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l81t1849r192b1900],
9	animals	NNS	O	animal	prep_in	4	SENT_17	[p1l216t1849r593b1900],
10	?	VBD	O	?	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l216t1849r593b1900],
11	an	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_17	[p1l216t1849r593b1900],
12	overview	NN	O	overview	dobj	10	SENT_17	[p1l619t1848r912b1910],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l619t1848r912b1910],
14	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	12	SENT_17	[p1l938t1864r990b1911],
15	19-37	CD	DATE	19-37	num	14	SENT_17	[p1l1027t1849r1217b1900],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l1027t1849r1217b1900],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1245t1850r1311b1900],
2	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	3	SENT_18	[p1l1337t1851r1393b1900],
3	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	dobj	4	SENT_18	[p1l1423t1849r1473b1900],
4	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l1501t1850r1563b1901],
5	Leadbeater	NNP	PERSON	Leadbeater	nsubj	8	SENT_18	[p1l1593t1850r1925b1901],
6	and	CC	O	and	prep	5	SENT_18	[p1l1946t1850r2056b1901],
7	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	dep	6	SENT_18	[p1l2082t1852r2146b1901],
8	Riding	VBG	PERSON	ride	ccomp	4	SENT_18	[p1l84t1924r287b1988],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	10	SENT_18	[p1l313t1925r488b1986],
10	eds	NNS	O	ed	dobj	8	SENT_18	[p1l313t1925r488b1986],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l313t1925r488b1986],
12	)	SYM	O	)	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l313t1925r488b1986],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l313t1925r488b1986],
2	Biomineralization	NNP	O	Biomineralization	dep	3	SENT_19	[p1l518t1924r1061b1976],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1089t1924r1144b1975],
4	Lower	NNP	O	Lower	nn	5	SENT_19	[p1l1174t1926r1364b1976],
5	Plants	NNPS	O	Plants	pobj	3	SENT_19	[p1l1390t1926r1573b1976],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1598t1926r1708b1977],
7	Animals	NNPS	O	Animals	conj_and	5	SENT_19	[p1l1734t1924r2003b1977],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1734t1924r2003b1977],

1	The	DT	ORGANIZATION	the	det	3	SENT_20	[p1l2032t1927r2149b1977],
2	Systematics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Systematics	nn	3	SENT_20	[p1l83t2001r436b2064],
3	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Association	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l460t2001r827b2062],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l460t2001r827b2062],
5	Special	JJ	O	special	amod	6	SENT_20	[p1l855t2001r1066b2063],
6	Volume	NN	O	volume	appos	3	SENT_20	[p1l1091t2002r1331b2053],
7	30	CD	NUMBER	30	dep	6	SENT_20	[p1l1357t2002r1443b2053],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1357t2002r1443b2053],

1	SOEST	NNP	LOCATION	SOEST	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l14t2076r204b2137],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l14t2076r204b2137],
3	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	6	SENT_21	[p1l234t2078r299b2127],
4	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	6	SENT_21	[p1l330t2078r412b2127],
5	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	6	SENT_21	[p1l443t2077r522b2127],
6	VAN	NNP	PERSON	VAN	appos	1	SENT_21	[p1l552t2078r700b2127],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l552t2078r700b2127],

1	1984	CD	DATE	1984	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l765t2077r921b2128],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l765t2077r921b2128],

1	De?cient	JJ	O	de?cient	amod	3	SENT_23	[p1l978t2076r1250b2128],
2	Merlia	NN	O	merlium	nn	3	SENT_23	[p1l1274t2076r1475b2128],
3	normani	NNS	O	normanus	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1503t2079r1760b2129],
4	Kirkpatrick	NNP	PERSON	Kirkpatrick	dep	3	SENT_23	[p1l1784t2077r2147b2140],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1784t2077r2147b2140],
6	1908	CD	DATE	1908	appos	4	SENT_23	[p1l90t2152r248b2212],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l90t2152r248b2212],
8	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l276t2151r419b2203],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_23	[p1l445t2153r538b2203],
10	Curacao	NNP	LOCATION	Curacao	nn	11	SENT_23	[p1l562t2152r811b2203],
11	Reef	NN	LOCATION	reef	prep_from	4	SENT_23	[p1l837t2151r987b2213],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l837t2151r987b2213],
13	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1014t2152r1144b2203],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	15	SENT_23	[p1l1170t2167r1202b2203],
15	discussion	NN	O	discussion	prep_with	4	SENT_23	[p1l1226t2152r1534b2204],
16	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1559t2168r1632b2204],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_23	[p1l1657t2154r1749b2204],
18	phylogenetic	JJ	O	phylogenetic	amod	19	SENT_23	[p1l1772t2154r2149b2217],
19	interpretation	NN	O	interpretation	prep_on	15	SENT_23	[p1l83t2228r497b2290],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l519t2228r587b2279],
21	sclerosponges	NNS	O	sclerosponge	prep_of	4	SENT_23	[p1l599t2230r1022b2291],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l599t2230r1022b2291],

1	Bijdragen	NN	O	bijdragen	nn	2	SENT_24	[p1l1049t2229r1334b2292],
2	tot	NN	O	tot	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1356t2238r1438b2281],
3	de	IN	O	de	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1459t2230r1529b2281],
4	Dierkunde	NNP	O	Dierkunde	prep_de	2	SENT_24	[p1l1551t2230r1886b2290],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1551t2230r1886b2290],
6	54:21	CD	NUMBER	54:21	num	7	SENT_24	[p1l1914t2230r2068b2282],
7	1219	CD	DATE	1219	appos	4	SENT_24	[p1l2090t2233r2152b2280, p1l84t2306r209b2356],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l2090t2233r2152b2280, p1l84t2306r209b2356],

1	TERMIER	NNP	LOCATION	TERMIER	nn	3	SENT_25	[p1l14t2382r292b2441],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l14t2382r292b2441],
3	H.	NNP	O	H.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l324t2383r414b2441],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l324t2383r414b2441],
5	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l443t2394r569b2432],
6	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	7	SENT_25	[p1l597t2382r666b2432],
7	TERMIER	NNP	PERSON	TERMIER	conj_and	3	SENT_25	[p1l699t2382r975b2432],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l699t2382r975b2432],

1	1973	CD	DATE	1973	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1041t2382r1198b2433],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l1041t2382r1198b2433],

1	Stromatopores	NNP	PERSON	Stromatopores	nsubj	3	SENT_27	[p1l1256t2382r1713b2444],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1256t2382r1713b2444],
3	scl?rosponges	VBZ	O	scl?rosponges	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1744t2380r2149b2446],
4	et	FW	O	et	nn	5	SENT_27	[p1l82t2465r135b2508],
5	phar?trones	FW	O	phar?trones	dobj	3	SENT_27	[p1l160t2455r530b2517],
6	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l160t2455r530b2517],
7	les	FW	O	les	nn	8	SENT_27	[p1l558t2458r636b2508],
8	Ischyrospongia	FW	O	ischyrospongia	dep	5	SENT_27	[p1l661t2458r1128b2520],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l661t2458r1128b2520],

1	Annales	NNP	MISC	Annales	nn	7	SENT_28	[p1l1156t2458r1398b2509],
2	des	NNP	MISC	des	nn	7	SENT_28	[p1l1422t2459r1519b2510],
3	Mines	NNP	MISC	Mines	nn	7	SENT_28	[p1l1544t2459r1729b2510],
4	et	NNP	MISC	et	nn	7	SENT_28	[p1l1753t2467r1805b2510],
5	de	FW	MISC	de	nn	7	SENT_28	[p1l1830t2460r1899b2511],
6	la	FW	MISC	la	nn	7	SENT_28	[p1l1924t2460r1975b2510],
7	G?ologie	NNP	MISC	G?ologie	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l2001t2457r2146b2510, p1l83t2533r240b2597],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l2001t2457r2146b2510, p1l83t2533r240b2597],
9	26:285	CD	NUMBER	26:285	num	10	SENT_28	[p1l268t2533r637b2585],
10	-297	CD	NUMBER	-297	appos	7	SENT_28	[p1l268t2533r637b2585],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l268t2533r637b2585],

1	TUCKER	NNP	LOCATION	TUCKER	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l14t2610r271b2669],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l14t2610r271b2669],
3	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	4	SENT_29	[p1l297t2610r377b2660],
4	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	appos	1	SENT_29	[p1l403t2610r478b2669],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l403t2610r478b2669],
6	AND	NNP	O	AND	nn	9	SENT_29	[p1l502t2623r628b2660],
7	V.	NNP	PERSON	V.	nn	9	SENT_29	[p1l649t2611r715b2660],
8	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	9	SENT_29	[p1l741t2612r797b2660],
9	WRIGHT	NNP	PERSON	WRIGHT	appos	4	SENT_29	[p1l823t2611r1086b2661],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l823t2611r1086b2661],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1147t2610r1303b2662],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1147t2610r1303b2662],

1	Carbonate	NNP	O	Carbonate	nn	2	SENT_31	[p1l1353t2611r1664b2662],
2	Sedimentology	NNP	O	Sedimentology	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1687t2611r2145b2675],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1687t2611r2145b2675],

1	Blackwell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Blackwell	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l84t2685r370b2737],
2	Scienti?c	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scienti?c	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l396t2685r669b2737],
3	Publications	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Publications	nn	5	SENT_32	[p1l694t2685r1083b2747],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l694t2685r1083b2747],
5	Oxford	NNP	LOCATION	Oxford	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1109t2685r1339b2747],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1109t2685r1339b2747],
7	482	CD	NUMBER	482	num	8	SENT_32	[p1l1366t2687r1476b2738],
8	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	5	SENT_32	[p1l1502t2702r1554b2749],

1	VACELET	NNP	LOCATION	VACELET	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l14t2762r292b2821],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l14t2762r292b2821],
3	J	NNP	O	J	appos	1	SENT_33	[p1l318t2762r348b2815],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l354t2802r363b2812],

1	1964	CD	DATE	1964	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l427t2761r584b2812],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l427t2761r584b2812],

1	Etude	NN	O	etude	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l639t2762r813b2813],
2	monographique	FW	O	monographique	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l839t2761r1313b2824],
3	de	FW	O	de	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l1336t2763r1406b2814],
4	l?Eponge	FW	O	l?eponge	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l1432t2763r1690b2825],
5	Calcaire	FW	O	calcaire	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l1715t2763r1958b2814],
6	Phar?tronide	FW	O	phar?tronide	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l1984t2764r2146b2814, p1l81t2834r331b2889],
7	de	FW	O	de	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l355t2838r424b2889],
8	M?diterran?e	FW	O	m?diterran?e	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l450t2835r851b2889],
9	Petrobiona	FW	O	petrobiona	nn	1	SENT_35	[p1l876t2836r1202b2890],
10	massiliana	FW	O	massiliana	dep	1	SENT_35	[p1l1229t2837r1549b2890],
11	Vacelet	NNP	PERSON	Vacelet	dep	1	SENT_35	[p1l1573t2840r1794b2890],
12	et	FW	O	et	nn	13	SENT_35	[p1l1819t2847r1872b2890],
13	L?vi	FW	O	l?vi	dep	11	SENT_35	[p1l1897t2837r2044b2891],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1897t2837r2044b2891],

1	Le	NNP	PERSON	Le	nn	2	SENT_36	[p1l2074t2841r2147b2891],
2	Phar?tronides	NNP	PERSON	Phar?tronides	nsubj	3	SENT_36	[p1l82t2911r502b2965],
3	actuelles	VBZ	O	actuelle	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l525t2914r782b2965],
4	et	FW	O	et	nn	5	SENT_36	[p1l806t2922r859b2965],
5	fossiles	FW	O	fossiles	dobj	3	SENT_36	[p1l885t2913r1114b2965],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l885t2913r1114b2965],

1	Recueil	NNP	O	Recueil	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1144t2914r1365b2966],
2	des	FW	O	des	nn	5	SENT_37	[p1l1391t2915r1488b2966],
3	travaux	FW	O	travaux	nn	5	SENT_37	[p1l1512t2923r1739b2967],
4	de	FW	O	de	nn	5	SENT_37	[p1l1764t2916r1834b2967],
5	la	FW	O	la	dep	1	SENT_37	[p1l1859t2916r1909b2966],
6	Station	NNP	O	Station	dep	5	SENT_37	[p1l1935t2916r2146b2967],
7	marine	JJ	O	marine	amod	8	SENT_37	[p1l83t2988r294b3040],
8	d?Endoume	NN	O	d?endoume	dep	1	SENT_37	[p1l308t2990r673b3050],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l308t2990r673b3050],
10	Facult?	NNP	O	Facult?	nn	11	SENT_37	[p1l692t2987r911b3041],
11	des	NNP	O	des	appos	8	SENT_37	[p1l925t2991r1023b3042],
12	sciences	NNS	O	science	dep	1	SENT_37	[p1l1038t2990r1277b3042],
13	de	IN	O	de	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1291t2991r1361b3042],
14	Marseille	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Marseille	prep_de	12	SENT_37	[p1l1377t2991r1669b3052],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1377t2991r1669b3052],
16	Bulletin	NNP	O	Bulletin	appos	1	SENT_37	[p1l1688t2991r1921b3043],
17	34	CD	NUMBER	34	num	16	SENT_37	[p1l1939t2992r2144b3054],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	number	19	SENT_37	[p1l1939t2992r2144b3054],
19	50	CD	NUMBER	50	num	20	SENT_37	[p1l1939t2992r2144b3054],
20	)	NN	O	)	dep	16	SENT_37	[p1l1939t2992r2144b3054],
21	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1939t2992r2144b3054],
22	1-125	CD	NUMBER	1-125	dep	16	SENT_37	[p1l90t3069r281b3119],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l90t3069r281b3119],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l15t3166r167b3190],

1	1979	CD	DATE	1979	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l231t3140r388b3191],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l231t3140r388b3191],

1	Development	NN	O	development	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l443t3142r853b3203],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l878t3140r946b3193],
3	skeletal	JJ	O	skeletal	amod	4	SENT_44	[p1l962t3142r1182b3193],
4	formation	NN	O	formation	prep_of	1	SENT_44	[p1l1210t3141r1526b3204],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1210t3141r1526b3204],
6	microstructure	NN	O	microstructure	prep_of	1	SENT_44	[p1l1556t3143r2010b3205],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1556t3143r2010b3205],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l2038t3146r2147b3197],
9	mineralogy	NN	O	mineralogy	conj_and	4	SENT_44	[p1l87t3215r422b3280],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l451t3216r519b3268],
11	rigid	JJ	O	rigid	amod	13	SENT_44	[p1l539t3216r676b3280],
12	calcareous	JJ	O	calcareous	amod	13	SENT_44	[p1l706t3218r1017b3269],
13	sponges	NNS	O	sponge	prep_of	1	SENT_44	[p1l1048t3233r1279b3282],
14	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l1309t3218r1453b3270],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_44	[p1l1485t3221r1576b3271],
16	late	JJ	O	late	amod	17	SENT_44	[p1l1605t3221r1711b3271],
17	Palaeozoic	NN	O	palaeozoic	prep_from	1	SENT_44	[p1l1742t3221r2059b3273],
18	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l2089t3230r2147b3273],
19	Recent	JJ	O	recent	prep_to	17	SENT_44	[p1l87t3294r309b3353],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l87t3294r309b3353],
21	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	19	SENT_44	[p1l332t3308r384b3353],
22	449-475	CD	NUMBER	449-475	num	21	SENT_44	[p1l407t3293r681b3344],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p1l407t3293r681b3344],

1	In	IN	O	in	mark	2	SENT_45	[p1l708t3294r773b3345],
2	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l796t3294r858b3345],
3	Levi	NNP	PERSON	Levi	dep	2	SENT_45	[p1l882t3294r1014b3345],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1035t3295r1144b3346],
5	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	8	SENT_45	[p1l1165t3297r1235b3346],
6	Boury-Esnault	NNP	PERSON	Boury-Esnault	nn	8	SENT_45	[p1l1259t3297r1689b3359],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_45	[p1l1708t3297r1882b3359],
8	eds	NNS	O	ed	dep	2	SENT_45	[p1l1708t3297r1882b3359],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p1l1708t3297r1882b3359],
10	)	SYM	O	)	dep	2	SENT_45	[p1l1708t3297r1882b3359],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l1708t3297r1882b3359],
2	Biologic	JJ	O	biologic	dep	3	SENT_46	[p1l1905t3297r2147b3361],
3	des	FW	O	des	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l84t3368r182b3419],
4	Spongiaires	FW	O	spongiaires	dep	3	SENT_46	[p1l209t3368r568b3431],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l209t3368r568b3431],

1	Colloques	NNP	O	Colloques	nn	4	SENT_47	[p1l597t3369r897b3431],
2	intemationaux	NN	O	intemationaux	nn	4	SENT_47	[p1l923t3369r1363b3422],
3	du	NNP	O	du	nn	4	SENT_47	[p1l1388t3372r1464b3423],
4	Centre	NNP	O	Centre	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1490t3372r1688b3423],
5	National	NNP	O	National	nn	9	SENT_47	[p1l1713t3372r1974b3424],
6	de	NNP	O	de	nn	9	SENT_47	[p1l2000t3374r2070b3425],
7	la	NNP	O	la	nn	9	SENT_47	[p1l2096t3374r2147b3425],
8	Recherche	NNP	O	Recherche	nn	9	SENT_47	[p1l86t3447r399b3497],
9	Scienti?que	NNP	O	Scienti?que	dep	4	SENT_47	[p1l423t3446r790b3509],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l423t3446r790b3509],
11	number	NN	O	number	appos	9	SENT_47	[p1l817t3448r1053b3499],
12	291	CD	NUMBER	291	num	11	SENT_47	[p1l1077t3448r1202b3500],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p1l1077t3448r1202b3500],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_51	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_52	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p1l9t3546r163b3572],

1	1981	CD	DATE	1981	_	0	SENT_53	[p1l239t3522r402b3573],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p1l239t3522r402b3573],

1	Eponges	NNS	O	eponge	nn	2	SENT_54	[p1l469t3523r727b3585],
2	hypercalci??es	NNS	O	hypercalci??es	nsubj	3	SENT_54	[p1l766t3521r1222b3585],
3	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_54	[p1l1259t3522r1821b3585],
4	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	5	SENT_54	[p1l1259t3522r1821b3585],
5	Phar?tronides	NNS	O	phar?tronides	dobj	3	SENT_54	[p1l1259t3522r1821b3585],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p1l1259t3522r1821b3585],
7	?	FW	O	?	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l1259t3522r1821b3585],
8	?	FW	O	?	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l1860t3523r2144b3576, p1l80t3598r345b3660],
9	Scl?rosponges	FW	O	scl?rosponges	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l1860t3523r2144b3576, p1l80t3598r345b3660],
10	?	FW	O	?	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l1860t3523r2144b3576, p1l80t3598r345b3660],
11	)	FW	O	)	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l1860t3523r2144b3576, p1l80t3598r345b3660],
12	des	FW	O	des	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l362t3598r460b3649],
13	cavit?s	FW	O	cavit?s	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l477t3595r683b3649],
14	des	FW	O	des	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l701t3598r799b3649],
15	r?cifs	FW	O	r?cifs	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l817t3595r974b3649],
16	coralliens	FW	O	coralliens	nn	17	SENT_54	[p1l992t3598r1279b3650],
17	de	FW	O	de	appos	5	SENT_54	[p1l1295t3600r1365b3651],
18	Nouvelle-Caledonie	NNP	O	Nouvelle-Caledonie	dep	17	SENT_54	[p1l1382t3600r1997b3652],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p1l1382t3600r1997b3652],

1	Mus?um	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mus?um	nn	4	SENT_55	[p1l2018t3602r2144b3652, p1l81t3671r233b3724],
2	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	4	SENT_55	[p1l254t3674r510b3725],
3	d?Histoire	NNP	ORGANIZATION	d?Histoire	nn	4	SENT_55	[p1l529t3674r826b3725],
4	Naturelle	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Naturelle	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l843t3676r1131b3735],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l843t3676r1131b3735],
6	Bulletin	NNP	O	Bulletin	appos	4	SENT_55	[p1l1153t3675r1396b3736],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l1153t3675r1396b3736],
8	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	9	SENT_55	[p1l1417t3677r1451b3726],
9	s?rie	NN	O	s?rie	appos	4	SENT_55	[p1l1471t3674r1619b3737],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l1471t3674r1619b3737],
11	section	NN	O	section	nn	12	SENT_55	[p1l1641t3677r1842b3728],
12	A	NN	O	a	appos	4	SENT_55	[p1l1862t3677r1927b3738],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l1862t3677r1927b3738],
14	2:313351	CD	NUMBER	2:313351	appos	4	SENT_55	[p1l1949t3677r2147b3729, p1l82t3752r207b3803],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p1l1949t3677r2147b3729, p1l82t3752r207b3803],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l9t44r161b70],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l9t44r161b70],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p2l9t44r161b70],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l9t44r161b70],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l9t44r161b70],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l9t44r161b70],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l9t44r161b70],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l9t44r161b70],

1	1983	CD	DATE	1983	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l216t20r372b71],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l216t20r372b71],

1	Les	NNP	O	Les	nn	3	SENT_62	[p2l420t21r521b71],
2	Eponges	NNP	O	Eponges	nn	3	SENT_62	[p2l539t21r788b83],
3	calci??es	NNS	O	calci??es	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l802t18r1069b72],
4	et	FW	O	et	dep	3	SENT_62	[p2l1085t29r1137b72],
5	les	FW	O	les	nn	7	SENT_62	[p2l1154t22r1231b72],
6	r?cifs	FW	O	r?cifs	nn	7	SENT_62	[p2l1248t19r1405b73],
7	anciens	NNS	O	ancien	dep	4	SENT_62	[p2l1420t22r1658b73],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1420t22r1658b73],

1	Pour	NNP	O	Pour	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1678t24r1824b74],
2	la	NNP	O	la	nn	3	SENT_63	[p2l1838t24r1888b74],
3	Science	NNP	O	Science	dep	1	SENT_63	[p2l1906t23r2142b84],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1906t23r2142b84],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l8t197r160b223],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l8t197r160b223],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l8t197r160b223],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l8t197r160b223],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l8t197r160b223],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l8t197r160b223],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l8t197r160b223],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l8t197r160b223],

1	1985	CD	DATE	1985	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l222t172r378b223],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l222t172r378b223],

1	Coralline	NNP	O	Coralline	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l431t172r708b224],
2	sponges	NNS	O	sponge	dep	1	SENT_70	[p2l731t188r964b236],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l985t174r1096b225],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_70	[p2l1119t175r1211b225],
5	evolution	NN	O	evolution	dep	1	SENT_70	[p2l1233t174r1518b226],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1541t174r1609b226],
7	Porifera	NNP	LOCATION	Porifera	prep_of	1	SENT_70	[p2l1622t174r1878b236],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1622t174r1878b236],
9	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	7	SENT_70	[p2l1903t191r1954b236],
10	1-13	CD	NUMBER	1-13	num	9	SENT_70	[p2l1990t177r2141b228],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1990t177r2141b228],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l79t248r144b298],
2	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	nn	4	SENT_71	[p2l164t247r213b298],
3	Conway	NNP	PERSON	Conway	nn	4	SENT_71	[p2l235t248r479b311],
4	Morris	NNP	PERSON	Morris	pobj	1	SENT_71	[p2l498t248r720b308],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l498t248r720b308],
6	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	appos	4	SENT_71	[p2l738t250r783b303],
7	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	8	SENT_71	[p2l806t250r875b299],
8	George	NNP	PERSON	George	rcmod	6	SENT_71	[p2l897t249r1127b312],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l897t249r1127b312],
10	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	11	SENT_71	[p2l1150t251r1213b300],
11	Gibson	NNP	PERSON	Gibson	appos	8	SENT_71	[p2l1235t249r1470b311],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1235t249r1470b311],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1489t251r1599b302],
14	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	18	SENT_71	[p2l1618t252r1688b302],
15	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	18	SENT_71	[p2l1709t252r1789b303],
16	Platt	NNP	PERSON	Platt	nn	18	SENT_71	[p2l1811t252r1950b303],
17	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_71	[p2l1967t253r2142b314],
18	cds	NNS	O	cd	conj_and	11	SENT_71	[p2l1967t253r2142b314],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1967t253r2142b314],
20	)	SYM	O	)	dep	8	SENT_71	[p2l1967t253r2142b314],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l1967t253r2142b314],
2	The	DT	O	the	dep	3	SENT_72	[p2l78t324r195b374],
3	Origins	NNS	MISC	origin	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l219t323r440b387],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l462t325r572b376],
5	Relationships	NNPS	O	Relationships	conj_and	3	SENT_72	[p2l599t324r1010b387],
6	of	IN	O	of	prep	3	SENT_72	[p2l1033t324r1101b376],
7	Lower	NNP	O	Lower	nn	8	SENT_72	[p2l1115t327r1306b377],
8	Invertebrates	NNPS	O	Invertebrates	dep	6	SENT_72	[p2l1328t327r1738b378],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l1328t327r1738b378],

1	The	DT	ORGANIZATION	the	det	3	SENT_73	[p2l1764t329r1882b379],
2	Systematics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Systematics	nn	3	SENT_73	[p2l1906t328r2142b391, p2l77t400r213b452],
3	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Association	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l237t401r606b462],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l237t401r606b462],
5	Special	JJ	O	special	amod	6	SENT_73	[p2l633t401r844b464],
6	Volume	NN	O	volume	appos	3	SENT_73	[p2l869t403r1109b454],
7	28	CD	NUMBER	28	num	6	SENT_73	[p2l1134t403r1221b454],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l1134t403r1221b454],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l7t500r159b535],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l7t500r159b535],
3	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l184t489r310b526],
4	M.	NNP	O	M.	nn	5	SENT_74	[p2l331t477r411b526],
5	J.	NNP	O	J.	nn	6	SENT_74	[p2l435t477r482b530],
6	URIZ	NNP	O	URIZ	conj_and	1	SENT_74	[p2l509t477r670b527],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l509t477r670b527],

1	1991	CD	DATE	1991	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l731t477r886b528],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l731t477r886b528],

1	De?cient	JJ	O	de?cient	amod	2	SENT_76	[p2l940t476r1211b529],
2	spiculation	NN	O	spiculation	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l1233t477r1560b540],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l1583t478r1639b528],
4	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_76	[p2l1661t494r1693b530],
5	new	JJ	O	new	amod	6	SENT_76	[p2l1716t494r1835b530],
6	species	NNS	O	species	prep_in	2	SENT_76	[p2l1858t480r2064b540],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l2085t479r2153b531],
8	Merlia	NNP	LOCATION	Merlia	prep_of	6	SENT_76	[p2l76t550r278b603],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_76	[p2l302t552r598b614],
10	Merliida	NNP	PERSON	Merliida	nn	12	SENT_76	[p2l302t552r598b614],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l302t552r598b614],
12	Demospongiae	NNP	O	Demospongiae	dep	2	SENT_76	[p2l626t554r1094b617],
13	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	12	SENT_76	[p2l626t554r1094b617],
14	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l1120t553r1263b605],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_76	[p2l1288t556r1380b606],
16	Balearic	NNP	LOCATION	Balearic	nn	17	SENT_76	[p2l1403t555r1643b607],
17	Islands	NNPS	LOCATION	Islands	prep_from	12	SENT_76	[p2l1667t557r1893b617],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l1667t557r1893b617],
19	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	17	SENT_76	[p2l1920t572r1972b617],
20	171177	CD	NUMBER	171177	num	19	SENT_76	[p2l2007t558r2145b607, p2l85t628r204b678],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l2007t558r2145b607, p2l85t628r204b678],

1	In	IN	O	in	mark	2	SENT_77	[p2l234t629r300b678],
2	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	_	0	SENT_77	[p2l324t628r369b681],
3	Reitner	NNP	PERSON	Reitner	dep	2	SENT_77	[p2l401t627r626b679],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_77	[p2l648t629r759b680],
5	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	8	SENT_77	[p2l786t630r856b679],
6	Keupp	NNP	PERSON	Keupp	nn	8	SENT_77	[p2l886t629r1086b689],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_77	[p2l1111t630r1286b691],
8	cds	NNS	O	cd	dep	2	SENT_77	[p2l1111t630r1286b691],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p2l1111t630r1286b691],
10	)	SYM	O	)	dep	2	SENT_77	[p2l1111t630r1286b691],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1111t630r1286b691],
2	Fossil	NNP	O	Fossil	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1316t630r1488b681],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1513t631r1624b682],
4	Recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	5	SENT_78	[p2l1651t632r1856b682],
5	Sponges	NNS	O	sponge	conj_and	2	SENT_78	[p2l1882t632r2138b695],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1882t632r2138b695],

1	Springer-Verlag	NNP	LOCATION	Springer-Verlag	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l78t704r567b769],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l78t704r567b769],
3	Berlin	NNP	LOCATION	Berlin	nn	5	SENT_79	[p2l594t706r791b766],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l594t706r791b766],
5	Heidelberg	NNP	LOCATION	Heidelberg	appos	1	SENT_79	[p2l819t706r1161b770],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l819t706r1161b770],

1	431-440	CD	NUMBER	431-440	num	2	SENT_81	[p2l678t924r873b964],
2	Copyright	NN	O	copyright	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l21t975r247b1023],
3	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	4	SENT_81	[p2l269t978r308b1016],
4	1995	CD	DATE	1995	dep	2	SENT_81	[p2l340t977r457b1022],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l340t977r457b1022],
6	The	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_81	[p2l477t979r565b1017],
7	Paleontological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paleontological	nn	8	SENT_81	[p2l585t979r927b1028],
8	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	4	SENT_81	[p2l946t981r1107b1028],
9	0022-3360/95	CD	DURATION	0022-3360/95	dep	8	SENT_81	[p2l20t1043r767b1087],
10	/	:	O	/	punct	8	SENT_81	[p2l20t1043r767b1087],
11	0069-0431	CD	DURATION	0069-0431	dep	8	SENT_81	[p2l20t1043r767b1087],
12	$	$	MONEY	$	nn	14	SENT_81	[p2l20t1043r767b1087],
13	03.00	CD	MONEY	03.00	num	12	SENT_81	[p2l20t1043r767b1087],
14	VEIZER	NNP	O	VEIZER	dep	11	SENT_81	[p2l8t1113r233b1173],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l8t1113r233b1173],
16	J	NNP	O	J	dep	4	SENT_81	[p2l263t1112r293b1166],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l300t1153r329b1173],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_82	[p2l300t1153r329b1173],
2	AND	CC	O	and	cc	3	SENT_82	[p2l360t1124r487b1163],
3	J.	NNP	PERSON	J.	nn	4	SENT_82	[p2l513t1112r559b1166],
4	WENDT	NNP	PERSON	WENDT	_	0	SENT_82	[p2l592t1111r829b1162],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_82	[p2l592t1111r829b1162],

1	1976	CD	DATE	1976	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l896t1109r1053b1162],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l896t1109r1053b1162],

1	Mineralogy	NNP	O	Mineralogy	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l1113t1108r1455b1173],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l1484t1109r1594b1161],
3	chemical	JJ	O	chemical	amod	4	SENT_84	[p2l1623t1107r1889b1160],
4	composition	NN	O	composition	conj_and	1	SENT_84	[p2l1920t1122r2148b1170, p2l77t1187r244b1240],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l277t1186r345b1239],
6	Recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	9	SENT_84	[p2l371t1189r578b1239],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l609t1187r721b1239],
8	fossil	JJ	O	fossil	amod	9	SENT_84	[p2l754t1185r907b1238],
9	skeletons	NNS	O	skeleton	prep_of	4	SENT_84	[p2l941t1186r1217b1238],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l1248t1184r1316b1237],
11	calcareous	JJ	O	calcareous	amod	12	SENT_84	[p2l1338t1186r1650b1237],
12	sponges	NNS	O	sponge	prep_of	4	SENT_84	[p2l1681t1199r1930b1248],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l1681t1199r1930b1248],

1	Neues	NNP	O	Neues	nn	2	SENT_85	[p2l1965t1185r2150b1235],
2	Jahrbuch	NNP	O	Jahrbuch	nsubj	3	SENT_85	[p2l74t1265r354b1320],
3	?ir	VBZ	O	?ir	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l387t1263r473b1316],
4	Geologic	JJ	MISC	geologic	amod	6	SENT_85	[p2l502t1262r771b1327],
5	und	NN	O	und	nn	6	SENT_85	[p2l803t1263r916b1315],
6	Pal?iontologie	NN	O	pal?iontologie	dobj	3	SENT_85	[p2l950t1261r1374b1326],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l950t1261r1374b1326],
8	Monatshefte	NN	O	monatshefte	appos	6	SENT_85	[p2l1409t1260r1801b1323],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l1409t1260r1801b1323],
10	1976:558573	CD	NUMBER	1976:558573	appos	8	SENT_85	[p2l1843t1261r2153b1313, p2l81t1342r204b1393],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l1843t1261r2153b1313, p2l81t1342r204b1393],

1	WENDT	NNP	LOCATION	WENDT	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l9t1421r248b1480],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l9t1421r248b1480],
3	J	NNP	O	J	appos	1	SENT_86	[p2l277t1420r305b1474],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l312t1461r323b1470],

1	1974	CD	DATE	1974	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l390t1419r546b1471],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l390t1419r546b1471],

1	Der	NNP	O	Der	nn	4	SENT_88	[p2l606t1419r721b1470],
2	Skelettbau	NNP	O	Skelettbau	nn	4	SENT_88	[p2l748t1418r1063b1470],
3	aragonitischer	NN	O	aragonitischer	nn	4	SENT_88	[p2l1089t1416r1517b1481],
4	Kalkschwamme	NNP	O	Kalkschwamme	_	0	SENT_88	[p2l1543t1416r2025b1469],
5	aus	NN	O	aus	dep	4	SENT_88	[p2l2051t1430r2150b1468],
6	der	FW	O	der	nn	5	SENT_88	[p2l76t1496r174b1548],
7	alpinen	FW	O	alpinen	nn	5	SENT_88	[p2l201t1495r423b1559],
8	Obertrias	FW	O	obertrias	dep	5	SENT_88	[p2l454t1494r752b1548],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_88	[p2l454t1494r752b1548],

1	Neues	NNP	O	Neues	nn	2	SENT_89	[p2l785t1496r971b1547],
2	Jahrbuch	NNP	O	Jahrbuch	nsubj	3	SENT_89	[p2l998t1494r1275b1549],
3	?ir	VBZ	O	?ir	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l1306t1492r1392b1546],
4	Geologic	JJ	MISC	geologic	amod	8	SENT_89	[p2l1419t1492r1687b1557],
5	und	NN	O	und	nn	8	SENT_89	[p2l1717t1493r1830b1545],
6	Paliiontologic	NNP	O	Paliiontologic	nn	8	SENT_89	[p2l1861t1493r2148b1545, p2l76t1571r234b1635],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l1861t1493r2148b1545, p2l76t1571r234b1635],
8	Monatshefte	NNP	O	Monatshefte	dobj	3	SENT_89	[p2l262t1570r655b1632],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l262t1570r655b1632],
10	1974:498	CD	NUMBER	1974:498	number	11	SENT_89	[p2l691t1570r1067b1623],
11	?	CD	NUMBER	?	appos	8	SENT_89	[p2l691t1570r1067b1623],
12	5l	NN	O	5l	dep	11	SENT_89	[p2l691t1570r1067b1623],
13	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	12	SENT_89	[p2l1089t1572r1129b1621],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l1089t1572r1129b1621],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_94	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_94	[p2l10t1678r163b1702],

1	1979	CD	DATE	1979	_	0	SENT_95	[p2l227t1650r383b1702],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_95	[p2l227t1650r383b1702],

1	Development	NN	O	development	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l439t1650r850b1710],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l875t1648r943b1701],
3	skeletal	JJ	O	skeletal	amod	4	SENT_96	[p2l960t1649r1181b1701],
4	formation	NN	O	formation	prep_of	1	SENT_96	[p2l1209t1647r1525b1709],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l1209t1647r1525b1709],
6	microstructure	NN	O	microstructure	prep_of	1	SENT_96	[p2l1555t1647r2012b1708],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l1555t1647r2012b1708],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l2039t1648r2148b1700],
9	mineralogy	NN	O	mineralogy	conj_and	4	SENT_96	[p2l83t1726r419b1790],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l448t1725r516b1778],
11	rigid	JJ	O	rigid	amod	13	SENT_96	[p2l537t1725r673b1790],
12	calcareous	JJ	O	calcareous	amod	13	SENT_96	[p2l704t1726r1015b1778],
13	sponges	NNS	O	sponge	prep_of	1	SENT_96	[p2l1045t1740r1278b1789],
14	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l1308t1723r1452b1776],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_96	[p2l1484t1725r1576b1776],
16	late	JJ	O	late	amod	17	SENT_96	[p2l1605t1725r1712b1776],
17	Palaeozoic	NN	O	palaeozoic	prep_from	1	SENT_96	[p2l1742t1723r2061b1776],
18	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l2090t1731r2149b1775],
19	Recent	JJ	O	recent	prep_to	17	SENT_96	[p2l83t1806r305b1865],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l83t1806r305b1865],
21	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	19	SENT_96	[p2l329t1819r379b1865],
22	449-475	CD	NUMBER	449-475	num	21	SENT_96	[p2l403t1804r678b1856],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_96	[p2l403t1804r678b1856],

1	In	IN	O	in	mark	2	SENT_97	[p2l706t1804r771b1855],
2	C.	NNP	PERSON	C.	_	0	SENT_97	[p2l794t1803r856b1855],
3	Levi	NNP	PERSON	Levi	dep	2	SENT_97	[p2l880t1802r1013b1855],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_97	[p2l1033t1803r1144b1855],
5	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	nn	8	SENT_97	[p2l1165t1804r1234b1854],
6	Boury-Esnault	NNP	PERSON	Boury-Esnault	nn	8	SENT_97	[p2l1259t1803r1690b1866],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_97	[p2l1709t1802r1884b1864],
8	cds	NNS	O	cd	dep	2	SENT_97	[p2l1709t1802r1884b1864],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_97	[p2l1709t1802r1884b1864],
10	)	SYM	O	)	dep	2	SENT_97	[p2l1709t1802r1884b1864],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p2l1709t1802r1884b1864],
2	Biologic	JJ	MISC	biologic	dep	3	SENT_98	[p2l1907t1800r2149b1865],
3	dcs	NNS	MISC	dc	_	0	SENT_98	[p2l81t1880r178b1932],
4	Spongiaircs	NNS	MISC	spongiairc	dep	3	SENT_98	[p2l205t1879r566b1944],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_98	[p2l205t1879r566b1944],

1	Colloqucs	NNP	O	Colloqucs	nn	4	SENT_99	[p2l595t1879r895b1942],
2	intcmationaux	NN	O	intcmationaux	nn	4	SENT_99	[p2l921t1877r1363b1931],
3	du	NNP	O	du	nn	4	SENT_99	[p2l1388t1878r1465b1930],
4	Centre	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Centre	_	0	SENT_99	[p2l1491t1878r1689b1930],
5	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	9	SENT_99	[p2l1715t1876r1976b1930],
6	de	NNP	ORGANIZATION	de	nn	9	SENT_99	[p2l2002t1878r2072b1930],
7	la	NNP	ORGANIZATION	la	nn	9	SENT_99	[p2l2098t1878r2149b1929],
8	Recherche	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Recherche	nn	9	SENT_99	[p2l83t1957r397b2009],
9	Scicnti?quc	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scicnti?quc	dep	4	SENT_99	[p2l421t1955r788b2019],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p2l421t1955r788b2019],
11	number	NN	O	number	appos	9	SENT_99	[p2l814t1956r1050b2008],
12	291	CD	NUMBER	291	num	11	SENT_99	[p2l1076t1955r1200b2007],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_99	[p2l1076t1955r1200b2007],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_100	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_101	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_101	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_102	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_103	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_103	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_104	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_104	[p2l10t2062r163b2087],

1	1984	CD	DATE	1984	_	0	SENT_105	[p2l222t2035r379b2087],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_105	[p2l222t2035r379b2087],

1	Skeletal	JJ	O	skeletal	amod	4	SENT_106	[p2l429t2034r660b2086],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l680t2034r791b2086],
3	spicular	JJ	O	spicular	conj_and	1	SENT_106	[p2l812t2032r1048b2097],
4	mineralogy	NN	O	mineralogy	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1067t2032r1419b2097],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1067t2032r1419b2097],
6	microstructure	NN	O	microstructure	appos	4	SENT_106	[p2l1444t2031r1885b2085],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1903t2033r2013b2085],
8	diagenesis	NN	O	diagenesis	appos	4	SENT_106	[p2l2032t2031r2147b2085, p2l80t2110r292b2175],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l312t2110r380b2163],
10	corallinc	NN	O	corallinc	nn	12	SENT_106	[p2l391t2110r651b2163],
11	calcareous	JJ	O	calcareous	amod	12	SENT_106	[p2l671t2111r982b2162],
12	sponges	NNS	O	sponge	prep_of	6	SENT_106	[p2l1004t2124r1252b2173],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1004t2124r1252b2173],
14	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	4	SENT_106	[p2l1275t2125r1327b2171],
15	326-336	CD	NUMBER	326-336	num	14	SENT_106	[p2l1354t2109r1626b2161],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_106	[p2l1354t2109r1626b2161],

1	In	IN	O	in	dep	9	SENT_107	[p2l1655t2110r1720b2161],
2	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	4	SENT_107	[p2l1744t2110r1826b2161],
3	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	4	SENT_107	[p2l1851t2108r1916b2161],
4	Oliver	NNP	PERSON	Oliver	pobj	1	SENT_107	[p2l1941t2107r2147b2170],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_107	[p2l1941t2107r2147b2170],
6	Jr.	NNP	O	Jr.	appos	4	SENT_107	[p2l80t2190r172b2250],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_107	[p2l80t2190r172b2250],
8	W.	NNP	O	W.	nn	9	SENT_107	[p2l199t2190r282b2240],
9	J	NNP	O	J	_	0	SENT_107	[p2l309t2190r337b2244],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_107	[p2l345t2231r355b2241],

1	Sando	NNP	PERSON	Sando	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l384t2188r585b2249],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l384t2188r585b2249],
3	S.	NNP	PERSON	S.	nn	5	SENT_108	[p2l615t2188r664b2240],
4	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	5	SENT_108	[p2l693t2189r763b2240],
5	Caims	NNP	PERSON	Caims	appos	1	SENT_108	[p2l790t2186r1001b2249],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l790t2186r1001b2249],
7	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	9	SENT_108	[p2l1030t2187r1096b2239],
8	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	9	SENT_108	[p2l1124t2187r1193b2239],
9	Coatcs	NNP	PERSON	Coatcs	conj_and	5	SENT_108	[p2l1220t2187r1438b2248],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l1220t2187r1438b2248],
11	I.	NNP	PERSON	I.	nn	13	SENT_108	[p2l1467t2188r1505b2239],
12	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	13	SENT_108	[p2l1533t2186r1603b2239],
13	Macintyrc	NNP	PERSON	Macintyrc	conj_and	5	SENT_108	[p2l1632t2185r1954b2250],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l1632t2185r1954b2250],
15	F.	NNP	PERSON	F.	nn	17	SENT_108	[p2l1983t2187r2037b2238],
16	M.	NNP	PERSON	M.	nn	17	SENT_108	[p2l2067t2187r2145b2238],
17	Bayer	NNP	PERSON	Bayer	conj_and	5	SENT_108	[p2l83t2267r270b2330],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l83t2267r270b2330],
19	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l296t2266r407b2318],
20	J	NN	O	j	conj_and	5	SENT_108	[p2l431t2266r459b2320],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_108	[p2l467t2307r477b2317],

1	E.	NNP	PERSON	E.	nn	2	SENT_109	[p2l506t2266r562b2317],
2	Sorauf	NNP	PERSON	Sorauf	_	0	SENT_109	[p2l592t2263r795b2317],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	4	SENT_109	[p2l811t2265r987b2327],
4	cds	NNS	O	cd	dep	2	SENT_109	[p2l811t2265r987b2327],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_109	[p2l811t2265r987b2327],
6	)	SYM	O	)	dep	2	SENT_109	[p2l811t2265r987b2327],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l811t2265r987b2327],
2	Recent	JJ	O	recent	dep	3	SENT_110	[p2l1016t2266r1223b2316],
3	Advances	NNS	O	advance	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l1248t2264r1540b2316],
4	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l1566t2263r1621b2315],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_110	[p2l1648t2264r1740b2316],
6	Palcobiology	NN	O	palcobiology	prep_in	3	SENT_110	[p2l1766t2262r2151b2327],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l81t2343r192b2395],
8	Geology	NN	O	geology	prep_in	3	SENT_110	[p2l223t2342r473b2406],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l504t2341r572b2394],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_110	[p2l592t2343r685b2394],
11	Cnidaria	NNP	LOCATION	Cnidaria	prep_of	6	SENT_110	[p2l715t2340r993b2403],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l715t2340r993b2403],
13	Fourth	JJ	ORDINAL	fourth	advmod	3	SENT_110	[p2l1027t2342r1232b2394],
14	Intcmational	NNP	O	Intcmational	nn	15	SENT_110	[p2l1265t2340r1655b2393],
15	Symposium	NNP	O	Symposium	dep	3	SENT_110	[p2l1689t2339r2043b2405],
16	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l2076t2355r2148b2393],
17	Fossil	NNP	O	Fossil	nn	19	SENT_110	[p2l83t2419r256b2471],
18	Cnidaria	NNP	O	Cnidaria	nn	19	SENT_110	[p2l281t2418r543b2472],
19	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	Washington	prep_on	15	SENT_110	[p2l568t2418r947b2482],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l568t2418r947b2482],
21	Proceedings	NNP	O	Proceedings	appos	19	SENT_110	[p2l975t2418r1350b2482],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_110	[p2l975t2418r1350b2482],

1	Palacontographica	NNP	O	Palacontographica	nn	2	SENT_111	[p2l1378t2417r1932b2481],
2	Americana	NNS	O	americana	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l1956t2417r2148b2470, p2l83t2494r255b2555],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l1956t2417r2148b2470, p2l83t2494r255b2555],
4	number	NN	O	number	appos	2	SENT_111	[p2l282t2495r520b2546],
5	5_4	CD	NUMBER	5_4	num	4	SENT_111	[p2l545t2495r630b2551],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_111	[p2l545t2495r630b2551],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_112	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_113	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_114	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_115	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_116	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_116	[p2l7t2598r159b2624],

1	1990	CD	DATE	1990	_	0	SENT_117	[p2l228t2572r383b2624],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_117	[p2l228t2572r383b2624],

1	Corals	NNS	O	coral	_	0	SENT_118	[p2l442t2572r635b2624],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_118	[p2l663t2572r774b2624],
3	corallinc	NN	O	corallinc	nn	4	SENT_118	[p2l803t2571r1063b2624],
4	sponges	NNS	O	sponge	conj_and	1	SENT_118	[p2l1092t2586r1341b2634],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_118	[p2l1092t2586r1341b2634],
6	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	1	SENT_118	[p2l1372t2586r1424b2634],
7	45-65	CD	NUMBER	45-65	num	6	SENT_118	[p2l1457t2572r1655b2623],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_118	[p2l1457t2572r1655b2623],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_119	[p2l1689t2572r1754b2623],
2	J	NN	O	j	pobj	1	SENT_119	[p2l1782t2572r1810b2626],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_119	[p2l1817t2613r1827b2623],

1	G.	NNP	PERSON	G.	nn	3	SENT_120	[p2l1861t2572r1930b2623],
2	Carter	NNP	PERSON	Carter	nn	3	SENT_120	[p2l1962t2572r2152b2624],
3	(	NN	O	(	nsubj	4	SENT_120	[p2l77t2649r226b2711],
4	ed	VBD	O	ed	_	0	SENT_120	[p2l77t2649r226b2711],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_120	[p2l77t2649r226b2711],
6	)	SYM	O	)	dep	4	SENT_120	[p2l77t2649r226b2711],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p2l77t2649r226b2711],
2	Skeletal	JJ	O	skeletal	amod	3	SENT_121	[p2l253t2648r485b2700],
3	Biomincralization	NN	O	biomincralization	_	0	SENT_121	[p2l511t2647r1072b2700],
4	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_121	[p2l511t2647r1072b2700],
5	Pattems	NNP	O	Pattems	dep	3	SENT_121	[p2l1099t2649r1362b2709],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p2l1099t2649r1362b2709],
7	Processes	NNP	O	Processes	dep	3	SENT_121	[p2l1388t2649r1673b2700],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_121	[p2l1694t2648r1804b2700],
9	Evolutionary	NNP	O	Evolutionary	nn	10	SENT_121	[p2l1829t2647r2149b2700, p2l76t2741r171b2790],
10	Trends	NNPS	O	Trends	dep	3	SENT_121	[p2l195t2726r422b2778],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_121	[p2l195t2726r422b2778],

1	Van	NNP	PERSON	Van	nn	3	SENT_122	[p2l450t2727r573b2778],
2	Nostrand	NNP	PERSON	Nostrand	nn	3	SENT_122	[p2l599t2726r882b2778],
3	Reinhold	NNP	PERSON	Reinhold	_	0	SENT_122	[p2l909t2726r1202b2787],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_122	[p2l909t2726r1202b2787],
5	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	6	SENT_122	[p2l1229t2727r1366b2777],
6	York	NNP	LOCATION	York	appos	3	SENT_122	[p2l1390t2726r1560b2787],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_122	[p2l1390t2726r1560b2787],
8	Volume	NN	O	volume	appos	6	SENT_122	[p2l1586t2727r1826b2778],
9	I-II	CD	NUMBER	i-ii	num	8	SENT_122	[p2l1851t2727r1976b2777],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_122	[p2l1851t2727r1976b2777],

1	WILBUR	NNP	LOCATION	WILBUR	_	0	SENT_123	[p2l10t2804r265b2863],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_123	[p2l10t2804r265b2863],
3	K.	NNP	O	K.	nn	4	SENT_123	[p2l295t2803r362b2853],
4	M.	NNP	O	M.	appos	1	SENT_123	[p2l393t2803r475b2853],
5	1984	CD	DATE	1984	dep	4	SENT_123	[p2l537t2802r693b2854],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_123	[p2l537t2802r693b2854],

1	Many	JJ	O	many	amod	2	SENT_124	[p2l750t2802r923b2865],
2	minerals	NNS	O	mineral	_	0	SENT_124	[p2l952t2801r1226b2863],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_124	[p2l952t2801r1226b2863],
4	several	JJ	O	several	amod	5	SENT_124	[p2l1255t2803r1461b2854],
5	phyla	NN	O	phylum	appos	2	SENT_124	[p2l1489t2803r1670b2866],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_124	[p2l1489t2803r1670b2866],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_124	[p2l1697t2802r1807b2854],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	10	SENT_124	[p2l1832t2817r1864b2854],
9	few	JJ	O	few	amod	10	SENT_124	[p2l1891t2801r1993b2854],
10	considerations	NNS	O	consideration	appos	2	SENT_124	[p2l2019t2817r2148b2854, p2l78t2879r422b2932],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_124	[p2l2019t2817r2148b2854, p2l78t2879r422b2932],

1	American	JJ	MISC	american	amod	2	SENT_125	[p2l451t2879r745b2931],
2	Zoologist	NN	MISC	zoologist	_	0	SENT_125	[p2l769t2879r1067b2942],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_125	[p2l769t2879r1067b2942],
4	24:839	CD	NUMBER	24:839	num	5	SENT_125	[p2l1095t2879r1465b2932],
5	-845	CD	NUMBER	-845	appos	2	SENT_125	[p2l1095t2879r1465b2932],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_125	[p2l1095t2879r1465b2932],

1	WILLENZ	NNP	LOCATION	WILLENZ	nn	3	SENT_126	[p2l10t2954r289b3014],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_126	[p2l10t2954r289b3014],
3	P.	NNP	O	P.	_	0	SENT_126	[p2l319t2955r395b3014],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_126	[p2l319t2955r395b3014],
5	AND	NNP	O	AND	nn	8	SENT_126	[p2l423t2967r548b3004],
6	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	8	SENT_126	[p2l573t2955r656b3005],
7	D.	NNP	PERSON	D.	nn	8	SENT_126	[p2l687t2956r756b3005],
8	HARTMAN	NNP	PERSON	HARTMAN	appos	3	SENT_126	[p2l788t2956r1106b3006],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_126	[p2l788t2956r1106b3006],

1	1985	CD	DATE	1985	_	0	SENT_127	[p2l1171t2956r1327b3007],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_127	[p2l1171t2956r1327b3007],

1	Calci?cation	NN	O	calci?cation	nn	2	SENT_128	[p2l1384t2956r1760b3009],
2	rate	NN	O	rate	nsubj	6	SENT_128	[p2l1788t2967r1900b3010],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l1926t2958r1994b3010],
4	Ceratoporella	NN	O	ceratoporellum	nn	5	SENT_128	[p2l2016t2959r2142b3010, p2l76t3028r377b3092],
5	nicholsoni	NNS	O	nicholsonus	prep_of	2	SENT_128	[p2l400t3028r704b3083],
6	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l723t3030r1002b3093],
7	Porifera	NNP	O	Porifera	dobj	6	SENT_128	[p2l723t3030r1002b3093],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l723t3030r1002b3093],
9	Sclcrospongiae	FW	O	sclcrospongiae	nn	10	SENT_128	[p2l1027t3032r1509b3097],
10	)	FW	O	)	dep	7	SENT_128	[p2l1027t3032r1509b3097],
11	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l1027t3032r1509b3097],
12	an	DT	O	a	dep	7	SENT_128	[p2l1532t3049r1602b3086],
13	in	FW	O	in	nn	14	SENT_128	[p2l1628t3035r1683b3086],
14	situ	FW	O	situ	advmod	15	SENT_128	[p2l1703t3035r1810b3086],
15	study	NN	O	study	dep	12	SENT_128	[p2l1833t3036r1994b3099],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l2014t3034r2144b3088],
17	calcein	NN	O	calcein	prep_with	15	SENT_128	[p2l76t3105r299b3167],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l76t3105r299b3167],
19	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	7	SENT_128	[p2l334t3121r384b3167],
20	113-118	CD	NUMBER	113-118	num	19	SENT_128	[p2l430t3106r696b3159],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_128	[p2l430t3106r696b3159],

1	Fifth	JJ	ORGANIZATION	fifth	amod	5	SENT_129	[p2l732t3106r876b3159],
2	Intcmational	JJ	ORGANIZATION	intcmational	amod	5	SENT_129	[p2l911t3107r1302b3161],
3	Coral	NN	ORGANIZATION	coral	nn	5	SENT_129	[p2l1333t3109r1496b3161],
4	Reef	NN	ORGANIZATION	reef	nn	5	SENT_129	[p2l1531t3109r1676b3162],
5	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Congress	_	0	SENT_129	[p2l1697t3111r1982b3174],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_129	[p2l1697t3111r1982b3174],
7	Proceedings	NNP	O	Proceedings	nn	9	SENT_129	[p2l2017t3113r2144b3164, p2l76t3185r345b3250],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_129	[p2l2017t3113r2144b3164, p2l76t3185r345b3250],
9	Tahiti	NNP	LOCATION	Tahiti	appos	5	SENT_129	[p2l373t3185r573b3248],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_129	[p2l373t3185r573b3248],
11	volume	NN	O	volume	appos	9	SENT_129	[p2l601t3188r827b3239],
12	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	11	SENT_129	[p2l855t3189r902b3239],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_129	[p2l855t3189r902b3239],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_130	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_131	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_131	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_132	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_133	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_133	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_134	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_134	[p2l7t3289r162b3324],
3	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_134	[p2l184t3276r311b3314],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_134	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_135	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_135	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_136	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_137	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_137	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],

1	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_138	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_138	[p2l329t3289r483b3315],

1	1989	CD	DATE	1989	_	0	SENT_139	[p2l543t3263r699b3315],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_139	[p2l543t3263r699b3315],

1	Micromorphology	NNP	O	Micromorphology	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l751t3262r1301b3327],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l1321t3264r1431b3316],
3	ultrastructure	NN	O	ultrastructure	conj_and	1	SENT_140	[p2l1455t3264r1860b3316],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l1880t3263r1947b3316],
5	Caribbean	NNP	LOCATION	Caribbean	nn	6	SENT_140	[p2l1958t3263r2148b3316, p2l77t3340r218b3392],
6	sclerosponges	NNS	O	sclerosponge	prep_of	3	SENT_140	[p2l242t3340r667b3403],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l242t3340r667b3403],
8	I.	NN	PERSON	i.	nn	10	SENT_140	[p2l691t3341r730b3391],
9	Ceratoporella	NNP	PERSON	Ceratoporella	nn	10	SENT_140	[p2l758t3337r1163b3402],
10	nicholsoni	NNS	O	nicholsonus	prep_of	3	SENT_140	[p2l1186t3338r1490b3392],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l1507t3340r1618b3392],
12	Stromatospongia	FW	LOCATION	stromatospongia	nn	15	SENT_140	[p2l1639t3340r2151b3404],
13	norae	FW	O	norae	nn	15	SENT_140	[p2l81t3432r250b3469],
14	(	FW	O	(	nn	15	SENT_140	[p2l270t3416r810b3480],
15	Ceratoporellidae	FW	O	ceratoporellidae	conj_and	6	SENT_140	[p2l270t3416r810b3480],
16	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l270t3416r810b3480],
17	Porifera	NN	O	porifera	nn	18	SENT_140	[p2l838t3416r1116b3480],
18	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_140	[p2l838t3416r1116b3480],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_140	[p2l838t3416r1116b3480],

1	Marine	NNP	O	Marine	nn	2	SENT_141	[p2l1144t3417r1362b3470],
2	Biology	NNP	O	Biology	_	0	SENT_141	[p2l1387t3417r1630b3482],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_141	[p2l1387t3417r1630b3482],
4	103:387	CD	NUMBER	103:387	num	5	SENT_141	[p2l1665t3418r2064b3471],
5	-401	CD	NUMBER	-401	appos	2	SENT_141	[p2l1665t3418r2064b3471],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_141	[p2l1665t3418r2064b3471],

1	WOOD	NN	O	wood	_	0	SENT_142	[p2l9t3495r218b3554],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_142	[p2l9t3495r218b3554],
3	R.	NNP	O	R.	appos	1	SENT_142	[p2l249t3495r314b3544],
4	1991	CD	DATE	1991	num	3	SENT_142	[p2l378t3494r533b3545],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_142	[p2l378t3494r533b3545],

1	Non-spicular	JJ	O	non-spicular	amod	2	SENT_143	[p2l589t3493r987b3554],
2	biomineralization	NN	O	biomineralization	_	0	SENT_143	[p2l1010t3493r1548b3545],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_143	[p2l1575t3494r1631b3544],
4	calci?ed	JJ	O	calci?ed	amod	5	SENT_143	[p2l1658t3494r1903b3546],
5	demosponges	NNS	O	demosponge	prep_in	2	SENT_143	[p2l1928t3495r2148b3546, p2l76t3585r299b3634],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_143	[p2l1928t3495r2148b3546, p2l76t3585r299b3634],
7	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	5	SENT_143	[p2l332t3585r383b3633],
8	323-340	CD	NUMBER	323-340	num	7	SENT_143	[p2l420t3570r693b3622],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_143	[p2l420t3570r693b3622],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_144	[p2l727t3570r792b3622],
2	J	NN	O	j	pobj	1	SENT_144	[p2l820t3571r849b3625],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_144	[p2l855t3612r866b3622],

1	Reitner	NNP	O	Reitner	_	0	SENT_145	[p2l901t3570r1126b3622],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_145	[p2l1153t3571r1263b3623],
3	H.	NNP	PERSON	H.	nn	6	SENT_145	[p2l1295t3572r1364b3622],
4	Keupp	NNP	PERSON	Keupp	nn	6	SENT_145	[p2l1398t3571r1599b3633],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_145	[p2l1628t3571r1803b3634],
6	cds	NNS	O	cd	conj_and	1	SENT_145	[p2l1628t3571r1803b3634],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_145	[p2l1628t3571r1803b3634],
8	)	SYM	O	)	dep	1	SENT_145	[p2l1628t3571r1803b3634],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_146	[p2l1628t3571r1803b3634],
2	Fossil	NNP	O	Fossil	_	0	SENT_146	[p2l1836t3570r2009b3623],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_146	[p2l2039t3572r2149b3624],
4	Recent	JJ	O	recent	amod	5	SENT_146	[p2l78t3648r286b3699],
5	Sponges	NNS	O	sponge	conj_and	2	SENT_146	[p2l311t3647r570b3711],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_146	[p2l311t3647r570b3711],

1	Springer-Verlag	NNP	LOCATION	Springer-Verlag	_	0	SENT_147	[p2l598t3647r1087b3711],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_147	[p2l598t3647r1087b3711],
3	Berlin	NNP	LOCATION	Berlin	nn	5	SENT_147	[p2l1116t3647r1313b3709],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_147	[p2l1116t3647r1313b3709],
5	Heidelberg	NNP	LOCATION	Heidelberg	appos	1	SENT_147	[p2l1341t3647r1683b3712],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_147	[p2l1341t3647r1683b3712],

1	ACCEPTED	VBN	O	accept	_	0	SENT_148	[p3l7t32r312b84],
2	1	CD	DATE	1	num	3	SENT_148	[p3l342t34r359b83],
3	JULY	NN	DATE	july	tmod	1	SENT_148	[p3l393t34r542b87],
4	1994	CD	DATE	1994	dep	3	SENT_148	[p3l575t33r714b84],

1	EARLY	NNP	O	EARLY	nn	4	SENT_149	[p3l313t162r526b206],
2	DEVONIAN	NNP	O	DEVONIAN	nn	4	SENT_149	[p3l546t163r882b207],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	4	SENT_149	[p3l902t163r1222b218],
4	PRAGIAN	NNP	O	PRAGIAN	_	0	SENT_149	[p3l902t163r1222b218],
5	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	6	SENT_149	[p3l902t163r1222b218],
6	GASTROPODS	NNPS	O	GASTROPODS	dep	4	SENT_149	[p3l1242t164r1655b209],
7	FROM	IN	O	from	amod	6	SENT_149	[p3l1676t166r1857b210],

1	KYRGYZSTAN	NNP	LOCATION	KYRGYZSTAN	_	0	SENT_150	[p3l615t231r1050b276],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	1	SENT_150	[p3l1069t231r1380b286],
3	CENTRAL	NNP	O	CENTRAL	nn	4	SENT_150	[p3l1069t231r1380b286],
4	ASIA	NNP	O	ASIA	nsubj	5	SENT_150	[p3l1398t232r1558b287],
5	)	VBD	O	)	rcmod	1	SENT_150	[p3l1398t232r1558b287],
6	ALEXANDER	NNP	PERSON	ALEXANDER	nn	8	SENT_150	[p3l593t325r845b354],
7	P.	NNP	PERSON	P.	nn	8	SENT_150	[p3l859t327r889b354],
8	GUBANOV	NNP	PERSON	GUBANOV	dobj	5	SENT_150	[p3l904t326r1119b361],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_150	[p3l904t326r1119b361],
10	ROBERT	NNP	PERSON	ROBERT	nn	12	SENT_150	[p3l1134t327r1296b356],
11	B.	NNP	PERSON	B.	nn	12	SENT_150	[p3l1309t328r1341b356],
12	BLODGETT	NNP	PERSON	BLODGETT	appos	8	SENT_150	[p3l1356t328r1581b362],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_150	[p3l1356t328r1581b362],

1	AND	CC	O	and	cc	2	SENT_151	[p3l789t371r858b392],
2	VLADIMIR	NNP	PERSON	VLADIMIR	dep	4	SENT_151	[p3l871t364r1078b393],
3	N.	NNP	PERSON	N.	dep	2	SENT_151	[p3l1091t366r1129b394],
4	LYTOCHKIN	NNP	PERSON	LYTOCHKIN	_	0	SENT_151	[p3l1144t366r1387b394],

1	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	_	0	SENT_152	[p3l551t412r674b438],
2	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_152	[p3l684t412r718b438],
3	Geology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geology	nn	6	SENT_152	[p3l725t413r854b445],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_152	[p3l725t413r854b445],
5	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	6	SENT_152	[p3l868t413r1024b445],
6	Avenue	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Avenue	prep_of	1	SENT_152	[p3l1035t413r1148b440],
7	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	6	SENT_152	[p3l1160t414r1184b445],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_152	[p3l1160t414r1184b445],
9	Novosibirsk	NNP	LOCATION	Novosibirsk	appos	6	SENT_152	[p3l1197t414r1378b441],
10	630090	CD	NUMBER	630090	num	9	SENT_152	[p3l1390t415r1506b446],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_152	[p3l1390t415r1506b446],
12	Russia	NNP	LOCATION	Russia	appos	9	SENT_152	[p3l1520t415r1624b446],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_152	[p3l1520t415r1624b446],

1	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	U.S.	nn	3	SENT_153	[p3l601t450r663b475],
2	Geological	NNP	O	Geological	nn	3	SENT_153	[p3l677t450r832b481],
3	Survey	NNP	O	Survey	_	0	SENT_153	[p3l844t450r953b482],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_153	[p3l844t450r953b482],
5	Branch	NNP	O	Branch	dep	3	SENT_153	[p3l967t451r1070b476],
6	of	IN	O	of	dep	5	SENT_153	[p3l1081t451r1115b477],
7	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	pobj	6	SENT_153	[p3l1122t452r1311b483],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_153	[p3l1322t452r1375b478],
9	Stratigraphy	NNP	O	Stratigraphy	pobj	6	SENT_153	[p3l1388t452r1574b484],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_153	[p3l1388t452r1574b484],

1	970	CD	NUMBER	970	_	0	SENT_154	[p3l717t488r770b514],
2	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	7	SENT_154	[p3l783t488r911b515],
3	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	nn	7	SENT_154	[p3l923t489r1028b520],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p3l923t489r1028b520],
5	Reston	NNP	LOCATION	Reston	appos	7	SENT_154	[p3l1041t490r1151b520],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p3l1041t490r1151b520],
7	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	Virginia	dep	1	SENT_154	[p3l1163t489r1282b521],
8	22092	CD	NUMBER	22092	num	7	SENT_154	[p3l1295t490r1393b521],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_154	[p3l1295t490r1393b521],
10	and	CC	O	and	advmod	1	SENT_154	[p3l1405t491r1459b517],

1	PKF	NNP	O	PKF	_	0	SENT_155	[p3l582t526r652b550],
2	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	1	SENT_155	[p3l662t526r824b557],
3	Kyrtash	NNP	O	Kyrtash	dep	1	SENT_155	[p3l662t526r824b557],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_155	[p3l662t526r824b557],
5	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	7	SENT_155	[p3l662t526r824b557],
6	Ehrkindyle	NNP	O	Ehrkindyle	nn	7	SENT_155	[p3l837t526r998b558],
7	Avenue	NNP	O	Avenue	appos	3	SENT_155	[p3l1009t526r1122b553],
8	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	7	SENT_155	[p3l1133t527r1158b557],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_155	[p3l1133t527r1158b557],
10	Bishkek	NNP	LOCATION	Bishkek	appos	3	SENT_155	[p3l1172t527r1287b553],
11	720039	CD	NUMBER	720039	num	10	SENT_155	[p3l1300t528r1416b558],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_155	[p3l1300t528r1416b558],
13	Kyrgyzstan	NNP	LOCATION	Kyrgyzstan	appos	3	SENT_155	[p3l1430t529r1592b560],

1	ABSTRACl	NN	O	abstracl	_	0	SENT_156	[p3l111t652r319b678],
2	?	NN	O	?	dep	1	SENT_156	[p3l111t652r319b678],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_156	[p3l111t652r319b678],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_157	[p3l111t652r319b678],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_157	[p3l111t652r319b678],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_158	[p3l111t652r319b678],
2	gastropod	NN	O	gastropod	nn	3	SENT_158	[p3l329t653r474b684],
3	assemblage	NN	O	assemblage	nsubjpass	5	SENT_158	[p3l485t653r650b685],
4	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_158	[p3l661t653r684b679],
5	described	VBN	O	describe	_	0	SENT_158	[p3l694t653r834b679],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_158	[p3l844t653r915b679],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_158	[p3l926t654r971b679],
8	middle	JJ	O	middle	amod	13	SENT_158	[p3l982t653r1085b680],
9	Lower	JJR	O	lower	dep	8	SENT_158	[p3l1095t654r1188b680],
10	Devonian	JJ	O	devonian	amod	13	SENT_158	[p3l1198t654r1342b680],
11	(	NN	O	(	nn	13	SENT_158	[p3l1353t654r1485b686],
12	Pragian	JJ	O	pragian	amod	13	SENT_158	[p3l1353t654r1485b686],
13	)	NN	O	)	prep_from	5	SENT_158	[p3l1353t654r1485b686],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_158	[p3l1495t654r1528b681],
15	Alai	NNP	PERSON	Alai	nn	16	SENT_158	[p3l1533t654r1594b681],
16	Ridge	NNP	PERSON	Ridge	prep_of	13	SENT_158	[p3l1605t655r1698b687],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_158	[p3l1605t655r1698b687],
18	Kyrgyzstan	NNP	LOCATION	Kyrgyzstan	appos	16	SENT_158	[p3l1710t656r1882b687],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_158	[p3l1710t656r1882b687],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubj	2	SENT_159	[p3l1894t656r1917b682],
2	includes	VBZ	O	include	_	0	SENT_159	[p3l1927t655r2047b682],
3	eight	CD	NUMBER	eight	num	4	SENT_159	[p3l111t690r183b721],
4	species	NNS	O	species	dobj	2	SENT_159	[p3l193t690r303b721],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_159	[p3l193t690r303b721],
6	six	CD	NUMBER	six	nsubj	10	SENT_159	[p3l315t690r355b716],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_159	[p3l365t690r398b716],
8	which	WDT	O	which	prep_of	6	SENT_159	[p3l403t690r491b716],
9	are	VBP	O	be	cop	10	SENT_159	[p3l501t698r546b716],
10	new	JJ	O	new	rcmod	4	SENT_159	[p3l556t698r622b716],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_159	[p3l556t698r622b716],

1	Two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	3	SENT_160	[p3l633t691r700b716],
2	new	JJ	O	new	amod	3	SENT_160	[p3l709t698r768b716],
3	genera	NN	O	genus	nsubjpass	5	SENT_160	[p3l777t698r873b722],
4	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_160	[p3l882t699r927b717],
5	established	VBN	O	establish	_	0	SENT_160	[p3l936t691r1106b722],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_160	[p3l936t691r1106b722],
7	Alaionema	NN	LOCATION	alaionema	dobj	5	SENT_160	[p3l1115t691r1276b717],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_160	[p3l1285t692r1339b718],
9	Barroisocaulus	NN	O	barroisocaulus	dobj	5	SENT_160	[p3l1348t692r1571b718],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_160	[p3l1348t692r1571b718],

1	Newly	RB	O	newly	advmod	2	SENT_161	[p3l1583t693r1677b724],
2	named	VBN	O	name	amod	3	SENT_161	[p3l1686t693r1785b719],
3	species	NNS	O	species	nsubj	9	SENT_161	[p3l1796t693r1897b723],
4	belonging	VBG	O	belong	partmod	3	SENT_161	[p3l1906t694r2048b725],
5	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_161	[p3l111t731r140b753],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_161	[p3l154t728r199b753],
7	above	JJ	O	above	amod	8	SENT_161	[p3l212t728r301b753],
8	genera	NN	O	genus	prep_to	4	SENT_161	[p3l313t735r409b759],
9	include	VBP	O	include	_	0	SENT_161	[p3l423t727r538b754],
10	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_161	[p3l423t727r538b754],
11	Alaionema	NN	O	alaionema	nn	12	SENT_161	[p3l550t727r712b754],
12	kyrgyzensis	NN	O	kyrgyzensis	dobj	9	SENT_161	[p3l725t727r893b759],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_161	[p3l905t729r959b755],
14	Barroisocaulus	NN	O	barroisocaulus	nn	15	SENT_161	[p3l971t728r1189b755],
15	oliveri	NNS	O	oliverus	conj_and	12	SENT_161	[p3l1202t728r1296b755],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_161	[p3l1202t728r1296b755],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_162	[p3l1312t730r1342b755],
2	addition	NN	O	addition	prep_in	13	SENT_162	[p3l1356t729r1487b760],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_162	[p3l1356t729r1487b760],
4	four	CD	NUMBER	four	num	6	SENT_162	[p3l1502t729r1562b756],
5	new	JJ	O	new	amod	6	SENT_162	[p3l1575t737r1633b756],
6	species	NNS	O	species	nsubjpass	13	SENT_162	[p3l1647t730r1748b761],
7	belonging	VBG	O	belong	partmod	6	SENT_162	[p3l1761t730r1902b762],
8	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_162	[p3l1915t735r1944b757],
9	extant	JJ	O	extant	amod	10	SENT_162	[p3l1957t735r2047b757],
10	genera	NN	O	genus	prep_to	7	SENT_162	[p3l111t771r207b796],
11	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_162	[p3l215t772r260b790],
12	also	RB	O	also	advmod	13	SENT_162	[p3l268t765r326b790],
13	described	VBN	O	describe	_	0	SENT_162	[p3l335t764r483b791],
14	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_162	[p3l335t764r483b791],
15	Omphalocirrus	NN	O	omphalocirrus	nn	16	SENT_162	[p3l494t764r714b796],
16	kaukensis	NN	O	kaukensis	dep	13	SENT_162	[p3l722t764r871b794],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_162	[p3l722t764r871b794],

1	Ruedemannia	NN	O	ruedemannium	nn	2	SENT_163	[p3l882t765r1088b792],
2	tienshanica	NN	O	tienshanica	_	0	SENT_163	[p3l1097t765r1269b795],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_163	[p3l1097t765r1269b795],
4	Oriostoma	NN	O	oriostoma	nn	5	SENT_163	[p3l1281t767r1435b793],
5	sarydalchaensis	NN	O	sarydalchaensis	appos	2	SENT_163	[p3l1442t766r1676b798],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_163	[p3l1442t766r1676b798],

1	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_164	[p3l1687t768r1742b794],
2	Goniasma	NNP	PERSON	Goniasma	dep	1	SENT_164	[p3l1752t768r1916b794],
3	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_164	[p3l1752t768r1916b794],

1	asiatica	NN	O	asiatica	_	0	SENT_165	[p3l1924t769r2043b794],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_165	[p3l1924t769r2043b794],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_166	[p3l413t890r655b911],

1	ALEOZOIC	NNP	O	ALEOZOIC	nn	2	SENT_167	[p3l72t943r226b964],
2	DEPOSITS	NNS	O	deposit	nsubj	13	SENT_167	[p3l238t943r382b965],
3	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l395t945r436b964],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_167	[p3l450t937r501b965],
5	southern	JJ	O	southern	amod	6	SENT_167	[p3l515t937r658b965],
6	slope	NN	O	slope	prep_on	2	SENT_167	[p3l672t937r756b971],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l770t937r807b965],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_167	[p3l815t938r865b965],
9	Alai	NNP	LOCATION	Alai	nn	10	SENT_167	[p3l878t937r947b966],
10	Ridge	NNP	LOCATION	Ridge	prep_of	6	SENT_167	[p3l961t938r1056b972],
11	are	VBP	O	be	cop	13	SENT_167	[p3l93t987r144b1006],
12	richly	RB	O	richly	advmod	13	SENT_167	[p3l161t978r256b1013],
13	fossiliferous	JJ	O	fossiliferous	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l273t978r481b1012],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l273t978r481b1012],
15	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l500t979r554b1007],
16	until	IN	O	until	dep	21	SENT_167	[p3l571t979r647b1007],
17	recently	RB	DATE	recently	nsubjpass	21	SENT_167	[p3l665t980r796b1014],
18	have	VBP	O	have	aux	21	SENT_167	[p3l812t980r891b1007],
19	not	RB	O	not	neg	21	SENT_167	[p3l909t984r963b1008],
20	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	21	SENT_167	[p3l980t980r1056b1008],
21	studied	VBN	O	study	conj_but	13	SENT_167	[p3l11t1023r131b1051],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l143t1023r175b1050],
23	detail	NN	O	detail	prep_in	21	SENT_167	[p3l186t1023r287b1051],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_167	[p3l186t1023r287b1051],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_168	[p3l300t1023r329b1051],
2	moderately	RB	O	moderately	advmod	3	SENT_168	[p3l341t1024r528b1057],
3	diverse	JJ	O	diverse	amod	4	SENT_168	[p3l539t1024r658b1052],
4	assemblage	NN	O	assemblage	nsubjpass	10	SENT_168	[p3l669t1024r854b1058],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l866t1024r904b1052],
6	wellpreserved	JJ	O	wellpreserved	amod	7	SENT_168	[p3l909t1025r1055b1058, p3l10t1069r117b1096],
7	gastropods	NNS	O	gastropod	prep_of	4	SENT_168	[p3l134t1069r313b1103],
8	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	10	SENT_168	[p3l330t1069r385b1097],
9	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_168	[p3l403t1069r480b1097],
10	found	VBN	O	find	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l498t1069r594b1097],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l612t1069r644b1097],
12	addition	NN	O	addition	prep_in	10	SENT_168	[p3l661t1069r800b1097],
13	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l818t1074r850b1098],
14	other	JJ	O	other	amod	16	SENT_168	[p3l868t1070r955b1098],
15	fossil	JJ	O	fossil	amod	16	SENT_168	[p3l972t1070r1055b1099],
16	groups	NNS	O	group	prep_to	10	SENT_168	[p3l8t1122r119b1148],
17	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l135t1114r242b1142],
18	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	19	SENT_168	[p3l257t1115r420b1142],
19	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_within	16	SENT_168	[p3l435t1115r571b1148],
20	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l587t1123r628b1142],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_168	[p3l644t1115r694b1143],
22	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	23	SENT_168	[p3l710t1123r806b1149],
23	reaches	NNS	O	reach	prep_on	10	SENT_168	[p3l821t1116r942b1144],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l958t1116r995b1143],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_168	[p3l1006t1116r1056b1144],
26	Kauk	NNP	LOCATION	Kauk	nn	27	SENT_168	[p3l9t1159r100b1186],
27	River	NNP	LOCATION	River	prep_of	23	SENT_168	[p3l113t1159r215b1187],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_168	[p3l113t1159r215b1187],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_169	[p3l230t1159r304b1187],
2	gastropod	NN	O	gastropod	nn	3	SENT_169	[p3l316t1160r480b1193],
3	assemblage	NN	O	assemblage	nsubj	4	SENT_169	[p3l492t1160r678b1194],
4	has	VBZ	O	have	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l691t1160r745b1188],
5	much	RB	O	much	dobj	4	SENT_169	[p3l759t1161r851b1188],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l864t1160r896b1187],
7	common	JJ	O	common	amod	12	SENT_169	[p3l908t1169r1056b1188],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l9t1204r82b1232],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_169	[p3l92t1205r143b1233],
10	classical	JJ	O	classical	amod	11	SENT_169	[p3l153t1204r287b1233],
11	Koneprusy	NNP	MISC	Koneprusy	prep_with	7	SENT_169	[p3l298t1206r481b1239],
12	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	prep_in	5	SENT_169	[p3l491t1205r583b1234],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l592t1205r630b1234],
14	Bohemian	JJ	MISC	bohemian	prep_of	12	SENT_169	[p3l634t1206r804b1234],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l814t1207r875b1234],
16	along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l885t1206r974b1241],
17	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l983t1207r1056b1235],
18	other	JJ	O	other	amod	20	SENT_169	[p3l9t1250r97b1278],
19	co-occurring	VBG	O	co-occur	amod	20	SENT_169	[p3l108t1250r318b1284],
20	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	prep_along_with	24	SENT_169	[p3l330t1250r431b1279],
21	]	CD	NUMBER	]	num	22	SENT_169	[p3l330t1250r431b1279],
22	groups	NNS	O	group	nsubj	24	SENT_169	[p3l445t1258r556b1285],
23	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	24	SENT_169	[p3l569t1251r595b1279],
24	suggestive	JJ	O	suggestive	conj_and	4	SENT_169	[p3l609t1251r775b1285],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l788t1251r826b1279],
26	a	DT	O	a	det	28	SENT_169	[p3l833t1260r852b1280],
27	Pragian	JJ	MISC	pragian	amod	28	SENT_169	[p3l865t1252r990b1286],
28	age	NN	O	age	prep_of	24	SENT_169	[p3l1002t1260r1055b1286],
29	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l9t1295r57b1322],
30	the	DT	O	the	prep_for	28	SENT_169	[p3l69t1296r120b1323],
31	enclosing	VBG	O	enclose	partmod	30	SENT_169	[p3l133t1295r288b1330],
32	strata	NN	O	stratum	nn	34	SENT_169	[p3l300t1300r392b1323],
33	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	34	SENT_169	[p3l405t1296r586b1330],
34	Lytochkin	NNP	PERSON	Lytochkin	dobj	31	SENT_169	[p3l405t1296r586b1330],
35	et	FW	O	et	nn	36	SENT_169	[p3l599t1300r629b1324],
36	al.	FW	O	al.	dep	34	SENT_169	[p3l642t1297r689b1329],
37	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l642t1297r689b1329],
38	1993	CD	DATE	1993	num	39	SENT_169	[p3l709t1297r807b1330],
39	)	NN	O	)	appos	36	SENT_169	[p3l709t1297r807b1330],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_169	[p3l709t1297r807b1330],

1	GEOLOGIC	NNP	O	GEOLOGIC	_	0	SENT_170	[p3l1307t892r1466b914],
2	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_170	[p3l1479t892r1547b913],
3	STRATIGRAPHIC	NNP	O	STRATIGRAPHIC	conj_and	1	SENT_170	[p3l1560t893r1808b915],
4	SETTING	NNP	O	SETTING	dep	1	SENT_170	[p3l1822t894r1951b915],

1	Nappe-fold	JJ	O	nappe-fold	amod	2	SENT_171	[p3l1144t939r1333b973],
2	structures	NNS	O	structure	nsubjpass	20	SENT_171	[p3l1349t944r1510b968],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1527t940r1564b968],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_171	[p3l1575t941r1625b968],
5	southem	NN	O	southem	nn	6	SENT_171	[p3l1642t941r1785b969],
6	Tien-Shan	NNP	MISC	Tien-Shan	prep_of	2	SENT_171	[p3l1801t941r1974b969],
7	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_171	[p3l1990t950r2066b970],
8	generated	VBN	O	generate	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l2081t950r2150b976, p3l1106t982r1208b1009],
9	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1222t981r1330b1016],
10	late	JJ	O	late	amod	13	SENT_171	[p3l1344t982r1402b1010],
11	Hercynian	JJ	O	hercynian	amod	13	SENT_171	[p3l1416t982r1589b1017],
12	(	NN	O	(	nn	13	SENT_171	[p3l1603t982r1851b1017],
13	Carboniferous	NNP	O	Carboniferous	prep_during	8	SENT_171	[p3l1603t982r1851b1017],
14	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1865t987r1897b1011],
15	Permian	NNP	LOCATION	Permian	prep_to	8	SENT_171	[p3l1911t983r2063b1018],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	15	SENT_171	[p3l1911t983r2063b1018],
17	time	NN	O	time	tmod	8	SENT_171	[p3l2077t984r2151b1012],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1106t1027r1167b1054],
19	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	20	SENT_171	[p3l1181t1034r1258b1054],
20	built	VBN	O	build	conj_and	8	SENT_171	[p3l1272t1026r1349b1054],
21	up	RP	O	up	prt	20	SENT_171	[p3l1363t1035r1404b1060],
22	mainly	RB	O	mainly	advmod	20	SENT_171	[p3l1419t1027r1534b1061],
23	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1548t1027r1588b1061],
24	structural	JJ	O	structural	amod	25	SENT_171	[p3l1602t1028r1759b1056],
25	complexes	NNS	O	complex	agent	20	SENT_171	[p3l1773t1029r1946b1061],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1960t1028r1998b1056],
27	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	28	SENT_171	[p3l2007t1029r2092b1062],
28	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	prep_of	25	SENT_171	[p3l2106t1029r2150b1056, p3l1106t1071r1204b1100],
29	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1215t1076r1247b1100],
30	Late	JJ	O	late	amod	32	SENT_171	[p3l1259t1073r1330b1100],
31	Carboniferous	JJ	O	carboniferous	amod	32	SENT_171	[p3l1341t1072r1578b1101],
32	age	NN	O	age	prep_to	20	SENT_171	[p3l1588t1081r1650b1107],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_171	[p3l1588t1081r1650b1107],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1663t1074r1697b1100],
2	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	4	SENT_172	[p3l1708t1073r1786b1101],
3	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	4	SENT_172	[p3l1795t1078r1915b1107],
4	structure	NN	O	structure	prep_in	6	SENT_172	[p3l1926t1078r2071b1102],
5	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	6	SENT_172	[p3l2081t1075r2151b1108],
6	form	VBP	O	form	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1106t1117r1186b1145],
7	a	DT	O	a	det	8	SENT_172	[p3l1207t1126r1225b1145],
8	packet	NN	O	packet	nsubj	11	SENT_172	[p3l1245t1119r1353b1151],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1373t1118r1411b1146],
10	nappes	NNS	O	nappe	prep_of	8	SENT_172	[p3l1426t1127r1540b1152],
11	consisting	VBG	O	consist	dep	6	SENT_172	[p3l1561t1119r1726b1153],
12	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1746t1119r1783b1147],
13	overthrust	NN	O	overthrust	nn	14	SENT_172	[p3l1798t1120r1970b1148],
14	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	prep_of	11	SENT_172	[p3l1989t1121r2151b1148],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	16	SENT_172	[p3l1106t1162r1279b1196],
16	limestone	NN	O	limestone	tmod	11	SENT_172	[p3l1106t1162r1279b1196],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1291t1164r1353b1191],
18	dolomite	NN	O	dolomite	conj_and	16	SENT_172	[p3l1365t1163r1526b1197],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	20	SENT_172	[p3l1365t1163r1526b1197],
20	units	NNS	O	unit	dep	11	SENT_172	[p3l1538t1164r1620b1192],
21	that	WDT	O	that	nsubjpass	23	SENT_172	[p3l1633t1164r1697b1192],
22	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	23	SENT_172	[p3l1710t1173r1759b1192],
23	identi?ed	VBN	O	identi?ed	rcmod	20	SENT_172	[p3l1772t1164r1928b1193],
24	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1940t1173r1973b1193],
25	sediments	NNS	O	sediment	prep_as	23	SENT_172	[p3l1986t1165r2151b1194],
26	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1106t1208r1186b1236],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_172	[p3l1202t1209r1253b1237],
28	intemal	JJ	O	intemal	amod	29	SENT_172	[p3l1269t1208r1396b1237],
29	part	NN	O	part	prep_from	25	SENT_172	[p3l1413t1214r1479b1243],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1495t1209r1533b1237],
31	a	DT	O	a	det	33	SENT_172	[p3l1542t1218r1561b1238],
32	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	33	SENT_172	[p3l1576t1210r1738b1238],
33	shelf	NN	O	shelf	prep_of	29	SENT_172	[p3l1755t1210r1836b1239],
34	based	VBN	O	base	prep	23	SENT_172	[p3l1846t1211r1939b1239],
35	upon	IN	O	upon	pcomp	34	SENT_172	[p3l1955t1219r2039b1245],
36	palinspastic	JJ	O	palinspastic	amod	37	SENT_172	[p3l2054t1211r2150b1245, p3l1106t1253r1217b1287],
37	reconstruction	NN	O	reconstruction	pobj	35	SENT_172	[p3l1239t1254r1486b1282],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_172	[p3l1239t1254r1486b1282],

1	Among	IN	O	among	_	0	SENT_173	[p3l1509t1254r1633b1289],
2	these	DT	O	these	det	4	SENT_173	[p3l1654t1255r1737b1284],
3	structural	JJ	O	structural	amod	4	SENT_173	[p3l1760t1256r1916b1284],
4	complexes	NNS	O	complex	prep_among	12	SENT_173	[p3l1938t1257r2111b1290],
5	a	DT	O	a	det	6	SENT_173	[p3l2133t1265r2150b1285],
6	number	NN	O	number	nsubjpass	12	SENT_173	[p3l1105t1299r1236b1327],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_173	[p3l1254t1299r1292b1327],
8	lithofacial	JJ	O	lithofacial	amod	9	SENT_173	[p3l1306t1299r1471b1328],
9	units	NNS	O	unit	prep_of	6	SENT_173	[p3l1491t1300r1573b1328],
10	can	MD	O	can	aux	12	SENT_173	[p3l1592t1309r1648b1328],
11	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	12	SENT_173	[p3l1668t1301r1705b1329],
12	distinguished	VBN	O	distinguish	_	0	SENT_173	[p3l1725t1301r1953b1335],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_173	[p3l1725t1301r1953b1335],

1	These	DT	O	these	nsubj	2	SENT_174	[p3l1974t1302r2071b1330],
2	are	VBP	O	be	_	0	SENT_174	[p3l2090t1311r2148b1330],
3	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_174	[p3l2090t1311r2148b1330],

1	This	DT	O	this	_	0	SENT_175	[p3l509t1410r568b1434],
2	content	JJ	O	content	dep	1	SENT_175	[p3l578t1414r679b1434],
3	downloaded	VBN	O	download	dep	2	SENT_175	[p3l688t1410r855b1434],
4	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_175	[p3l864t1410r930b1434],
5	144.92.142.158	CD	NUMBER	144.92.142.158	prep_from	3	SENT_175	[p3l942t1410r1151b1434],
6	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_175	[p3l1162t1418r1196b1434],
7	Wed	NNP	TIME	Wed	prep_on	3	SENT_175	[p3l1205t1410r1276b1438],
8	,	,	TIME	,	_	0	SENT_175	[p3l1205t1410r1276b1438],
9	8	CD	TIME	8	num	10	SENT_175	[p3l1288t1410r1302b1434],
10	May	NNP	DATE	May	appos	7	SENT_175	[p3l1312t1411r1374b1441],
11	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	10	SENT_175	[p3l1385t1410r1450b1434],
12	16:27:48	CD	TIME	16:27:48	num	13	SENT_175	[p3l1464t1410r1581b1434],
13	PM	NN	TIME	pm	dep	10	SENT_175	[p3l1592t1411r1640b1434],

1	>	JJR	O	>	_	0	SENT_176	[p3l60t1719r92b1749],
2	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_176	[p3l60t1719r92b1749],
3	LL	NN	O	ll	dep	1	SENT_176	[p3l58t1755r91b1776],
4	!	.	O	!	_	0	SENT_176	[p3l58t1755r91b1776],

1	o	NN	O	o	nn	2	SENT_177	[p3l59t1781r93b1805],
2	E	NN	O	e	_	0	SENT_177	[p3l61t1831r92b1864],
3	Q	NNP	O	Q	dep	2	SENT_177	[p3l411t1871r467b1882],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_177	[p3l412t1883r467b1896],
5	_	IN	O	_	amod	3	SENT_177	[p3l412t1883r467b1896],

1	o	NN	O	o	nn	3	SENT_178	[p3l63t2374r94b2400],
2	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	3	SENT_178	[p3l125t2357r154b2399],
3	LL	NN	O	ll	_	0	SENT_178	[p3l124t2427r155b2451],
4	>	JJR	O	>	amod	6	SENT_178	[p3l67t2493r94b2519],
5	X	NN	O	x	nn	6	SENT_178	[p3l129t2584r159b2614],
6	w	NN	O	w	dep	3	SENT_178	[p3l64t2648r160b2683],
7	<	JJR	O	<	dep	6	SENT_178	[p3l64t2648r160b2683],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	3	SENT_178	[p3l132t2727r160b2753],

1	I111	NN	O	i111	_	0	SENT_179	[p3l179t2726r405b2749],

1	D	NN	O	d	_	0	SENT_180	[p3l65t2792r161b2832],
2	<	JJR	O	<	dep	1	SENT_180	[p3l65t2792r161b2832],

1	o	NN	O	o	nn	2	SENT_181	[p3l427t2853r459b2881],
2	X	NN	O	x	_	0	SENT_181	[p3l131t2879r160b2906],
3	<	JJR	O	<	dep	2	SENT_181	[p3l131t2948r161b2980],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_181	[p3l131t2948r161b2980],
5	D5	NN	O	d5	npadvmod	6	SENT_181	[p3l65t3008r100b3034],
6	at	IN	O	at	advmod	3	SENT_181	[p3l133t3019r162b3045],

1	<	JJR	O	<	dep	8	SENT_182	[p3l132t3091r163b3118],
2	_	CD	NUMBER	_	num	3	SENT_182	[p3l183t3118r193b3120],
3	Idolorgll?ud	NN	O	idolorgll?ud	dep	1	SENT_182	[p3l848t3091r1001b3146],
4	I	PRP	O	I	dep	8	SENT_182	[p3l856t3123r862b3145],
5	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	8	SENT_182	[p3l971t3126r985b3144],
6	L	NN	O	l	nn	8	SENT_182	[p3l66t3150r97b3170],
7	?	NN	O	?	nn	8	SENT_182	[p3l66t3150r97b3170],
8	X	NN	O	x	dep	12	SENT_182	[p3l132t3163r161b3188],
9	IE	JJ	O	ie	amod	10	SENT_182	[p3l182t3125r408b3177],
10	mes	NNS	O	me	dep	8	SENT_182	[p3l865t3128r915b3146],
11	one	CD	NUMBER	one	num	12	SENT_182	[p3l926t3128r969b3144],
12	limeslones	NNS	O	limeslone	_	0	SENT_182	[p3l845t3226r993b3252],

1	3	CD	NUMBER	3	_	0	SENT_183	[p3l69t3287r95b3328],
2	u-until	NN	O	u-until	dep	1	SENT_183	[p3l183t3285r404b3334],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_183	[p3l863t3338r867b3341],

1	i	FW	O	i	nn	3	SENT_184	[p3l349t3365r413b3388],
2	[	FW	O	[	nn	3	SENT_184	[p3l474t3333r493b3461],
3	saltsfoines	NNS	O	saltsfoine	nsubj	5	SENT_184	[p3l846t3335r983b3388],
4	and	CC	O	and	advmod	3	SENT_184	[p3l999t3335r1051b3359],
5	lit	VBD	O	light	_	0	SENT_184	[p3l184t3368r345b3389],
6	muds	NNS	O	mud	nn	7	SENT_184	[p3l846t3369r928b3389],
7	ones	NNS	O	one	dobj	5	SENT_184	[p3l942t3369r1010b3390],
8	:13	CD	NUMBER	:13	num	10	SENT_184	[p3l184t3391r380b3413],
9	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_184	[p3l184t3391r380b3413],
10	20m	CD	NUMBER	20m	dep	7	SENT_184	[p3l502t3380r586b3411],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_184	[p3l502t3380r586b3411],

1	9	CD	NUMBER	9	num	2	SENT_185	[p3l754t3472r778b3495],
2	localltg	NN	O	localltg	_	0	SENT_185	[p3l846t3454r963b3489],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_185	[p3l973t3450r1002b3477],
4	gash-opods	NNS	O	gash-opod	prep_of	2	SENT_185	[p3l847t3484r1021b3514],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_186	[p3l71t3580r100b3599],

1	J	NN	O	j	_	0	SENT_187	[p3l71t3580r100b3599],

1	JOURNAL	NN	O	journal	_	0	SENT_188	[p3l614t1557r800b1585],
2	OF	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_188	[p3l813t1557r868b1585],
3	PALEONTOLOGY	NNP	O	PALEONTOLOGY	nn	5	SENT_188	[p3l878t1557r1211b1590],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_188	[p3l878t1557r1211b1590],
5	V.	NNP	O	V.	prep_of	1	SENT_188	[p3l1232t1558r1260b1586],
6	69	CD	NUMBER	69	num	5	SENT_188	[p3l1277t1559r1323b1590],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_188	[p3l1277t1559r1323b1590],
8	No.	NN	O	no.	appos	5	SENT_188	[p3l1339t1558r1403b1587],
9	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	8	SENT_188	[p3l1421t1559r1446b1590],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_188	[p3l1421t1559r1446b1590],
11	I995	NN	O	i995	dep	1	SENT_188	[p3l1466t1559r1543b1587],

1	KYRGYZSTAN	NNP	LOCATION	KYRGYZSTAN	_	0	SENT_189	[p3l1213t1795r1672b1849],

1	FIGURE	NN	O	figure	_	0	SENT_190	[p3l20t3664r128b3689],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_190	[p3l141t3662r311b3693],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_190	[p3l141t3662r311b3693],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_191	[p3l141t3662r311b3693],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_191	[p3l141t3662r311b3693],

1	Locality	NNP	O	Locality	nn	2	SENT_192	[p3l141t3662r311b3693],
2	map	NN	O	map	_	0	SENT_192	[p3l323t3669r387b3692],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_192	[p3l398t3661r452b3687],
4	stratigraphic	JJ	O	stratigraphic	amod	6	SENT_192	[p3l463t3660r647b3692],
5	columnar	NN	O	columnar	nn	6	SENT_192	[p3l657t3660r798b3686],
6	section	NN	O	section	conj_and	2	SENT_192	[p3l809t3659r910b3685],
7	showing	VBG	O	show	partmod	2	SENT_192	[p3l922t3659r1042b3690],
8	location	NN	O	location	dobj	7	SENT_192	[p3l1052t3658r1169b3685],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_192	[p3l1181t3658r1214b3684],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_192	[p3l1220t3659r1265b3684],
11	Pragian	JJ	MISC	pragian	amod	13	SENT_192	[p3l1275t3658r1385b3690],
12	age	NN	O	age	nn	13	SENT_192	[p3l1397t3666r1443b3690],
13	gastropods	NNS	O	gastropod	prep_of	2	SENT_192	[p3l1454t3658r1611b3690],
14	described	VBN	O	describe	partmod	13	SENT_192	[p3l1621t3657r1759b3684],
15	here	RB	O	here	advmod	14	SENT_192	[p3l1770t3658r1833b3683],
16	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_192	[p3l1843t3657r1914b3683],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_192	[p3l1926t3657r1970b3683],
18	Alai	NNP	LOCATION	Alai	nn	19	SENT_192	[p3l1981t3656r2042b3683],
19	Ridge	NNP	LOCATION	Ridge	prep_from	14	SENT_192	[p3l2053t3656r2145b3688],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_192	[p3l2053t3656r2145b3688],

1	Kyrgyzstan	NNP	LOCATION	Kyrgyzstan	_	0	SENT_193	[p3l87t3710r441b3773],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_193	[p3l87t3710r441b3773],

1	limestone	NN	O	limestone	nn	2	SENT_194	[p4l8t103r339b162],
2	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l365t101r644b172],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l672t101r748b159],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_194	[p4l766t103r870b159],
5	extemal	JJ	O	extemal	amod	6	SENT_194	[p4l897t100r1169b158],
6	part	NN	O	part	prep_of	2	SENT_194	[p4l1196t108r1332b170],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l1359t99r1434b157],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_194	[p4l1454t101r1557b157],
9	shelf	NN	O	shelf	prep_of	6	SENT_194	[p4l1586t98r1752b157],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l1768t100r1891b157],
11	barrier	NN	O	barrier	nn	13	SENT_194	[p4l1919t97r2150b156],
12	reef	NN	O	reef	nn	13	SENT_194	[p4l7t188r144b246],
13	complex	NN	O	complex	conj_and	9	SENT_194	[p4l147t187r454b257],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l147t187r454b257],
15	terrigenous-siliceous	JJ	O	terrigenous-siliceous	amod	16	SENT_194	[p4l473t185r1170b257],
16	formations	NNS	O	formation	conj_and	6	SENT_194	[p4l1187t184r1556b242],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l1571t183r1645b240],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_194	[p4l1652t184r1755b241],
19	continental	JJ	O	continental	amod	20	SENT_194	[p4l1769t182r2148b240],
20	slope	NN	O	slope	prep_of	16	SENT_194	[p4l10t273r182b341],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l205t271r330b329],
22	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	23	SENT_194	[p4l354t270r431b328],
23	base	NN	O	base	prep_of	16	SENT_194	[p4l453t271r619b336],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l453t271r619b336],
25	terrigenous-siliceous	JJ	O	terrigenous-siliceous	amod	26	SENT_194	[p4l645t267r1343b340],
26	formations	NNS	O	formation	conj_and	6	SENT_194	[p4l1365t266r1734b325],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l1757t265r1833b324],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_194	[p4l1845t267r1948b324],
29	abyssal	JJ	O	abyssal	amod	30	SENT_194	[p4l1970t266r2147b335, p4l10t357r97b414],
30	plain	NN	O	plain	prep_of	26	SENT_194	[p4l125t354r313b424],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l125t354r313b424],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l343t356r469b412],
33	sedimentary-volcanogenic	JJ	O	sedimentary-volcanogenic	amod	35	SENT_194	[p4l497t352r1388b423],
34	ophiolite	NN	O	ophiolite	nn	35	SENT_194	[p4l1413t351r1715b419],
35	complexes	NNS	O	complex	prep_of	2	SENT_194	[p4l1740t351r2110b418],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_194	[p4l1740t351r2110b418],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_195	[p4l85t443r219b498],
2	studied	VBN	O	study	amod	3	SENT_195	[p4l248t442r494b498],
3	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	nsubjpass	5	SENT_195	[p4l523t441r729b497],
4	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	5	SENT_195	[p4l756t456r858b497],
5	derived	VBN	O	derive	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l886t439r1143b496],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1172t438r1334b495],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_195	[p4l1363t439r1468b495],
8	Karakavak	NNP	O	Karakavak	nn	9	SENT_195	[p4l1497t438r1867b494],
9	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	5	SENT_195	[p4l1896t438r2147b493, p4l8t525r161b592],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1896t438r2147b493, p4l8t525r161b592],
11	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	26	SENT_195	[p4l181t525r383b581],
12	comprises	VBZ	O	comprise	rcmod	9	SENT_195	[p4l400t524r742b593],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_195	[p4l757t524r863b580],
14	base	NN	O	base	dobj	12	SENT_195	[p4l879t524r1025b579],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1042t521r1119b579],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_195	[p4l1123t522r1228b578],
17	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	18	SENT_195	[p4l1245t522r1459b578],
18	Devonian	NNP	MISC	Devonian	prep_of	14	SENT_195	[p4l1474t520r1807b578],
19	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1823t528r1889b576],
20	Middle	NNP	LOCATION	Middle	nn	23	SENT_195	[p4l1906t520r2149b576],
21	Carboniferous	NNP	LOCATION	Carboniferous	nn	23	SENT_195	[p4l7t608r495b667],
22	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	23	SENT_195	[p4l517t609r850b666],
23	complex	NN	O	complex	prep_to	12	SENT_195	[p4l872t607r1161b674],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1183t607r1308b662],
25	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	26	SENT_195	[p4l1332t605r1384b662],
26	exposed	VBN	O	expose	conj_and	12	SENT_195	[p4l1407t606r1679b672],
27	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1703t620r1785b660],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_195	[p4l1810t604r1914b660],
29	southern	JJ	O	southern	amod	30	SENT_195	[p4l1938t604r2148b660, p4l8t710r116b750],
30	slope	NN	O	slope	prep_on	26	SENT_195	[p4l151t694r324b760],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l356t692r432b749],
32	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_195	[p4l452t693r557b748],
33	Alai	NNP	LOCATION	Alai	nn	36	SENT_195	[p4l588t691r729b748],
34	Ridge	NNP	LOCATION	Ridge	nn	36	SENT_195	[p4l764t690r961b760],
35	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	36	SENT_195	[p4l992t690r1232b759],
36	Figure	NNP	O	Figure	prep_of	30	SENT_195	[p4l992t690r1232b759],
37	1	CD	NUMBER	1	number	38	SENT_195	[p4l1275t691r1329b758],
38	)	CD	NUMBER	)	npadvmod	36	SENT_195	[p4l1275t691r1329b758],
39	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1361t689r1426b744],
40	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_195	[p4l1458t689r1562b745],
41	inter?uve	NN	O	inter?uve	prep_in	36	SENT_195	[p4l1593t687r1918b745],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l1949t686r2026b744],
43	the	DT	O	the	det	47	SENT_195	[p4l2045t688r2149b744],
44	Sarydlcha	NNP	O	Sarydlcha	nn	47	SENT_195	[p4l10t779r343b849],
45	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l386t780r509b835],
46	Kainutok	NNP	PERSON	Kainutok	conj_and	44	SENT_195	[p4l552t777r874b834],
47	Rivers	NNP	PERSON	Rivers	prep_of	41	SENT_195	[p4l916t776r1156b832],
48	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_195	[p4l916t776r1156b832],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_196	[p4l1201t776r1334b831],
2	Karakavak	NNP	O	Karakavak	nn	3	SENT_196	[p4l1377t774r1747b831],
3	Formation	NN	O	formation	nsubj	4	SENT_196	[p4l1789t773r2150b830],
4	consists	VBZ	O	consist	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l9t861r275b919],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l300t860r377b917],
6	thin-layered	JJ	O	thin-layered	amod	7	SENT_196	[p4l391t860r803b929],
7	calcarenites	NNS	O	calcarenite	prep_of	4	SENT_196	[p4l828t857r1223b915],
8	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l1248t858r1397b914],
9	abundant	JJ	O	abundant	amod	12	SENT_196	[p4l1422t857r1742b913],
10	varying	VBG	O	vary	amod	12	SENT_196	[p4l1767t855r2021b925],
11	detrital	JJ	O	detrital	amod	12	SENT_196	[p4l2043t856r2148b911, p4l10t946r174b1003],
12	components	NNS	O	component	prep_with	4	SENT_196	[p4l196t953r628b1012],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l196t953r628b1012],
14	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	15	SENT_196	[p4l652t943r855b1000],
15	occur	VBP	O	occur	rcmod	12	SENT_196	[p4l877t959r1063b999],
16	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l1083t941r1147b997],
17	altemation	NN	O	altemation	prep_in	15	SENT_196	[p4l1169t940r1538b998],
18	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l1558t940r1706b995],
19	minor	JJ	O	minor	amod	20	SENT_196	[p4l1730t939r1939b996],
20	layers	NNS	O	layer	prep_with	15	SENT_196	[p4l1957t939r2150b1008],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l11t1030r88b1087],
22	limy	JJ	O	limy	amod	23	SENT_196	[p4l114t1029r267b1098],
23	siltstones	NNS	O	siltstone	prep_of	20	SENT_196	[p4l307t1029r618b1086],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l654t1029r779b1085],
25	mudstones	NNS	O	mudstone	prep_of	20	SENT_196	[p4l817t1028r1200b1085],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_196	[p4l817t1028r1200b1085],

1	Siltstones	NNS	O	siltstone	nsubj	2	SENT_197	[p4l1243t1026r1566b1082],
2	prevail	VBP	O	prevail	_	0	SENT_197	[p4l1601t1024r1835b1092],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_197	[p4l1872t1023r1936b1079],
4	some	DT	O	some	det	5	SENT_197	[p4l1976t1039r2152b1079],
5	locations	NNS	O	location	prep_in	2	SENT_197	[p4l10t1114r335b1171],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_197	[p4l10t1114r335b1171],

1	Lens-like	JJ	O	lens-like	amod	2	SENT_198	[p4l368t1113r680b1170],
2	beds	NNS	O	bed	nsubj	14	SENT_198	[p4l708t1113r860b1169],
3	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l890t1128r957b1168],
4	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l986t1111r1122b1168],
5	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l1151t1127r1218b1167],
6	biohermal	JJ	O	biohermal	amod	8	SENT_198	[p4l1248t1109r1594b1166],
7	coralstromatoporoid	JJ	O	coralstromatoporoid	amod	8	SENT_198	[p4l1624t1109r2149b1165, p4l11t1198r237b1267],
8	limestones	NNS	O	limestone	conj_and	2	SENT_198	[p4l259t1198r621b1255],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l642t1198r767b1254],
10	interlayers	NNS	O	interlayer	conj_and	2	SENT_198	[p4l790t1196r1144b1265],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l1166t1194r1242b1251],
12	basic	JJ	O	basic	amod	13	SENT_198	[p4l1253t1194r1423b1251],
13	effusives	NNS	O	effusive	prep_of	8	SENT_198	[p4l1444t1192r1733b1251],
14	occur	VBP	O	occur	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l1755t1209r1941b1249],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l1961t1192r2026b1247],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_198	[p4l2048t1192r2152b1248],
17	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	18	SENT_198	[p4l12t1298r207b1350],
18	part	NN	O	part	prep_in	14	SENT_198	[p4l234t1290r370b1349],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l397t1280r474b1337],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_198	[p4l489t1281r594b1337],
21	formation	NN	O	formation	prep_of	18	SENT_198	[p4l622t1278r980b1336],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_198	[p4l622t1278r980b1336],

1	Lithologic	JJ	MISC	lithologic	amod	2	SENT_199	[p4l84t1364r431b1435],
2	composition	NN	O	composition	nsubj	8	SENT_199	[p4l457t1363r881b1434],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_199	[p4l910t1363r985b1420],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_199	[p4l1003t1363r1108b1420],
5	formation	NN	O	formation	prep_of	2	SENT_199	[p4l1137t1362r1474b1420],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	8	SENT_199	[p4l1503t1362r1555b1419],
7	rather	RB	O	rather	advmod	8	SENT_199	[p4l1583t1363r1786b1419],
8	consistent	JJ	O	consistent	_	0	SENT_199	[p4l1813t1361r2150b1418],
9	laterally	RB	O	laterally	advmod	8	SENT_199	[p4l7t1449r298b1519],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_199	[p4l7t1449r298b1519],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_200	[p4l320t1450r454b1505],
2	only	JJ	O	only	amod	4	SENT_200	[p4l474t1449r620b1518],
3	lithologic	JJ	O	lithologic	amod	4	SENT_200	[p4l640t1447r957b1518],
4	change	NN	O	change	nsubjpass	6	SENT_200	[p4l975t1447r1208b1517],
5	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	6	SENT_200	[p4l1227t1446r1279b1503],
6	expressed	VBN	O	express	_	0	SENT_200	[p4l1298t1445r1626b1514],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_200	[p4l1645t1445r1710b1501],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_200	[p4l1729t1446r1833b1502],
9	eastward	RB	O	eastward	advmod	10	SENT_200	[p4l1851t1445r2150b1501],
10	increase	NN	O	increase	prep_in	6	SENT_200	[p4l8t1533r281b1591],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_200	[p4l308t1532r372b1590],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_200	[p4l403t1532r507b1590],
13	number	NN	O	number	prep_in	10	SENT_200	[p4l535t1533r803b1590],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_200	[p4l829t1530r906b1588],
15	interlayered	JJ	O	interlayered	amod	18	SENT_200	[p4l922t1530r1327b1600],
16	effusive	JJ	O	effusive	amod	18	SENT_200	[p4l1354t1528r1613b1587],
17	volcanic	JJ	O	volcanic	amod	18	SENT_200	[p4l1640t1527r1924b1586],
18	rocks	NNS	O	rock	prep_of	13	SENT_200	[p4l1950t1529r2145b1585],
19	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_200	[p4l1950t1529r2145b1585],
