1	Paleontological	NNP	O	Paleontological	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l17t81r380b129],
2	Society	NNP	O	Society	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l398t81r574b129],

1	Upper	NNP	O	Upper	nn	4	SENT_2	[p1l15t270r146b313],
2	Campanian	NNP	O	Campanian	nn	4	SENT_2	[p1l167t270r402b313],
3	(	NNP	O	(	nn	4	SENT_2	[p1l423t266r568b313],
4	Upper	NNP	O	Upper	dep	19	SENT_2	[p1l423t266r568b313],
5	Cretaceous	JJ	O	cretaceous	amod	7	SENT_2	[p1l589t266r834b306],
6	)	NN	O	)	nn	7	SENT_2	[p1l589t266r834b306],
7	Ammonites	NNS	O	ammonite	dep	4	SENT_2	[p1l855t270r1108b302],
8	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1129t270r1245b302],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_2	[p1l1266t270r1336b302],
10	Marshalltown	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Marshalltown	nn	14	SENT_2	[p1l1357t270r1656b302],
11	Formation-Mount	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Formation-Mount	nn	14	SENT_2	[p1l1677t270r2070b302],
12	Laurel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Laurel	nn	14	SENT_2	[p1l15t324r148b356],
13	Boundary	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Boundary	nn	14	SENT_2	[p1l169t324r380b367],
14	Beds	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Beds	prep_from	7	SENT_2	[p1l401t324r497b356],
15	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l518t327r560b356],
16	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	prep_in	7	SENT_2	[p1l581t324r770b356],
17	Author	NN	LOCATION	author	dep	19	SENT_2	[p1l15t374r232b414],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_2	[p1l15t374r232b414],
19	s	NNS	O	s	dep	22	SENT_2	[p1l15t374r232b414],
20	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	19	SENT_2	[p1l15t374r232b414],
21	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l15t374r232b414],
22	W.	NNP	O	W.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l255t378r310b410],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l333t378r372b410],

1	T.	NNP	PERSON	T.	nn	2	SENT_3	[p1l333t378r372b410],
2	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	Kennedy	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l396t378r587b421],
3	and	CC	O	and	prep	2	SENT_3	[p1l608t378r682b410],
4	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	7	SENT_3	[p1l703t378r757b410],
5	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	7	SENT_3	[p1l781t378r823b410],
6	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	nn	7	SENT_3	[p1l846t378r1001b410],
7	Source	NNP	O	Source	dep	3	SENT_3	[p1l15t432r166b464],
8	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l15t432r166b464],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l190t432r363b464],

1	Tourna1	NN	O	tourna1	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l190t432r363b464],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l383t432r433b464],
3	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	nn	5	SENT_4	[p1l448t432r739b477],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l448t432r739b477],
5	Vol	NNP	O	Vol	prep_of	1	SENT_4	[p1l765t432r845b464],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l765t432r845b464],

1	71	CD	NUMBER	71	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l868t432r925b469],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l868t432r925b469],
3	No.	NN	O	no.	nn	5	SENT_5	[p1l951t432r1018b464],
4	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	5	SENT_5	[p1l1046t432r1059b464],
5	(	NN	O	(	appos	1	SENT_5	[p1l1084t428r1201b469],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1084t428r1201b469],

1	Tan.	NNP	O	Tan.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1084t428r1201b469],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1084t428r1201b469],
3	1997	CD	DATE	1997	num	4	SENT_6	[p1l1232t428r1348b469],
4	)	NN	O	)	appos	1	SENT_6	[p1l1232t428r1348b469],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1232t428r1348b469],
6	pp	NN	O	pp	appos	4	SENT_6	[p1l1374t443r1436b475],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1374t443r1436b475],

1	UPPER	NNP	O	UPPER	nn	2	SENT_18	[p1l82t1756r284b1801],
2	CAMPANIAN	NNP	O	CAMPANIAN	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l303t1754r689b1800],
3	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_18	[p1l709t1755r927b1810],
4	UPPER	NNP	O	UPPER	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l709t1755r927b1810],
5	CRETACEOUS	NNPS	O	CRETACEOUS	dep	2	SENT_18	[p1l946t1754r1374b1810],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	7	SENT_18	[p1l946t1754r1374b1810],
7	AMMONITES	NNS	O	ammonite	dep	2	SENT_18	[p1l1394t1754r1775b1800],
8	FROM	IN	O	from	dep	7	SENT_18	[p1l1795t1755r1977b1800],
9	THE	DT	O	the	dep	8	SENT_18	[p1l1996t1755r2121b1798],

1	MARSHALLTOWN	NNP	LOCATION	MARSHALLTOWN	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l177t1821r718b1867],
2	FORMATION-MOUNT	JJ	O	formation-mount	amod	4	SENT_19	[p1l737t1821r1378b1867],
3	LAUREL	NN	O	laurel	nn	4	SENT_19	[p1l1397t1821r1649b1867],
4	BOUNDARY	NN	O	boundary	dep	1	SENT_19	[p1l1667t1821r2028b1867],

1	BEDS	NNS	O	bed	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l796t1890r950b1934],
2	IN	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l971t1891r1038b1933],
3	DELAWARE	NN	LOCATION	delaware	prep_in	1	SENT_20	[p1l1057t1889r1411b1933],

1	W.	NNP	O	W.	nn	2	SENT_21	[p1l768t1985r814b2013],
2	J	NNP	O	J	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l828t1985r844b2015],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l847t2007r853b2013],

1	KENNEDY	NNP	O	KENNEDY	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l868t1985r1068b2013],
2	AND	NNP	O	AND	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l1080t1991r1148b2013],
3	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l1161t1985r1207b2013],
4	A.	NNP	PERSON	A.	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l1221t1984r1258b2013],
5	COBBAN	NNP	PERSON	COBBAN	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l1273t1984r1439b2013],

1	Geological	JJ	O	geological	amod	2	SENT_23	[p1l532t2033r689b2064],
2	Collections	NNS	O	collection	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l699t2032r871b2063],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l699t2032r871b2063],
4	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	nn	5	SENT_23	[p1l884t2033r1041b2064],
5	Museum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Museum	appos	2	SENT_23	[p1l1051t2033r1188b2063],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1051t2033r1188b2063],
7	Parks	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Parks	nn	8	SENT_23	[p1l1200t2033r1282b2059],
8	Road	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Road	appos	2	SENT_23	[p1l1293t2033r1380b2063],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1293t2033r1380b2063],
10	Oxford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Oxford	nn	11	SENT_23	[p1l1393t2032r1498b2059],
11	University	NNP	ORGANIZATION	University	appos	8	SENT_23	[p1l1508t2032r1673b2064],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1508t2032r1673b2064],

1	Oxford	NNP	LOCATION	Oxford	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l784t2069r897b2100],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l784t2069r897b2100],
3	OX1	NN	O	ox1	nn	5	SENT_24	[p1l909t2069r977b2095],
4	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	5	SENT_24	[p1l994t2069r1009b2095],
5	PW	NN	O	pw	appos	1	SENT_24	[p1l1021t2070r1084b2100],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1021t2070r1084b2100],
7	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	8	SENT_24	[p1l1096t2069r1200b2095],
8	Kingdom	NNP	LOCATION	Kingdom	appos	1	SENT_24	[p1l1210t2069r1357b2101],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1210t2069r1357b2101],
10	and	CC	O	and	advmod	1	SENT_24	[p1l1369t2069r1424b2095],

1	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	U.S.	nn	3	SENT_25	[p1l411t2107r474b2134],
2	Geological	NNP	O	Geological	nn	3	SENT_25	[p1l487t2107r643b2139],
3	Survey	NNP	O	Survey	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l654t2107r764b2139],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l654t2107r764b2139],
5	Box	NNP	O	Box	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l776t2108r833b2133],
6	25046	CD	NUMBER	25046	num	5	SENT_25	[p1l846t2107r945b2138],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l846t2107r945b2138],
8	Mail	NNP	O	Mail	nn	9	SENT_25	[p1l957t2107r1026b2133],
9	Stop	NNP	O	Stop	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1037t2107r1103b2138],
10	919	CD	NUMBER	919	num	9	SENT_25	[p1l1115t2107r1177b2138],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1115t2107r1177b2138],
12	Federal	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Federal	nn	13	SENT_25	[p1l1189t2107r1299b2134],
13	Center	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Center	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1310t2107r1415b2138],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1310t2107r1415b2138],
15	Denver	NNP	LOCATION	Denver	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1427t2107r1544b2138],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1427t2107r1544b2138],
17	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	Colorado	appos	3	SENT_25	[p1l1557t2107r1693b2133],
18	80225	CD	NUMBER	80225	num	17	SENT_25	[p1l1705t2107r1794b2133],

1	Ans	NNS	MISC	an	poss	3	SENT_26	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],
2	'	POS	O	'	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],
3	rnAcr	NN	O	rnacr	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],

1	New	NNP	O	New	nn	2	SENT_28	[p1l138t2233r387b2261],
2	collections	NNS	O	collection	nsubj	20	SENT_28	[p1l398t2233r553b2261],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l564t2233r636b2260],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_28	[p1l647t2234r692b2260],
5	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	6	SENT_28	[p1l703t2234r907b2260],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	2	SENT_28	[p1l918t2233r1075b2260],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1086t2234r1141b2261],
8	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	11	SENT_28	[p1l1151t2234r1226b2261],
9	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	11	SENT_28	[p1l1237t2234r1337b2261],
10	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	11	SENT_28	[p1l1347t2234r1442b2260],
11	Sand	NNP	LOCATION	Sand	conj_and	2	SENT_28	[p1l1453t2234r1526b2260],
12	along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1536t2234r1616b2266],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_28	[p1l1625t2234r1671b2260],
14	Chesapeake	NNP	LOCATION	Chesapeake	nn	17	SENT_28	[p1l1682t2234r1854b2266],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l1865t2234r1920b2260],
16	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	nn	17	SENT_28	[p1l1930t2234r2068b2260],
17	Canal	NNP	LOCATION	Canal	prep_along	11	SENT_28	[p1l138t2271r223b2297],
18	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l234t2270r263b2297],
19	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	prep_in	11	SENT_28	[p1l274t2271r412b2297],
20	clarify	VB	O	clarify	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l424t2270r516b2303],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_28	[p1l527t2271r572b2297],
22	ammonite	JJ	O	ammonite	dobj	20	SENT_28	[p1l583t2271r734b2297],
23	dating	VBG	O	date	partmod	22	SENT_28	[p1l745t2270r837b2303],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l847t2271r881b2297],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_28	[p1l887t2271r933b2297],
26	interval	NN	O	interval	prep_of	23	SENT_28	[p1l944t2271r1065b2297],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_28	[p1l944t2271r1065b2297],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_29	[p1l1077t2271r1135b2297],
2	Marshalltown	NNP	O	Marshalltown	nn	5	SENT_29	[p1l1146t2271r1349b2297],
3	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	5	SENT_29	[p1l1360t2271r1518b2297],
4	yields	NNS	O	yield	nn	5	SENT_29	[p1l1528t2271r1613b2303],
5	Pachydiscus	NN	O	pachydiscus	nsubj	36	SENT_29	[p1l1623t2270r1799b2303],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_29	[p1l1810t2270r2006b2303],
7	Pachydiscus	NN	O	pachydiscus	dep	5	SENT_29	[p1l1810t2270r2006b2303],
8	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	9	SENT_29	[p1l1810t2270r2006b2303],
9	sp.	NN	O	sp.	dep	5	SENT_29	[p1l2018t2278r2067b2302],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l2018t2278r2067b2302],
11	Menuites	NN	O	menuite	conj_and	5	SENT_29	[p1l138t2309r273b2335],
12	portlocki	NN	O	portlockus	nn	14	SENT_29	[p1l277t2307r408b2340],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_29	[p1l414t2308r534b2340],
14	Sharpe	NNP	PERSON	Sharpe	dep	11	SENT_29	[p1l414t2308r534b2340],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l414t2308r534b2340],
16	1855	CD	DATE	1855	num	18	SENT_29	[p1l546t2308r626b2340],
17	)	NN	O	)	nn	18	SENT_29	[p1l546t2308r626b2340],
18	complexus	NN	O	complexus	conj_and	5	SENT_29	[p1l634t2307r788b2340],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_29	[p1l795t2308r868b2340],
20	Hall	NN	O	hall	dep	18	SENT_29	[p1l795t2308r868b2340],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l876t2308r930b2335],
22	Meek	NNP	PERSON	Meek	conj_and	5	SENT_29	[p1l937t2309r1027b2340],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l937t2309r1027b2340],
24	1856	CD	DATE	1856	num	25	SENT_29	[p1l1040t2308r1127b2341],
25	)	NN	O	)	appos	22	SENT_29	[p1l1040t2308r1127b2341],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1040t2308r1127b2341],
27	a	DT	O	a	det	28	SENT_29	[p1l1135t2316r1152b2335],
28	subspecies	NNS	O	subspecy	appos	22	SENT_29	[p1l1160t2308r1312b2341],
29	restricted	JJ	O	restricted	amod	28	SENT_29	[p1l1319t2308r1456b2335],
30	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1462t2313r1491b2335],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_29	[p1l1499t2308r1544b2335],
32	Baculites	NNPS	O	Baculites	nn	33	SENT_29	[p1l1551t2307r1684b2335],
33	gregoryensis	NN	O	gregoryensis	prep_to	29	SENT_29	[p1l1689t2309r1869b2341],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1875t2308r1930b2335],
35	Baculites	NNS	O	baculite	prep_to	29	SENT_29	[p1l1936t2307r2069b2335],
36	scotti	VBP	O	scotti	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l138t2346r215b2372],
37	zones	NNS	O	zone	dobj	36	SENT_29	[p1l225t2353r306b2372],
38	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l318t2345r347b2372],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	41	SENT_29	[p1l358t2346r404b2372],
40	Western	JJ	MISC	western	amod	41	SENT_29	[p1l415t2346r536b2372],
41	Interior	NNP	O	Interior	prep_in	36	SENT_29	[p1l548t2345r661b2372],
42	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l672t2346r705b2372],
43	the	DT	O	the	det	45	SENT_29	[p1l712t2346r757b2372],
44	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	45	SENT_29	[p1l768t2346r872b2372],
45	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	prep_of	41	SENT_29	[p1l884t2346r977b2377],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l884t2346r977b2377],
47	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l989t2346r1044b2372],
48	Didymoceras	FW	O	didymoceras	nn	50	SENT_29	[p1l1054t2345r1246b2378],
49	binodosum	FW	O	binodosum	nn	50	SENT_29	[p1l1257t2345r1416b2372],
50	(	FW	O	(	conj_and	36	SENT_29	[p1l1427t2346r1570b2378],
51	Kennedy	NN	PERSON	kennedy	dobj	50	SENT_29	[p1l1427t2346r1570b2378],
52	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1581t2346r1636b2372],
53	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	conj_and	51	SENT_29	[p1l1647t2346r1770b2377],
54	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1647t2346r1770b2377],
55	1993a	CD	DATE	1993a	num	56	SENT_29	[p1l1786t2346r1882b2378],
56	)	CD	NUMBER	)	appos	53	SENT_29	[p1l1786t2346r1882b2378],
57	known	VBN	O	know	dep	50	SENT_29	[p1l1894t2346r1993b2372],
58	only	RB	O	only	advmod	57	SENT_29	[p1l2004t2346r2068b2378],
59	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l138t2383r210b2410],
60	the	DT	O	the	det	63	SENT_29	[p1l221t2384r267b2410],
61	B.	NNP	MISC	B.	nn	63	SENT_29	[p1l278t2384r309b2410],
62	scotti	NNP	O	scotti	nn	63	SENT_29	[p1l322t2385r400b2410],
63	zone	NN	O	zone	prep_from	57	SENT_29	[p1l410t2391r479b2410],
64	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l491t2383r524b2410],
65	the	DT	O	the	det	67	SENT_29	[p1l531t2384r577b2410],
66	Western	JJ	ORGANIZATION	western	amod	67	SENT_29	[p1l588t2384r710b2410],
67	Interior	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Interior	prep_of	63	SENT_29	[p1l722t2383r835b2410],
68	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l846t2384r900b2410],
69	correlatives	NNS	O	correlative	conj_and	63	SENT_29	[p1l912t2383r1082b2410],
70	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1093t2383r1122b2410],
71	Arkansas	NNP	LOCATION	Arkansas	prep_in	69	SENT_29	[p1l1134t2383r1269b2410],
72	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1281t2384r1335b2410],
73	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_in	69	SENT_29	[p1l1347t2385r1440b2410],
74	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l1347t2385r1440b2410],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_30	[p1l1454t2384r1511b2410],
2	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	3	SENT_30	[p1l1522t2384r1597b2410],
3	part	NN	O	part	nsubj	9	SENT_30	[p1l1609t2387r1669b2415],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1680t2384r1713b2410],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_30	[p1l1720t2384r1766b2410],
6	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	8	SENT_30	[p1l1778t2384r1878b2410],
7	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	8	SENT_30	[p1l1889t2384r1983b2410],
8	Sand	NNP	LOCATION	Sand	prep_of	3	SENT_30	[p1l1995t2384r2068b2410],
9	contains	VBZ	O	contain	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l139t2420r261b2447],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_30	[p1l273t2428r289b2447],
11	complex	JJ	O	complex	amod	12	SENT_30	[p1l300t2421r425b2452],
12	assemblage	NN	O	assemblage	nsubj	13	SENT_30	[p1l436t2421r601b2453],
13	preserved	VBN	O	preserve	dep	9	SENT_30	[p1l612t2421r755b2452],
14	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l765t2428r795b2447],
15	phosphatic	JJ	O	phosphatic	amod	16	SENT_30	[p1l807t2421r967b2452],
16	molds	NNS	O	mold	prep_as	13	SENT_30	[p1l978t2421r1076b2447],
17	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l978t2421r1076b2447],
18	Nostoceras	FW	O	nostoceras	nn	22	SENT_30	[p1l1088t2421r1247b2447],
19	(	FW	O	(	nn	22	SENT_30	[p1l1257t2421r1436b2453],
20	Nostoceras	FW	O	nostoceras	nn	22	SENT_30	[p1l1257t2421r1436b2453],
21	)	FW	O	)	nn	22	SENT_30	[p1l1257t2421r1436b2453],
22	monotuberculatum	FW	O	monotuberculatum	dobj	9	SENT_30	[p1l1449t2420r1725b2447],
23	Kennedy	NN	PERSON	kennedy	dep	22	SENT_30	[p1l1736t2421r1868b2453],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1879t2421r1933b2447],
25	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	dep	22	SENT_30	[p1l1944t2421r2067b2452],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1944t2421r2067b2452],
27	1993a	NN	DATE	1993a	dep	22	SENT_30	[p1l143t2458r236b2489],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l143t2458r236b2489],
29	Nostoceras	FW	O	nostoceras	nn	31	SENT_30	[p1l247t2458r407b2484],
30	(	FW	O	(	nn	31	SENT_30	[p1l417t2458r455b2490],
31	N	NN	O	n	dep	22	SENT_30	[p1l417t2458r455b2490],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l456t2458r474b2490],
33	)	SYM	O	)	dep	22	SENT_30	[p1l456t2458r474b2490],

1	sp.	NN	O	sp.	nsubj	15	SENT_31	[p1l486t2465r535b2489],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l486t2465r535b2489],
3	Didymoceras	FW	O	didymoceras	appos	1	SENT_31	[p1l546t2457r738b2490],
4	platycostatum	FW	O	platycostatum	nn	6	SENT_31	[p1l746t2457r952b2490],
5	(	FW	O	(	nn	6	SENT_31	[p1l963t2458r1106b2490],
6	Kennedy	NN	PERSON	kennedy	dep	3	SENT_31	[p1l963t2458r1106b2490],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1116t2458r1171b2484],
8	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	conj_and	3	SENT_31	[p1l1181t2458r1304b2489],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1181t2458r1304b2489],
10	1993b	CD	NUMBER	1993b	num	11	SENT_31	[p1l1320t2458r1427b2490],
11	)	NN	O	)	appos	8	SENT_31	[p1l1320t2458r1427b2490],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1320t2458r1427b2490],
13	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	14	SENT_31	[p1l1438t2459r1472b2484],
14	stevensoni	NNS	O	stevensonus	appos	8	SENT_31	[p1l1485t2459r1633b2484],
15	(	VBP	O	(	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1643t2458r1799b2490],
16	Whit?eld	NNP	O	Whit?eld	nsubj	22	SENT_31	[p1l1643t2458r1799b2490],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1643t2458r1799b2490],
18	1877	CD	DATE	1877	number	19	SENT_31	[p1l1814t2458r1894b2490],
19	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	20	SENT_31	[p1l1814t2458r1894b2490],
20	(	NN	O	(	appos	16	SENT_31	[p1l1905t2457r2069b2490],
21	previously	RB	DATE	previously	advmod	22	SENT_31	[p1l1905t2457r2069b2490],
22	thought	VBD	O	think	ccomp	15	SENT_31	[p1l139t2496r252b2528],
23	to	TO	O	to	aux	24	SENT_31	[p1l261t2499r290b2522],
24	be	VB	O	be	xcomp	22	SENT_31	[p1l299t2496r334b2522],
25	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l343t2495r415b2522],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_31	[p1l425t2496r470b2522],
27	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	28	SENT_31	[p1l480t2496r694b2528],
28	)	NN	O	)	prep_from	24	SENT_31	[p1l480t2496r694b2528],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l703t2496r758b2522],
30	Exitelocerasjenneyi	NN	O	exitelocerasjenneyus	nn	32	SENT_31	[p1l766t2495r1061b2528],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	32	SENT_31	[p1l1070t2495r1226b2528],
32	Whit?eld	NNP	O	Whit?eld	conj_and	28	SENT_31	[p1l1070t2495r1226b2528],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1070t2495r1226b2528],
34	187	CD	NUMBER	187	number	35	SENT_31	[p1l1240t2496r1289b2522],
35	7	CD	NUMBER	7	num	36	SENT_31	[p1l1292t2496r1327b2528],
36	)	NN	O	)	appos	32	SENT_31	[p1l1292t2496r1327b2528],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1292t2496r1327b2528],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_32	[p1l1338t2496r1396b2522],
2	last	JJ	O	last	amod	3	SENT_32	[p1l1405t2496r1456b2522],
3	two	CD	NUMBER	two	nsubj	6	SENT_32	[p1l1465t2500r1518b2522],
4	are	VBP	O	be	cop	6	SENT_32	[p1l1528t2503r1572b2522],
5	index	NN	O	index	nn	6	SENT_32	[p1l1582t2496r1663b2522],
6	species	NNS	O	species	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1673t2496r1774b2527],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l1784t2495r1817b2522],
8	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	10	SENT_32	[p1l1822t2495r1892b2522],
9	eponymous	JJ	O	eponymous	amod	10	SENT_32	[p1l1900t2503r2068b2528],
10	zones	NNS	O	zone	prep_of	6	SENT_32	[p1l138t2540r220b2559],
11	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l231t2533r260b2559],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_32	[p1l271t2534r316b2559],
13	Western	JJ	O	western	amod	14	SENT_32	[p1l327t2534r448b2559],
14	Interior	NNP	O	Interior	prep_in	10	SENT_32	[p1l459t2533r579b2559],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l459t2533r579b2559],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_33	[p1l591t2533r657b2559],
2	sequence	NN	O	sequence	nsubj	4	SENT_33	[p1l669t2540r800b2564],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	4	SENT_33	[p1l810t2533r833b2559],
4	compatible	JJ	O	compatible	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l844t2533r1008b2564],
5	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1018t2533r1083b2559],
6	ammonites	NNS	O	ammonite	prep_with	4	SENT_33	[p1l1094t2533r1258b2559],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1268t2533r1339b2559],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_33	[p1l1350t2534r1396b2559],
9	Wenonah	NNP	O	Wenonah	nn	10	SENT_33	[p1l1406t2534r1548b2559],
10	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	6	SENT_33	[p1l1558t2533r1724b2564],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1558t2533r1724b2564],
12	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	24	SENT_33	[p1l1735t2533r1823b2559],
13	lies	VBZ	O	lie	rcmod	10	SENT_33	[p1l1834t2533r1883b2559],
14	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1893t2534r2013b2559],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_33	[p1l2023t2533r2068b2559],
16	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	19	SENT_33	[p1l138t2571r342b2597],
17	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l354t2571r408b2597],
18	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	19	SENT_33	[p1l420t2571r521b2597],
19	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	prep_between	13	SENT_33	[p1l533t2571r627b2597],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l638t2575r667b2597],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_33	[p1l679t2571r725b2596],
22	north	NN	O	north	prep_to	13	SENT_33	[p1l736t2570r816b2597],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l828t2571r883b2597],
24	contains	VBZ	O	contain	rcmod	10	SENT_33	[p1l895t2570r1018b2597],
25	ammonites	NNS	O	ammonite	nsubj	26	SENT_33	[p1l1029t2570r1193b2597],
26	indicative	JJ	O	indicative	xcomp	24	SENT_33	[p1l1205t2570r1351b2597],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1362t2570r1396b2597],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_33	[p1l1403t2571r1448b2597],
29	Baculites	NNP	O	Baculites	nn	31	SENT_33	[p1l1459t2570r1592b2597],
30	scotti	NN	O	scottus	nn	31	SENT_33	[p1l1603t2572r1680b2597],
31	zone	NN	O	zone	prep_of	6	SENT_33	[p1l1690t2578r1767b2601],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1690t2578r1767b2601],
33	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1780t2571r1835b2597],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_33	[p1l1846t2571r1892b2597],
35	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	conj_and	6	SENT_33	[p1l1904t2570r1985b2597],
36	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1997t2570r2068b2596],
37	higher	JJR	O	higher	prep_from	35	SENT_33	[p1l139t2607r232b2640],
38	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l242t2607r270b2634],
39	the	DT	O	the	det	42	SENT_33	[p1l281t2608r327b2634],
40	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	42	SENT_33	[p1l338t2608r439b2635],
41	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	42	SENT_33	[p1l449t2608r544b2634],
42	Sand	NNP	LOCATION	Sand	prep_in	37	SENT_33	[p1l555t2608r636b2639],
43	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l555t2608r636b2639],
44	which	WDT	O	which	nsubj	45	SENT_33	[p1l647t2607r736b2634],
45	includes	VBZ	O	include	rcmod	42	SENT_33	[p1l747t2607r868b2634],
46	elements	NNS	O	element	dobj	45	SENT_33	[p1l879t2608r1008b2634],
47	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1019t2607r1052b2634],
48	the	DT	O	the	det	50	SENT_33	[p1l1059t2608r1104b2634],
49	Didymoceras	FW	O	didymoceras	nn	50	SENT_33	[p1l1114t2607r1307b2640],
50	cheyennense	FW	O	cheyennense	prep_of	46	SENT_33	[p1l1317t2607r1498b2640],
51	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1508t2608r1562b2634],
52	Baculites	FW	O	baculites	nn	54	SENT_33	[p1l1572t2607r1705b2634],
53	compressus	FW	O	compressus	nn	54	SENT_33	[p1l1715t2615r1881b2639],
54	zones	NNS	O	zone	conj_and	46	SENT_33	[p1l1891t2615r1973b2634],
55	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l1984t2607r2017b2634],
56	the	DT	O	the	det	59	SENT_33	[p1l2023t2608r2069b2634],
57	Western	JJ	O	western	amod	59	SENT_33	[p1l138t2646r260b2673],
58	Interior	JJ	O	interior	amod	59	SENT_33	[p1l271t2646r384b2672],
59	sequence	NN	O	sequence	prep_of	54	SENT_33	[p1l395t2653r533b2677],
60	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l395t2653r533b2677],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l836t2863r1329b2908],

1	N	NN	O	n	ccomp	17	SENT_35	[p1l88t2976r136b3019],
2	MOST	JJS	O	most	dobj	1	SENT_35	[p1l163t2974r336b3020],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l364t2960r441b3020],
4	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	6	SENT_35	[p1l457t2960r536b3020],
5	outcrop	NN	O	outcrop	nn	6	SENT_35	[p1l563t2970r824b3031],
6	area	NN	O	area	prep_of	2	SENT_35	[p1l852t2977r993b3020],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1019t2959r1085b3018],
8	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	9	SENT_35	[p1l1112t2963r1269b3019],
9	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	prep_in	1	SENT_35	[p1l1294t2962r1519b3032],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1294t2962r1519b3032],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_35	[p1l1548t2961r1652b3020],
12	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	13	SENT_35	[p1l1681t2961r2150b3020],
13	Formation	NN	O	formation	nsubj	17	SENT_35	[p1l132t3047r494b3106],
14	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	17	SENT_35	[p1l519t3046r572b3105],
15	a	DT	O	a	det	17	SENT_35	[p1l598t3063r635b3105],
16	dark	JJ	O	dark	amod	17	SENT_35	[p1l662t3048r815b3106],
17	greenish-gray	NN	O	greenish-gray	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l839t3047r1309b3119],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l839t3047r1309b3119],
19	very	RB	O	very	advmod	20	SENT_35	[p1l1336t3064r1484b3118],
20	?ne	RB	O	?ne	amod	17	SENT_35	[p1l1510t3047r1631b3107],
21	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1658t3057r1723b3106],
22	?ne	NN	O	?ne	prep_to	20	SENT_35	[p1l1751t3047r1892b3117],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1751t3047r1892b3117],
24	clayey	NN	O	clayey	appos	17	SENT_35	[p1l1919t3049r2146b3120],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1919t3049r2146b3120],
26	glauconitic	JJ	O	glauconitic	amod	27	SENT_35	[p1l17t3130r385b3204],
27	sand	NN	O	sand	appos	17	SENT_35	[p1l418t3133r590b3202],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l418t3133r590b3202],
29	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	48	SENT_35	[p1l624t3133r895b3192],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_35	[p1l927t3132r1030b3191],
31	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	33	SENT_35	[p1l1063t3134r1294b3191],
32	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	33	SENT_35	[p1l1327t3133r1543b3192],
33	Sand	NNP	LOCATION	Sand	nsubj	48	SENT_35	[p1l1577t3134r1743b3192],
34	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	48	SENT_35	[p1l1774t3132r1827b3191],
35	largely	RB	O	largely	advmod	48	SENT_35	[p1l1859t3134r2080b3206],
36	a	DT	O	a	det	48	SENT_35	[p1l2112t3151r2149b3193],
37	light	JJ	O	light	amod	48	SENT_35	[p1l17t3216r168b3288],
38	gray	JJ	O	gray	amod	48	SENT_35	[p1l197t3234r340b3289],
39	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l372t3226r438b3276],
40	reddish-brown	JJ	O	reddish-brown	amod	42	SENT_35	[p1l471t3216r968b3276],
41	quartz	NN	O	quartz	nn	42	SENT_35	[p1l999t3226r1212b3287],
42	sand	NN	O	sand	prep_to	38	SENT_35	[p1l1247t3218r1401b3276],
43	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	45	SENT_35	[p1l1432t3218r1565b3276],
44	usually	RB	O	usually	advmod	45	SENT_35	[p1l1597t3218r1836b3289],
45	contains	VBZ	O	contain	rcmod	42	SENT_35	[p1l1867t3216r2149b3277],
46	very	RB	O	very	advmod	47	SENT_35	[p1l17t3319r165b3373],
47	little	JJ	O	little	acomp	45	SENT_35	[p1l184t3302r337b3361],
48	glauconite	NN	O	glauconite	dep	17	SENT_35	[p1l357t3302r722b3374],
49	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l357t3302r722b3374],
50	the	DT	O	the	det	52	SENT_35	[p1l745t3303r848b3361],
51	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	52	SENT_35	[p1l869t3313r993b3362],
52	units	NNS	O	unit	nsubj	61	SENT_35	[p1l1014t3303r1181b3362],
53	being	VBG	O	be	auxpass	54	SENT_35	[p1l1199t3302r1383b3375],
54	seperated	VBN	O	seperate	partmod	52	SENT_35	[p1l1403t3304r1720b3373],
55	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1738t3304r1820b3374],
56	the	DT	O	the	det	58	SENT_35	[p1l1840t3304r1943b3362],
57	Wenonah	NNP	O	Wenonah	nn	58	SENT_35	[p1l1964t3305r2147b3362, p1l17t3388r185b3447],
58	Formation	NN	O	formation	agent	54	SENT_35	[p1l203t3387r566b3447],
59	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	58	SENT_35	[p1l584t3389r836b3459],
60	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	dep	61	SENT_35	[p1l584t3389r836b3459],
61	et	FW	O	et	dep	48	SENT_35	[p1l855t3398r933b3447],
62	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l855t3398r933b3447],

1	al.	FW	O	al.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l956t3389r1031b3447],
2	1979	CD	DATE	1979	num	3	SENT_36	[p1l1063t3388r1264b3459],
3	)	NNP	O	)	dep	1	SENT_36	[p1l1063t3388r1264b3459],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1063t3388r1264b3459],

1	However	RB	O	however	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1288t3390r1613b3458],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1288t3390r1613b3458],
3	along	IN	O	along	dep	1	SENT_37	[p1l1634t3389r1817b3459],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_37	[p1l1834t3389r1937b3447],
5	Chesapeake	NNP	LOCATION	Chesapeake	nn	8	SENT_37	[p1l1957t3389r2147b3447, p1l17t3474r248b3543],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l264t3474r388b3532],
7	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	nn	8	SENT_37	[p1l403t3474r722b3532],
8	Canal	NNP	LOCATION	Canal	pobj	3	SENT_37	[p1l738t3474r934b3532],
9	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l949t3483r1012b3532],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_37	[p1l1026t3473r1129b3532],
11	boundary	NN	O	boundary	prep_at	8	SENT_37	[p1l1144t3474r1469b3544],
12	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1483t3474r1760b3532],
13	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	14	SENT_37	[p1l1773t3475r1930b3533],
14	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	prep_between	11	SENT_37	[p1l1943t3475r2149b3545],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l18t3559r143b3617],
16	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	nn	17	SENT_37	[p1l157t3558r476b3617],
17	(	NN	O	(	prep_between	11	SENT_37	[p1l495t3558r718b3629],
18	where	WRB	O	where	advmod	22	SENT_37	[p1l495t3558r718b3629],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_37	[p1l735t3558r838b3617],
20	Wenonah	NNP	PERSON	Wenonah	nsubj	22	SENT_37	[p1l855t3558r1183b3617],
21	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	22	SENT_37	[p1l1198t3556r1251b3617],
22	absent	JJ	O	absent	rcmod	8	SENT_37	[p1l1267t3558r1502b3628],
23	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1267t3558r1502b3628],
24	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	nn	25	SENT_37	[p1l1522t3558r1749b3617],
25	et	NNP	O	et	dep	8	SENT_37	[p1l1765t3567r1843b3617],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l1765t3567r1843b3617],

1	al.	FW	O	al.	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1863t3558r1938b3617],
2	1970	CD	DATE	1970	dep	1	SENT_38	[p1l1969t3558r2146b3627],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1969t3558r2146b3627],
4	?g	NN	O	?g	appos	2	SENT_38	[p1l18t3643r113b3715],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l18t3643r113b3715],

1	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	2	SENT_39	[p1l146t3645r230b3714],
2	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	40	SENT_39	[p1l146t3645r230b3714],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l146t3645r230b3714],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_39	[p1l262t3644r365b3702],
5	uncomformable	JJ	O	uncomformable	amod	6	SENT_39	[p1l396t3642r935b3702],
6	contact	NN	O	contact	appos	2	SENT_39	[p1l965t3652r1210b3702],
7	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1238t3644r1516b3702],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_39	[p1l1545t3644r1648b3702],
9	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	prep_between	6	SENT_39	[p1l1680t3643r2148b3702],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l17t3729r141b3787],
11	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	conj_and	9	SENT_39	[p1l159t3730r389b3787],
12	laurel	NN	O	laurel	nsubjpass	14	SENT_39	[p1l408t3729r625b3787],
13	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	14	SENT_39	[p1l643t3728r696b3786],
14	di?icult	VBN	O	di?icult	rcmod	6	SENT_39	[p1l714t3727r973b3787],
15	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_39	[p1l990t3738r1056b3787],
16	determine	VB	O	determine	xcomp	14	SENT_39	[p1l1075t3727r1415b3787],
17	owing	VBG	O	owe	xcomp	16	SENT_39	[p1l1434t3727r1637b3800],
18	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l1653t3737r1719b3786],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_39	[p1l1738t3728r1841b3786],
20	presence	NN	O	presence	prep_to	17	SENT_39	[p1l1860t3744r2147b3798],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l18t12r93b73],
22	a	DT	O	a	det	25	SENT_39	[p2l115t31r153b73],
23	local	JJ	O	local	amod	25	SENT_39	[p2l184t14r342b72],
24	glauconitic	JJ	O	glauconitic	amod	25	SENT_39	[p2l375t13r744b85],
25	sand	NN	O	sand	prep_of	20	SENT_39	[p2l777t14r950b82],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l777t14r950b82],
27	here	RB	O	here	advmod	28	SENT_39	[p2l987t14r1128b72],
28	assigned	VBN	O	assign	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1163t12r1445b85],
29	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1476t22r1542b72],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_39	[p2l1577t13r1680b72],
31	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	33	SENT_39	[p2l1713t13r1885b72],
32	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	33	SENT_39	[p2l1919t15r2150b72],
33	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	prep_to	28	SENT_39	[p2l18t99r253b169],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l18t99r253b169],
35	that	IN	O	that	nsubj	38	SENT_39	[p2l279t99r413b158],
36	resembles	VBZ	O	resemble	cop	38	SENT_39	[p2l437t99r771b158],
37	the	DT	O	the	det	38	SENT_39	[p2l795t99r898b158],
38	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	rcmod	33	SENT_39	[p2l925t99r1393b157],
39	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1417t99r1530b157],
40	contains	VBZ	O	contain	conj_but	28	SENT_39	[p2l1554t98r1838b157],
41	Exogyra	NNP	O	Exogyra	nn	43	SENT_39	[p2l1860t100r2148b169],
42	cancellata	NNP	O	cancellata	nn	43	SENT_39	[p2l18t182r355b243],
43	Stephenson	NNP	PERSON	Stephenson	dobj	40	SENT_39	[p2l388t184r793b254],
44	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l388t184r793b254],
45	1914	CD	DATE	1914	appos	43	SENT_39	[p2l837t185r1015b253],
46	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l837t185r1015b253],
47	a	DT	O	a	det	48	SENT_39	[p2l1049t200r1086b242],
48	bivalve	JJ	O	bivalve	appos	43	SENT_39	[p2l1117t183r1366b243],
49	known	VBN	O	know	partmod	48	SENT_39	[p2l1398t185r1626b242],
50	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l1658t183r1725b241],
51	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	52	SENT_39	[p2l1754t185r1911b243],
52	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	prep_in	49	SENT_39	[p2l1942t185r2148b255],
53	only	RB	O	only	advmod	49	SENT_39	[p2l18t270r165b341],
54	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l186t268r350b328],
55	the	DT	O	the	det	58	SENT_39	[p2l372t270r476b328],
56	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	58	SENT_39	[p2l498t271r729b328],
57	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	58	SENT_39	[p2l751t269r968b328],
58	Sand	NNP	LOCATION	Sand	prep_from	49	SENT_39	[p2l991t270r1174b328],
59	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p2l991t270r1174b328],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	3	SENT_40	[p2l1200t268r1351b327],
2	glauconitic	JJ	O	glauconitic	amod	3	SENT_40	[p2l1370t267r1738b340],
3	sand	NN	O	sand	nsubj	24	SENT_40	[p2l1760t269r1933b338],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1760t269r1933b338],
5	about	IN	O	about	advmod	3	SENT_40	[p2l1957t269r2149b327],
6	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	7	SENT_40	[p2l17t364r140b414],
7	meters	NNS	O	meter	pobj	5	SENT_40	[p2l164t364r388b413],
8	thick	JJ	O	thick	amod	18	SENT_40	[p2l410t354r581b413],
9	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l600t371r686b413],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_40	[p2l707t355r810b412],
11	canal	NN	O	canal	prep_on	8	SENT_40	[p2l833t355r1008b413],
12	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1030t363r1093b412],
13	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	nn	14	SENT_40	[p2l1115t354r1197b412],
14	Georges	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Georges	prep_at	11	SENT_40	[p2l1223t354r1514b425],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1223t354r1514b425],
16	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	nn	17	SENT_40	[p2l1538t353r1856b412],
17	(	NNP	O	(	appos	14	SENT_40	[p2l1879t353r2149b425],
18	Figures	NNS	O	figure	dep	3	SENT_40	[p2l1879t353r2149b425],
19	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	18	SENT_40	[p2l26t442r77b509],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l26t442r77b509],
21	2	CD	NUMBER	2	num	22	SENT_40	[p2l101t440r181b510],
22	)	NN	O	)	appos	3	SENT_40	[p2l101t440r181b510],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l101t440r181b510],
24	represents	VBZ	O	represent	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l204t449r545b509],
25	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_40	[p2l563t455r601b497],
26	condensed	JJ	O	condensed	amod	27	SENT_40	[p2l620t439r976b498],
27	succession	NN	O	succession	dobj	24	SENT_40	[p2l995t438r1346b498],
28	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	29	SENT_40	[p2l1364t438r1496b497],
29	contains	VBZ	O	contain	rcmod	27	SENT_40	[p2l1514t438r1798b497],
30	fragments	NNS	O	fragment	nsubj	33	SENT_40	[p2l1817t437r2149b509],
31	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l19t523r94b583],
32	ammonites	NNS	O	ammonite	prep_of	30	SENT_40	[p2l104t524r482b583],
33	characteristic	JJ	O	characteristic	xcomp	29	SENT_40	[p2l501t523r951b582],
34	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l971t522r1047b582],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_40	[p2l1056t524r1159b582],
36	Western	JJ	MISC	western	amod	40	SENT_40	[p2l1181t525r1459b582],
37	Interior	NNP	MISC	Interior	nn	40	SENT_40	[p2l1480t523r1740b582],
38	Campanian	NNP	MISC	Campanian	nn	40	SENT_40	[p2l1758t523r2149b592],
39	ammonite	JJ	O	ammonite	amod	40	SENT_40	[p2l18t608r364b668],
40	zones	NNS	O	zone	prep_of	33	SENT_40	[p2l401t625r588b667],
41	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l625t607r701b668],
42	Didymoceras	FW	O	didymoceras	nn	43	SENT_40	[p2l725t606r1167b679],
43	stevensoni	FW	O	stevensoni	prep_of	40	SENT_40	[p2l1201t610r1542b667],
44	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l1576t608r1700b667],
45	Exiteloceras	FW	O	exiteloceras	nn	46	SENT_40	[p2l1735t606r2150b667],
46	jenneyi	FW	O	jenneyi	conj_and	43	SENT_40	[p2l7t697r278b766],
47	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p2l7t697r278b766],

1	Examples	NNS	O	example	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l319t694r648b764],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l685t693r762b752],
3	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	4	SENT_41	[p2l787t696r866b752],
4	stevensoni	NNS	O	stevensonus	prep_of	1	SENT_41	[p2l908t696r1248b752],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1285t694r1409b752],
6	E	NN	O	e	prep_of	1	SENT_41	[p2l1445t695r1502b750],
7	-	:	O	-	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1510t730r1522b751],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p2l1510t730r1522b751],

1	jenneyi	NN	O	jenneyus	nsubjpass	9	SENT_42	[p2l1552t695r1806b764],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1842t692r2006b751],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_42	[p2l2045t694r2148b752],
4	Chesapeake	NNP	LOCATION	Chesapeake	nn	7	SENT_42	[p2l18t780r413b850],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l454t780r578b838],
6	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	conj_and	4	SENT_42	[p2l617t780r935b838],
7	Canal	NNP	LOCATION	Canal	prep_from	1	SENT_42	[p2l975t779r1170b838],
8	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_42	[p2l1209t795r1364b838],
9	described	VBN	O	describe	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1405t778r1726b837],
10	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l1762t779r1846b849],
11	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	agent	9	SENT_42	[p2l1884t778r2149b837],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_42	[p2l19t865r253b936],
13	1970	CD	DATE	1970	num	14	SENT_42	[p2l19t865r253b936],
14	)	NN	O	)	dep	11	SENT_42	[p2l19t865r253b936],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p2l19t865r253b936],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_43	[p2l276t864r407b923],
2	specimens	NNS	O	specimen	nsubjpass	7	SENT_43	[p2l431t863r778b934],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l798t863r874b922],
4	D.	NNP	MISC	D.	nn	5	SENT_43	[p2l882t866r960b921],
5	stevensoni	NNS	O	stevensonus	prep_of	2	SENT_43	[p2l984t865r1326b922],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_43	[p2l1343t879r1499b922],
7	thought	VBN	O	think	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1520t863r1780b934],
8	to	TO	O	to	aux	9	SENT_43	[p2l1800t872r1866b922],
9	be	VB	O	be	xcomp	7	SENT_43	[p2l1886t863r1964b922],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1985t862r2148b921],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_43	[p2l18t950r121b1008],
12	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	13	SENT_43	[p2l149t949r618b1008],
13	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	9	SENT_43	[p2l644t948r1026b1018],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l644t948r1026b1018],
15	whereas	IN	O	whereas	mark	22	SENT_43	[p2l1054t949r1324b1007],
16	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_43	[p2l1350t948r1453b1007],
17	examples	NNS	O	example	nsubjpass	22	SENT_43	[p2l1479t949r1795b1018],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1822t947r1898b1007],
19	E.	NNP	O	E.	nn	20	SENT_43	[p2l1911t949r1987b1006],
20	jenneyi	NNS	O	jenneyus	prep_of	17	SENT_43	[p2l2006t950r2144b1019, p2l21t1037r158b1106],
21	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	22	SENT_43	[p2l171t1052r327b1094],
22	thought	VBN	O	think	advcl	9	SENT_43	[p2l342t1035r604b1106],
23	to	TO	O	to	aux	24	SENT_43	[p2l618t1044r684b1093],
24	be	VB	O	be	xcomp	22	SENT_43	[p2l699t1035r776b1093],
25	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l793t1033r957b1093],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_43	[p2l972t1034r1075b1093],
27	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	29	SENT_43	[p2l1092t1036r1323b1093],
28	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	29	SENT_43	[p2l1337t1034r1554b1092],
29	Sand	NNP	LOCATION	Sand	prep_from	24	SENT_43	[p2l1571t1034r1753b1092],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_43	[p2l1571t1034r1753b1092],

1	Collections	NNS	O	collection	nsubj	2	SENT_44	[p2l1773t1033r2149b1092],
2	made	VBD	O	make	ccomp	32	SENT_44	[p2l20t1123r204b1178],
3	since	IN	O	since	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l232t1121r399b1178],
4	1970	CD	DATE	1970	prep_since	2	SENT_44	[p2l437t1122r594b1177],
5	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l622t1123r703b1190],
6	members	NNS	O	member	prep_by	2	SENT_44	[p2l733t1122r1044b1177],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1073t1120r1148b1177],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_44	[p2l1165t1121r1268b1178],
9	Monmouth	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Monmouth	prep_of	6	SENT_44	[p2l1298t1121r1683b1178],
10	Amateur	JJ	ORGANIZATION	amateur	amod	11	SENT_44	[p2l1709t1120r2010b1178],
11	Paleontologists	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	Paleontologists	dep	15	SENT_44	[p2l2036t1122r2147b1177, p2l19t1205r443b1276],
12	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	dep	11	SENT_44	[p2l460t1204r703b1276],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_44	[p2l722t1204r994b1276],
14	MAPS	NNS	O	map	dep	15	SENT_44	[p2l722t1204r994b1276],
15	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	2	SENT_44	[p2l722t1204r994b1276],
16	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1013t1203r1088b1261],
17	West	NNP	LOCATION	West	nn	19	SENT_44	[p2l1096t1206r1267b1263],
18	Long	NNP	LOCATION	Long	nn	19	SENT_44	[p2l1284t1206r1456b1275],
19	Branch	NNP	LOCATION	Branch	prep_of	15	SENT_44	[p2l1472t1204r1731b1273],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1472t1204r1731b1273],
21	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	22	SENT_44	[p2l1749t1206r1906b1262],
22	Jersey	NNP	LOCATION	Jersey	appos	19	SENT_44	[p2l1922t1206r2146b1275],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1922t1206r2146b1275],
24	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l19t1288r184b1348],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_44	[p2l203t1290r305b1348],
26	condensed	JJ	O	condensed	amod	27	SENT_44	[p2l327t1289r682b1348],
27	bed	NN	O	bed	prep_from	2	SENT_44	[p2l699t1289r822b1347],
28	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l841t1298r904b1347],
29	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	30	SENT_44	[p2l925t1289r1006b1347],
30	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_at	27	SENT_44	[p2l1031t1289r1322b1360],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1031t1289r1322b1360],
32	include	VBP	O	include	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1344t1288r1589b1347],
33	many	JJ	O	many	amod	34	SENT_44	[p2l1610t1304r1798b1358],
34	fragments	NNS	O	fragment	dobj	32	SENT_44	[p2l1818t1287r2150b1358],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l19t1375r95b1434],
36	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	37	SENT_44	[p2l122t1378r200b1433],
37	stevensoni	NNS	O	stevensonus	prep_of	34	SENT_44	[p2l240t1377r581b1434],
38	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l619t1376r743b1434],
39	E.	NNP	O	E.	nn	40	SENT_44	[p2l780t1375r857b1433],
40	jenneyi	NNS	O	jenneyus	prep_of	34	SENT_44	[p2l887t1377r1160b1445],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l887t1377r1160b1445],
42	as	RB	O	as	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1203t1391r1270b1433],
43	well	RB	O	well	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1307t1374r1444b1433],
44	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1482t1390r1549b1433],
45	a	DT	O	a	det	47	SENT_44	[p2l1587t1391r1624b1433],
46	few	JJ	O	few	amod	47	SENT_44	[p2l1663t1374r1779b1433],
47	fragments	NNS	O	fragment	conj_and	34	SENT_44	[p2l1818t1374r2150b1444],
48	referable	JJ	O	referable	amod	47	SENT_44	[p2l20t1459r312b1519],
49	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l342t1469r408b1518],
50	Nostoceras	FW	O	nostoceras	nn	52	SENT_44	[p2l436t1462r802b1518],
51	monotuberculatum	FW	O	monotuberculatum	nn	52	SENT_44	[p2l834t1458r1469b1518],
52	Kennedy	NN	PERSON	kennedy	prep_to	48	SENT_44	[p2l1498t1460r1801b1529],
53	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1829t1460r1952b1518],
54	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	prep_to	48	SENT_44	[p2l1984t1459r2148b1517, p2l18t1546r162b1614],
55	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l1984t1459r2148b1517, p2l18t1546r162b1614],
56	1993a	NN	DATE	1993a	prep_to	48	SENT_44	[p2l219t1546r435b1614],
57	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l219t1546r435b1614],
58	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l482t1546r607b1604],
59	Didymoceras	FW	O	didymoceras	prep_to	48	SENT_44	[p2l650t1542r1093b1615],
60	platycostatum	FW	O	platycostatum	nn	62	SENT_44	[p2l1131t1542r1607b1614],
61	(	FW	O	(	nn	62	SENT_44	[p2l1654t1544r1981b1614],
62	Kennedy	NN	PERSON	kennedy	nsubj	32	SENT_44	[p2l1654t1544r1981b1614],
63	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l2026t1544r2150b1602],
64	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	conj_and	62	SENT_44	[p2l20t1630r302b1699],
65	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l20t1630r302b1699],
66	1993b	CD	NUMBER	1993b	num	67	SENT_44	[p2l331t1630r574b1700],
67	)	NN	O	)	appos	64	SENT_44	[p2l331t1630r574b1700],
68	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_44	[p2l331t1630r574b1700],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_45	[p2l593t1629r652b1687],
2	few	JJ	O	few	amod	3	SENT_45	[p2l667t1628r783b1687],
3	specimens	NNS	O	specimen	nsubj	25	SENT_45	[p2l800t1628r1147b1699],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1162t1628r1237b1687],
5	Menuites	NN	O	menuite	prep_of	3	SENT_45	[p2l1241t1630r1552b1687],
6	portlocki	NN	O	portlockus	nn	8	SENT_45	[p2l1559t1626r1860b1697],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_45	[p2l1874t1628r2147b1699],
8	Sharpe	NNP	PERSON	Sharpe	dep	5	SENT_45	[p2l1874t1628r2147b1699],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1874t1628r2147b1699],
10	1855	CD	DATE	1855	num	12	SENT_45	[p2l30t1715r213b1784],
11	)	NN	O	)	nn	12	SENT_45	[p2l30t1715r213b1784],
12	complexus	NN	O	complexus	conj_and	5	SENT_45	[p2l239t1713r593b1783],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_45	[p2l618t1715r787b1784],
14	Hall	NN	O	hall	dep	12	SENT_45	[p2l618t1715r787b1784],
15	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l811t1715r936b1773],
16	Meek	NNP	PERSON	Meek	conj_and	5	SENT_45	[p2l961t1715r1167b1783],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l961t1715r1167b1783],
18	1856	CD	DATE	1856	num	19	SENT_45	[p2l1205t1715r1387b1784],
19	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	16	SENT_45	[p2l1205t1715r1387b1784],
20	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1413t1715r1537b1773],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	22	SENT_45	[p2l1561t1730r1599b1772],
22	fragment	NN	O	fragment	conj_and	16	SENT_45	[p2l1624t1713r1926b1785],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1949t1713r2024b1772],
24	Dz	NNP	O	Dz	prep_of	3	SENT_45	[p2l2039t1715r2146b1771, p2l20t1799r378b1870],
25	?d	MD	O	?d	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l2039t1715r2146b1771, p2l20t1799r378b1870],
26	ymoceras	FW	O	ymoceras	nn	28	SENT_45	[p2l2039t1715r2146b1771, p2l20t1799r378b1870],
27	binodosum	FW	O	binodosum	nn	28	SENT_45	[p2l399t1798r767b1858],
28	(	FW	O	(	dobj	25	SENT_45	[p2l788t1800r1116b1870],
29	Kennedy	NN	PERSON	kennedy	dep	25	SENT_45	[p2l788t1800r1116b1870],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1135t1800r1260b1858],
31	Cobban	NNP	PERSON	Cobban	dep	25	SENT_45	[p2l1282t1799r1564b1867],
32	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1282t1799r1564b1867],
33	1993a	CD	NUMBER	1993a	num	34	SENT_45	[p2l1596t1799r1817b1868],
34	)	CD	NUMBER	)	appos	31	SENT_45	[p2l1596t1799r1817b1868],
35	have	VBP	O	have	aux	38	SENT_45	[p2l1837t1800r1997b1857],
36	also	RB	O	also	advmod	38	SENT_45	[p2l2019t1799r2149b1857],
37	been	VBN	O	be	auxpass	38	SENT_45	[p2l19t1885r178b1943],
38	collected	VBN	O	collect	rcmod	34	SENT_45	[p2l218t1885r514b1944],
39	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l553t1883r717b1943],
40	spoil	NN	O	spoil	nn	41	SENT_45	[p2l759t1884r919b1953],
41	heaps	NNS	O	heap	prep_from	38	SENT_45	[p2l959t1885r1150b1953],
42	along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1189t1884r1371b1955],
43	the	DT	O	the	det	45	SENT_45	[p2l1410t1885r1513b1941],
44	canal	NN	O	canal	nn	45	SENT_45	[p2l1553t1884r1730b1942],
45	west	NN	O	west	prep_along	41	SENT_45	[p2l1768t1892r1918b1941],
46	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1957t1882r2033b1941],
47	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	48	SENT_45	[p2l2064t1884r2146b1941],
48	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_of	45	SENT_45	[p2l21t1971r312b2041],
49	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l21t1971r312b2041],
50	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	52	SENT_45	[p2l343t1972r487b2040],
51	probably	RB	O	probably	advmod	52	SENT_45	[p2l515t1970r816b2040],
52	came	VBD	O	come	parataxis	25	SENT_45	[p2l843t1986r1020b2029],
53	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1048t1969r1212b2028],
54	lower	JJR	O	lower	prep_from	52	SENT_45	[p2l1242t1970r1429b2028],
55	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l1456t1970r1522b2027],
56	the	DT	O	the	det	58	SENT_45	[p2l1550t1971r1653b2028],
57	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	58	SENT_45	[p2l1683t1970r2152b2028],
58	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_in	54	SENT_45	[p2l20t2056r401b2113],
59	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_45	[p2l20t2056r401b2113],

1	MARSHALLTOWN-MOUNT	JJ	O	marshalltown-mount	amod	4	SENT_46	[p2l249t2157r1061b2202],
2	LAUREL	NN	O	laurel	nn	4	SENT_46	[p2l1090t2157r1339b2202],
3	BOUNDARY	NN	O	boundary	nn	4	SENT_46	[p2l1365t2157r1726b2202],
4	BEDS	NNS	O	bed	_	0	SENT_46	[p2l1752t2158r1906b2201],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_47	[p2l89t2256r219b2315],
2	geology	NN	O	geology	nsubjpass	10	SENT_47	[p2l262t2256r516b2328],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l558t2255r633b2315],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_47	[p2l666t2257r769b2315],
5	Chesapeake	NNP	LOCATION	Chesapeake	nn	8	SENT_47	[p2l813t2256r1208b2326],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1253t2257r1377b2315],
7	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	nn	8	SENT_47	[p2l1419t2256r1736b2315],
8	Canal	NNP	LOCATION	Canal	prep_of	2	SENT_47	[p2l1780t2256r1974b2315],
9	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	10	SENT_47	[p2l2017t2272r2141b2314],
10	mapped	VBN	O	map	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l13t2342r285b2411],
11	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l321t2342r404b2412],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_47	[p2l442t2342r545b2400],
13	U.S.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	U.S.	nn	15	SENT_47	[p2l586t2342r731b2400],
14	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	15	SENT_47	[p2l774t2340r1134b2413],
15	Survey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Survey	agent	10	SENT_47	[p2l1174t2342r1406b2412],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_47	[p2l1446t2341r1661b2412],
17	1967	CD	DATE	1967	num	18	SENT_47	[p2l1446t2341r1661b2412],
18	)	NN	O	)	dobj	10	SENT_47	[p2l1446t2341r1661b2412],
19	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l1700t2350r1763b2400],
20	a	DT	O	a	det	21	SENT_47	[p2l1801t2358r1839b2400],
21	scale	NN	O	scale	prep_at	18	SENT_47	[p2l1878t2341r2035b2400],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l2076t2339r2152b2399],
23	l	NN	O	l	prep_of	21	SENT_47	[p2l22t2425r369b2495],
24	:250,000	CD	NUMBER	:250,000	num	23	SENT_47	[p2l22t2425r369b2495],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l22t2425r369b2495],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_48	[p2l397t2426r527b2484],
2	Delaware	NNP	O	Delaware	nn	4	SENT_48	[p2l554t2425r870b2485],
3	Geological	NNP	O	Geological	nn	4	SENT_48	[p2l896t2425r1257b2497],
4	Survey	NN	O	survey	nsubj	6	SENT_48	[p2l1281t2427r1514b2496],
5	later	RB	O	later	advmod	6	SENT_48	[p2l1537t2426r1688b2484],
6	mapped	VBD	O	map	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1711t2426r1983b2496],
7	it	PRP	O	it	dobj	6	SENT_48	[p2l2007t2423r2056b2484],
8	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l2079t2434r2142b2484],
9	l	NN	O	l	prep_at	6	SENT_48	[p2l22t2511r308b2580],
10	:24,000	CD	NUMBER	:24,000	number	11	SENT_48	[p2l22t2511r308b2580],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_48	[p2l345t2510r622b2582],
12	Pickett	NNP	PERSON	Pickett	dep	9	SENT_48	[p2l345t2510r622b2582],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l345t2510r622b2582],
14	1970	CD	DATE	1970	num	15	SENT_48	[p2l670t2511r870b2582],
15	)	NN	O	)	appos	9	SENT_48	[p2l670t2511r870b2582],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l670t2511r870b2582],

1	Both	DT	O	both	det	2	SENT_49	[p2l911t2511r1074b2570],
2	maps	NNS	O	map	nsubj	3	SENT_49	[p2l1109t2527r1289b2581],
3	show	VBP	O	show	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1327t2511r1499b2570],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_49	[p2l1535t2511r1638b2570],
5	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	6	SENT_49	[p2l1675t2511r2142b2570],
6	Formation	NN	O	formation	dobj	3	SENT_49	[p2l13t2593r376b2655],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l396t2596r521b2654],
8	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	10	SENT_49	[p2l542t2597r773b2654],
9	laurel	NN	O	laurel	nn	10	SENT_49	[p2l794t2596r1011b2654],
10	Sand	NNP	O	Sand	dobj	3	SENT_49	[p2l1034t2596r1199b2655],
11	along	IN	O	along	advmod	10	SENT_49	[p2l1221t2595r1404b2667],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_49	[p2l1423t2596r1526b2654],
13	canal	NN	O	canal	pobj	11	SENT_49	[p2l1548t2596r1724b2655],
14	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1746t2594r1909b2654],
15	a	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_49	[p2l1931t2612r1969b2654],
16	little	JJ	O	little	npadvmod	17	SENT_49	[p2l1989t2595r2141b2654],
17	east	JJ	O	east	prep_from	11	SENT_49	[p2l12t2690r143b2740],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l168t2680r244b2740],
19	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	20	SENT_49	[p2l261t2682r343b2740],
20	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_of	10	SENT_49	[p2l374t2681r647b2753],
21	west	NN	O	west	advmod	20	SENT_49	[p2l672t2691r822b2740],
22	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l847t2690r913b2740],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	26	SENT_49	[p2l939t2681r1043b2740],
24	Summit	NNP	LOCATION	Summit	nn	26	SENT_49	[p2l1072t2682r1344b2740],
25	Bridge	NNP	LOCATION	Bridge	nn	26	SENT_49	[p2l1370t2682r1588b2753],
26	area	NN	O	area	prep_to	21	SENT_49	[p2l1614t2698r1771b2740],
27	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_49	[p2l1614t2698r1771b2740],

1	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	nsubj	7	SENT_50	[p2l91t2767r318b2825],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l351t2767r476b2825],
3	Minard	NNP	PERSON	Minard	conj_and	1	SENT_50	[p2l509t2765r764b2824],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	3	SENT_50	[p2l797t2765r1014b2837],
5	1970	CD	DATE	1970	num	6	SENT_50	[p2l797t2765r1014b2837],
6	)	NN	O	)	dep	3	SENT_50	[p2l797t2765r1014b2837],
7	described	VBD	O	describe	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1047t2765r1368b2825],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	9	SENT_50	[p2l1402t2783r1439b2825],
9	section	NN	O	section	dobj	7	SENT_50	[p2l1473t2765r1708b2825],
10	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1742t2766r2005b2837],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_50	[p2l2039t2766r2142b2824],
12	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	prep_through	7	SENT_50	[p2l13t2851r482b2910],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l512t2851r636b2909],
14	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	18	SENT_50	[p2l668t2853r899b2909],
15	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nn	18	SENT_50	[p2l930t2851r1147b2909],
16	4.8	CD	NUMBER	4.8	num	18	SENT_50	[p2l1178t2851r1278b2909],
17	km	NN	O	km	nn	18	SENT_50	[p2l1313t2852r1422b2908],
18	west	NN	O	west	prep_through	7	SENT_50	[p2l1453t2860r1603b2909],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1633t2850r1709b2909],
20	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	21	SENT_50	[p2l1732t2851r1814b2909],
21	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_of	12	SENT_50	[p2l1849t2851r2139b2922],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1849t2851r2139b2922],
23	where	WRB	O	where	advmod	29	SENT_50	[p2l12t2937r212b2994],
24	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_50	[p2l241t2936r344b2994],
25	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nsubj	29	SENT_50	[p2l375t2936r842b2994],
26	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	29	SENT_50	[p2l871t2935r924b2993],
27	4.3	CD	NUMBER	4.3	num	28	SENT_50	[p2l954t2936r1055b2992],
28	m	NN	O	m	npadvmod	29	SENT_50	[p2l1087t2952r1153b2992],
29	thick	JJ	O	thick	advcl	7	SENT_50	[p2l1183t2935r1354b2993],
30	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l1380t2936r1506b2993],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	33	SENT_50	[p2l1534t2936r1637b2993],
32	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	33	SENT_50	[p2l1667t2937r1897b2993],
33	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	nsubj	37	SENT_50	[p2l1927t2935r2142b2992],
34	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	37	SENT_50	[p2l12t3020r66b3078],
35	4.6	CD	NUMBER	4.6	num	36	SENT_50	[p2l103t3021r203b3079],
36	m	NN	O	m	npadvmod	37	SENT_50	[p2l244t3037r310b3078],
37	thick	JJ	O	thick	advcl	7	SENT_50	[p2l348t3019r534b3079],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l348t3019r534b3079],

1	Well-preserved	JJ	O	well-preserved	amod	4	SENT_51	[p2l573t3021r1107b3090],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l573t3021r1107b3090],
3	calcareous	JJ	O	calcareous	amod	4	SENT_51	[p2l1146t3020r1495b3079],
4	shells	NNS	O	shell	nsubjpass	13	SENT_51	[p2l1534t3020r1717b3078],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1753t3018r1828b3079],
6	Exogyra	NNP	O	Exogyra	nn	8	SENT_51	[p2l1854t3021r2141b3090],
7	ponderosa	NNP	O	ponderosa	nn	8	SENT_51	[p2l7t3103r355b3175],
8	Roemer	NNP	PERSON	Roemer	prep_of	4	SENT_51	[p2l376t3107r664b3174],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l376t3107r664b3174],
10	1849	CD	DATE	1849	appos	8	SENT_51	[p2l697t3105r875b3175],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l697t3105r875b3175],
12	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_51	[p2l898t3122r1055b3164],
13	noted	VBN	O	note	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1078t3105r1269b3164],
14	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1289t3105r1355b3162],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_51	[p2l1377t3106r1480b3164],
16	middle	NN	O	middle	prep_in	13	SENT_51	[p2l1503t3105r1738b3164],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1760t3104r1837b3164],
18	the	DT	O	the	det	19	SENT_51	[p2l1846t3105r1949b3163],
19	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	prep_of	16	SENT_51	[p2l1972t3106r2140b3163, p2l14t3190r357b3259],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1972t3106r2140b3163, p2l14t3190r357b3259],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l377t3190r502b3248],
22	phosphatized	VBN	O	phosphatize	csubjpass	28	SENT_51	[p2l519t3189r971b3260],
23	internal	JJ	O	internal	amod	24	SENT_51	[p2l987t3189r1248b3248],
24	molds	NNS	O	mold	dobj	22	SENT_51	[p2l1266t3189r1474b3248],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l1493t3188r1568b3247],
26	shells	NNS	O	shell	prep_of	24	SENT_51	[p2l1577t3189r1760b3248],
27	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	28	SENT_51	[p2l1777t3205r1933b3248],
28	noted	VBN	O	note	conj_and	13	SENT_51	[p2l1953t3189r2144b3247],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l12t3275r79b3332],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_51	[p2l109t3275r212b3334],
31	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	32	SENT_51	[p2l244t3292r439b3346],
32	meter	NN	O	meter	prep_in	28	SENT_51	[p2l468t3285r663b3334],
33	or	CC	O	or	cc	32	SENT_51	[p2l694t3292r766b3334],
34	so	RB	O	so	advmod	32	SENT_51	[p2l796t3292r883b3334],
35	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l796t3292r883b3334],

1	Fossils	NNS	O	fossil	nsubjpass	7	SENT_52	[p2l919t3275r1148b3334],
2	other	JJ	O	other	advmod	7	SENT_52	[p2l1178t3275r1355b3333],
3	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1384t3275r1535b3333],
4	borings	NNS	O	boring	prep_than	2	SENT_52	[p2l1565t3274r1815b3346],
5	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_52	[p2l1843t3290r2000b3333],
6	not	RB	O	not	neg	7	SENT_52	[p2l2032t3282r2143b3332],
7	recorded	VBN	O	record	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l14t3360r310b3419],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l334t3359r401b3417],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_52	[p2l426t3360r529b3418],
10	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	11	SENT_52	[p2l557t3361r787b3418],
11	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	prep_in	7	SENT_52	[p2l813t3359r1030b3418],
12	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1056t3368r1119b3418],
13	that	DT	O	that	det	14	SENT_52	[p2l1145t3360r1278b3417],
14	locality	NN	O	locality	prep_at	7	SENT_52	[p2l1303t3358r1568b3430],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_52	[p2l1303t3358r1568b3430],

1	At	IN	O	at	dep	6	SENT_53	[p2l89t3445r174b3503],
2	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	3	SENT_53	[p2l203t3446r285b3504],
3	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	pobj	1	SENT_53	[p2l317t3446r609b3517],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l317t3446r609b3517],
5	abundant	JJ	O	abundant	amod	6	SENT_53	[p2l639t3446r959b3504],
6	shells	NNS	O	shell	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l988t3445r1171b3504],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1200t3443r1276b3504],
8	E	NN	O	e	prep_of	6	SENT_53	[p2l1291t3447r1349b3502],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1355t3491r1367b3503],

1	ponderosa	NN	O	ponderosa	nsubjpass	13	SENT_54	[p2l1394t3443r1741b3514],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1770t3444r1894b3503],
3	Ostrea	NN	O	ostrea	conj_and	1	SENT_54	[p2l1925t3444r2142b3503],
4	[	CD	NUMBER	[	num	7	SENT_54	[p2l16t3530r415b3603],
5	Agerostrea	NNP	O	Agerostrea	nn	7	SENT_54	[p2l16t3530r415b3603],
6	]	NN	O	]	nn	7	SENT_54	[p2l16t3530r415b3603],
7	falcata	NN	O	falca	dep	1	SENT_54	[p2l442t3527r682b3602],
8	Morton	NNP	PERSON	Morton	dep	1	SENT_54	[p2l719t3531r996b3599],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l719t3531r996b3599],
10	1829	CD	DATE	1829	appos	1	SENT_54	[p2l1046t3530r1223b3599],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1046t3530r1223b3599],
12	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	13	SENT_54	[p2l1261t3546r1417b3588],
13	observed	VBN	O	observe	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1456t3530r1760b3588],
14	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l1796t3530r1879b3600],
15	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	agent	13	SENT_54	[p2l1915t3530r2142b3588],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l14t3616r139b3674],
17	Minard	NNP	PERSON	Minard	agent	13	SENT_54	[p2l164t3615r417b3674],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_54	[p2l441t3616r657b3687],
19	1970	CD	DATE	1970	num	20	SENT_54	[p2l441t3616r657b3687],
20	)	NN	O	)	dobj	13	SENT_54	[p2l441t3616r657b3687],
21	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l681t3615r748b3673],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_54	[p2l772t3616r875b3674],
23	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	prep_in	20	SENT_54	[p2l900t3615r1387b3674],
24	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l900t3615r1387b3674],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	3	SENT_55	[p2l1414t3614r1473b3672],
2	thin	JJ	O	thin	amod	3	SENT_55	[p2l1496t3615r1632b3672],
3	bed	NN	O	bed	nsubjpass	9	SENT_55	[p2l1655t3615r1777b3673],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1801t3613r1878b3673],
5	orangebrown-weathered	JJ	O	orangebrown-weathered	amod	7	SENT_55	[p2l1892t3630r2142b3686, p2l13t3701r604b3760],
6	glauconitic	JJ	O	glauconitic	amod	7	SENT_55	[p2l628t3699r996b3772],
7	sand	NN	O	sand	prep_of	3	SENT_55	[p2l1024t3701r1180b3759],
8	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_55	[p2l1205t3717r1330b3759],
9	considered	VBN	O	consider	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1357t3699r1722b3759],
10	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l1747t3716r1815b3758],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_55	[p2l1841t3699r1944b3758],
12	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	13	SENT_55	[p2l1971t3699r2144b3758],
13	bed	NN	O	bed	prep_as	9	SENT_55	[p3l13t14r135b73],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l153t13r229b73],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_55	[p3l235t14r338b73],
16	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	17	SENT_55	[p3l356t16r587b73],
17	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	prep_of	13	SENT_55	[p3l604t14r838b72],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p3l604t14r838b72],

1	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	nsubj	10	SENT_56	[p3l860t14r1088b72],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1105t14r1230b72],
3	Minard	NNP	PERSON	Minard	nsubj	10	SENT_56	[p3l1247t13r1501b72],
4	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_56	[p3l1518t13r1729b84],
5	1970	CD	DATE	1970	dep	1	SENT_56	[p3l1518t13r1729b84],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1518t13r1729b84],
7	p.	NN	O	p.	nn	9	SENT_56	[p3l1749t29r1808b83],
8	15	CD	NUMBER	15	num	9	SENT_56	[p3l1838t14r1936b83],
9	)	NN	O	)	appos	1	SENT_56	[p3l1838t14r1936b83],
10	noted	VBD	O	note	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1954t13r2144b72],
11	that	IN	O	that	complm	23	SENT_56	[p3l13t100r147b158],
12	?	CD	NUMBER	?	npadvmod	23	SENT_56	[p3l184t99r310b158],
13	At	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l184t99r310b158],
14	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	15	SENT_56	[p3l348t100r430b158],
15	George	NNP	LOCATION	George	poss	17	SENT_56	[p3l473t100r767b170],
16	?s	POS	LOCATION	?s	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l473t100r767b170],
17	Bridge	NNP	LOCATION	Bridge	prep_at	23	SENT_56	[p3l804t98r1041b171],
18	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l804t98r1041b171],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_56	[p3l1081t99r1185b158],
20	dark-gray	JJ	O	dark-gray	amod	21	SENT_56	[p3l1224t99r1548b171],
21	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nsubjpass	23	SENT_56	[p3l1585t98r2053b157],
22	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	23	SENT_56	[p3l2090t97r2143b156],
23	capped	VBN	O	cap	ccomp	10	SENT_56	[p3l14t186r253b256],
24	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l280t186r363b257],
25	a	DT	O	a	det	27	SENT_56	[p3l392t201r429b243],
26	thin	JJ	O	thin	amod	27	SENT_56	[p3l459t184r595b243],
27	bed	NN	O	bed	agent	23	SENT_56	[p3l623t185r746b244],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l776t184r852b244],
29	orange-brown	JJ	O	orange-brown	amod	32	SENT_56	[p3l873t184r1343b256],
30	glauconite	NN	O	glauconite	nn	32	SENT_56	[p3l1370t184r1714b255],
31	quartz	NN	O	quartz	nn	32	SENT_56	[p3l1744t193r1959b254],
32	sand	NN	O	sand	prep_of	27	SENT_56	[p3l1990t184r2144b242],
33	identi?ed	VBN	O	identi?ed	partmod	32	SENT_56	[p3l14t269r334b329],
34	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l354t270r437b340],
35	us	PRP	O	we	agent	33	SENT_56	[p3l459t285r531b327],
36	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l554t285r621b328],
37	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_56	[p3l643t269r746b327],
38	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	40	SENT_56	[p3l768t269r941b327],
39	Mount	NNP	O	Mount	nn	40	SENT_56	[p3l963t270r1194b327],
40	laurel	NN	O	laurel	prep_as	33	SENT_56	[p3l1217t269r1450b327],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p3l1217t269r1450b327],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_57	[p3l1476t268r1607b326],
2	weathered	JJ	O	weathered	amod	3	SENT_57	[p3l1630t268r1975b326],
3	condition	NN	O	condition	nsubj	8	SENT_57	[p3l1996t284r2143b326, p3l15t354r217b413],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l236t353r312b413],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_57	[p3l321t354r424b413],
6	upper	JJ	O	upper	amod	7	SENT_57	[p3l445t370r641b424],
7	bed	NN	O	bed	prep_of	3	SENT_57	[p3l658t354r781b412],
8	makes	VBZ	O	make	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l801t354r1016b412],
9	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	10	SENT_57	[p3l1035t353r1084b412],
10	difficult	JJ	O	difficult	xcomp	8	SENT_57	[p3l1103t352r1379b422],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1103t352r1379b422],
12	however	RB	O	however	advmod	8	SENT_57	[p3l1402t353r1707b422],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l1402t353r1707b422],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_57	[p3l1730t361r1796b411],
15	be	VB	O	be	cop	16	SENT_57	[p3l1816t353r1893b411],
16	certain	JJ	O	certain	xcomp	8	SENT_57	[p3l1914t351r2144b411],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l16t441r91b497],
18	this	DT	O	this	det	19	SENT_57	[p3l106t441r230b499],
19	identi?cation	NN	O	identi?cation	prep_of	16	SENT_57	[p3l254t440r719b499],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_57	[p3l254t440r719b499],

1	If	IN	O	if	mark	3	SENT_58	[p3l749t440r812b497],
2	this	DT	O	this	nsubj	3	SENT_58	[p3l827t440r950b498],
3	represents	VBZ	O	represent	advcl	18	SENT_58	[p3l975t449r1316b508],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_58	[p3l1340t441r1444b498],
5	contact	NN	O	contact	dobj	3	SENT_58	[p3l1470t447r1716b497],
6	between	IN	O	between	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1739t439r2016b497],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_58	[p3l2040t438r2143b497],
8	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	9	SENT_58	[p3l14t534r137b584],
9	formations	NNS	O	formation	prep_between	5	SENT_58	[p3l168t524r556b594],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l168t524r556b594],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_58	[p3l586t524r689b583],
12	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nsubj	18	SENT_58	[p3l719t524r1188b583],
13	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	18	SENT_58	[p3l1216t524r1269b581],
14	less	RBR	O	less	advmod	15	SENT_58	[p3l1297t524r1416b582],
15	than	IN	O	than	quantmod	16	SENT_58	[p3l1445t523r1596b581],
16	10	CD	NUMBER	10	num	17	SENT_58	[p3l1633t524r1704b581],
17	feet	NNS	O	foot	npadvmod	18	SENT_58	[p3l1737t523r1857b582],
18	thick	JJ	O	thick	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l1884t522r2055b581],
19	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l2082t532r2144b581],
20	this	DT	O	this	det	21	SENT_58	[p3l15t611r137b669],
21	locality	NN	O	locality	prep_at	18	SENT_58	[p3l162t611r425b681],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p3l162t611r425b681],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_59	[p3l456t610r586b669],
2	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	3	SENT_59	[p3l610t610r782b668],
3	unit	NN	O	unit	nsubjpass	9	SENT_59	[p3l808t609r944b668],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l968t610r1044b668],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_59	[p3l1059t611r1162b668],
6	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	7	SENT_59	[p3l1188t611r1418b668],
7	laurel	NN	O	laurel	prep_of	3	SENT_59	[p3l1445t609r1660b667],
8	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_59	[p3l1685t609r1739b666],
9	exposed	VBN	O	expose	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1763t609r2035b677],
10	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l2059t624r2144b666],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_59	[p3l14t697r117b754],
12	south	JJ	O	south	amod	13	SENT_59	[p3l138t696r322b754],
13	bank	NN	O	bank	prep_on	9	SENT_59	[p3l339t695r507b753],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l524t694r600b753],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_59	[p3l607t695r710b753],
16	canal	NN	O	canal	prep_of	13	SENT_59	[p3l729t694r906b753],
17	east	JJ	O	east	advmod	16	SENT_59	[p3l923t703r1054b753],
18	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1072t694r1147b753],
19	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_59	[p3l1155t694r1258b753],
20	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	22	SENT_59	[p3l1279t695r1361b752],
21	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	nn	22	SENT_59	[p3l1383t694r1656b764],
22	Bridge	NNP	LOCATION	Bridge	prep_of	16	SENT_59	[p3l1674t693r1910b764],
23	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p3l1674t693r1910b764],

1	About	IN	O	about	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1930t692r2144b751],
2	2.5	CD	NUMBER	2.5	num	3	SENT_60	[p3l17t782r116b839],
3	feet	NNS	O	foot	prep_about	24	SENT_60	[p3l143t780r264b839],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l288t780r363b839],
5	unweathered	JJ	O	unweathered	amod	11	SENT_60	[p3l376t780r807b839],
6	pale-gray	JJ	O	pale-gray	amod	11	SENT_60	[p3l830t781r1139b850],
7	very	RB	O	very	advmod	8	SENT_60	[p3l1162t795r1310b850],
8	clayey	JJ	O	clayey	amod	11	SENT_60	[p3l1332t779r1540b850],
9	glauconite	NN	O	glauconite	nn	11	SENT_60	[p3l1562t779r1907b849],
10	quartz	NN	O	quartz	nn	11	SENT_60	[p3l1929t787r2144b847],
11	sand	NN	O	sand	prep_of	3	SENT_60	[p3l16t866r170b925],
12	having	VBG	O	have	csubj	24	SENT_60	[p3l207t865r437b937],
13	a	DT	O	a	det	14	SENT_60	[p3l470t881r507b923],
14	composition	NN	O	composition	dobj	12	SENT_60	[p3l543t864r965b934],
15	apparently	RB	O	apparently	advmod	16	SENT_60	[p3l1001t865r1359b935],
16	similar	JJ	O	similar	amod	14	SENT_60	[p3l1396t864r1632b922],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1667t872r1732b922],
18	that	DT	O	that	prep_to	16	SENT_60	[p3l1770t865r1902b921],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1939t862r2014b921],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_60	[p3l2040t863r2143b921],
21	weathered	JJ	O	weathered	amod	22	SENT_60	[p3l15t950r359b1009],
22	bed	NN	O	bed	prep_of	18	SENT_60	[p3l381t949r502b1008],
23	just	RB	O	just	advmod	12	SENT_60	[p3l518t949r648b1020],
24	mentioned	VBD	O	mention	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l670t948r1033b1007],
25	crops	NNS	O	crop	dobj	24	SENT_60	[p3l1054t964r1235b1018],
26	out	IN	O	out	dep	24	SENT_60	[p3l1258t957r1368b1007],
27	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l1389t948r1486b1007],
28	a	DT	O	a	det	29	SENT_60	[p3l1507t965r1545b1007],
29	distance	NN	O	distance	prep_for	24	SENT_60	[p3l1567t947r1842b1006],
30	of	IN	O	of	prep	29	SENT_60	[p3l1865t947r1940b1006],
31	about	IN	O	about	pcomp	30	SENT_60	[p3l1952t948r2144b1006],
32	100	CD	NUMBER	100	num	33	SENT_60	[p3l25t1036r139b1093],
33	yards	NNS	O	yard	pobj	31	SENT_60	[p3l170t1036r369b1106],
34	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p3l170t1036r369b1106],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l401t1036r474b1092],
2	general	JJ	O	general	amod	3	SENT_61	[p3l501t1035r742b1105],
3	appearance	NN	O	appearance	prep_in	8	SENT_61	[p3l770t1050r1149b1103],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_61	[p3l1179t1033r1302b1092],
5	bed	NN	O	bed	nsubj	8	SENT_61	[p3l1329t1033r1451b1092],
6	resembles	VBZ	O	resemble	cop	8	SENT_61	[p3l1480t1033r1812b1092],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_61	[p3l1841t1034r1944b1091],
8	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1974t1033r2142b1090, p3l17t1120r340b1178],
9	because	IN	O	because	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l369t1120r628b1178],
10	of	IN	O	of	prepc_because_of	8	SENT_61	[p3l659t1119r735b1178],
11	its	PRP$	O	its	poss	14	SENT_61	[p3l752t1119r831b1177],
12	very	RB	O	very	advmod	13	SENT_61	[p3l859t1135r1007b1189],
13	clayey	JJ	O	clayey	amod	14	SENT_61	[p3l1036t1119r1244b1189],
14	nature	NN	O	nature	pobj	8	SENT_61	[p3l1272t1127r1506b1186],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1272t1127r1506b1186],
16	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l1536t1119r1648b1177],
17	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	19	SENT_61	[p3l1677t1118r1725b1176],
18	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	19	SENT_61	[p3l1752t1118r1806b1176],
19	lighter	JJR	O	lighter	conj_but	8	SENT_61	[p3l1835t1118r2051b1188],
20	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l2078t1118r2144b1174],
21	color	NN	O	color	prep_in	19	SENT_61	[p3l15t1206r203b1264],
22	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p3l15t1206r203b1264],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_62	[p3l239t1205r391b1263],
2	similarity	NN	O	similarity	nsubj	4	SENT_62	[p3l424t1205r747b1275],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	4	SENT_62	[p3l778t1205r831b1263],
4	deceptive	JJ	O	deceptive	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l864t1204r1185b1274],
5	because	IN	O	because	mark	18	SENT_62	[p3l1216t1204r1477b1263],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_62	[p3l1510t1205r1614b1262],
7	cement	NN	O	cement	nsubj	18	SENT_62	[p3l1645t1212r1891b1262],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1922t1203r1988b1260],
9	this	DT	O	this	det	10	SENT_62	[p3l2021t1202r2144b1261],
10	unit	NN	O	unit	prep_in	7	SENT_62	[p3l17t1290r152b1348],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l172t1289r247b1349],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_62	[p3l257t1292r360b1348],
13	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	14	SENT_62	[p3l382t1291r613b1348],
14	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	prep_of	10	SENT_62	[p3l631t1289r850b1348],
15	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	18	SENT_62	[p3l868t1288r921b1347],
16	mostly	RB	O	mostly	advmod	18	SENT_62	[p3l942t1289r1170b1359],
17	clay-sized	JJ	O	clay-sized	amod	18	SENT_62	[p3l1189t1289r1521b1359],
18	calcite	NN	O	calcite	advcl	4	SENT_62	[p3l1540t1288r1753b1346],
19	rather	RB	O	rather	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1774t1289r1976b1346],
20	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1994t1288r2144b1346],
21	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_62	[p3l16t1391r53b1433],
22	complex	JJ	O	complex	amod	23	SENT_62	[p3l76t1375r363b1444],
23	assemblage	NN	O	assemblage	conj_negcc	18	SENT_62	[p3l386t1375r764b1445],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l788t1374r863b1433],
25	clay	NN	O	clay	nn	26	SENT_62	[p3l877t1375r1011b1444],
26	minerals	NNS	O	mineral	prep_of	23	SENT_62	[p3l1034t1374r1325b1432],
27	as	IN	O	as	prep	18	SENT_62	[p3l1348t1390r1415b1432],
28	in	IN	O	in	pcomp	27	SENT_62	[p3l1438t1374r1506b1430],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	30	SENT_62	[p3l1528t1375r1631b1432],
30	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	pobj	28	SENT_62	[p3l1656t1373r2142b1432],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p3l1656t1373r2142b1432],

1	KENNEDY	NNP	O	KENNEDY	nn	5	SENT_63	[p3l252t1688r450b1716],
2	AND	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l458t1688r542b1716],
3	COBBAN	NNP	O	COBBAN	conj_and	1	SENT_63	[p3l557t1688r750b1717],
4	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	5	SENT_63	[p3l557t1688r750b1717],
5	UPPER	NNP	O	UPPER	_	0	SENT_63	[p3l759t1689r886b1718],
6	CRETACEO	NNP	O	CRETACEO	nn	8	SENT_63	[p3l901t1689r1117b1719],
7	US	NNP	LOCATION	US	nn	8	SENT_63	[p3l1123t1690r1172b1719],
8	AMMONITES	NNP	O	AMMONITES	dep	5	SENT_63	[p3l1180t1691r1435b1720],
9	63	CD	NUMBER	63	dep	5	SENT_63	[p3l1869t1693r1907b1722],

1	Therefore	RB	O	therefore	advmod	13	SENT_64	[p3l23t1816r371b1887],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l23t1816r371b1887],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_64	[p3l401t1818r504b1876],
4	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	6	SENT_64	[p3l532t1818r703b1876],
5	Mount	NNP	O	Mount	nn	6	SENT_64	[p3l732t1819r963b1876],
6	laurel	NN	O	laurel	nsubj	13	SENT_64	[p3l990t1817r1206b1876],
7	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1234t1826r1296b1876],
8	this	DT	O	this	det	9	SENT_64	[p3l1324t1816r1447b1875],
9	locality	NN	O	locality	prep_at	6	SENT_64	[p3l1474t1816r1721b1888],
10	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	13	SENT_64	[p3l1748t1816r1801b1875],
11	an	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_64	[p3l1830t1833r1910b1875],
12	arenaceous	JJ	O	arenaceous	amod	13	SENT_64	[p3l1938t1833r2147b1875, p3l23t1920r209b1961],
13	calcilutite	NN	O	calcilutite	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l235t1902r562b1961],
14	or	CC	O	or	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l589t1920r661b1961],
15	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_64	[p3l686t1920r723b1961],
16	very	RB	O	very	advmod	17	SENT_64	[p3l749t1920r897b1974],
17	calcareous	JJ	O	calcareous	amod	20	SENT_64	[p3l924t1903r1273b1961],
18	glauconite	NN	O	glauconite	nn	20	SENT_64	[p3l1298t1902r1642b1973],
19	quartz	NN	O	quartz	nn	20	SENT_64	[p3l1669t1912r1883b1971],
20	sand	NN	O	sand	conj_or	13	SENT_64	[p3l1911t1903r2084b1971],
21	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1911t1903r2084b1971],
22	a	DT	O	a	det	23	SENT_64	[p3l2113t1919r2150b1960],
23	lithology	NN	O	lithology	npadvmod	24	SENT_64	[p3l24t1987r319b2059],
24	not	RB	O	not	neg	25	SENT_64	[p3l347t1997r459b2045],
25	observed	VBN	O	observe	partmod	13	SENT_64	[p3l488t1988r793b2046],
26	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l821t1987r886b2044],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_64	[p3l917t1988r1019b2045],
28	formation	NN	O	formation	prep_in	25	SENT_64	[p3l1050t1986r1388b2045],
29	elsewhere	RB	O	elsewhere	advmod	25	SENT_64	[p3l1416t1988r1759b2045],
30	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p3l1416t1988r1759b2045],

1	Fossils	NNS	O	fossil	nsubj	3	SENT_65	[p3l1793t1987r2020b2045],
2	are	VBP	O	be	cop	3	SENT_65	[p3l2048t2004r2148b2046],
3	abundant	JJ	O	abundant	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l24t2074r344b2131],
4	along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l367t2074r549b2144],
5	this	DT	O	this	det	7	SENT_65	[p3l571t2072r694b2131],
6	south-bank	JJ	O	south-bank	amod	7	SENT_65	[p3l719t2073r1101b2131],
7	exposure	NN	O	exposure	prep_along	3	SENT_65	[p3l1123t2089r1441b2142],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1123t2089r1441b2142],
9	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1466t2074r1579b2131],
10	Exogyra	NNP	O	Exogyra	nn	11	SENT_65	[p3l1600t2075r1888b2143],
11	cancellata	NN	O	cancella	nsubj	12	SENT_65	[p3l1913t2071r2146b2131, p3l26t2156r152b2216],
12	occurs	VBZ	O	occur	conj_but	3	SENT_65	[p3l176t2174r391b2216],
13	here	RB	O	here	dobj	12	SENT_65	[p3l415t2158r557b2216],
14	rather	RB	O	rather	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l583t2158r785b2216],
15	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l807t2158r959b2216],
16	E.	NNP	O	E.	nn	17	SENT_65	[p3l980t2160r1057b2215],
17	ponderosa	NNP	O	ponderosa	dobj	12	SENT_65	[p3l1079t2156r1445b2227],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p3l1079t2156r1445b2227],

1	Locally	RB	O	locally	advmod	12	SENT_66	[p3l1473t2159r1739b2228],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1473t2159r1739b2228],
3	small	JJ	O	small	amod	6	SENT_66	[p3l1768t2159r1946b2216],
4	darkbrown	JJ	O	darkbrown	amod	6	SENT_66	[p3l1971t2159r2148b2216, p3l23t2243r238b2300],
5	phosphatized	JJ	O	phosphatized	amod	6	SENT_66	[p3l266t2243r716b2312],
6	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	nsubj	12	SENT_66	[p3l742t2242r947b2300],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l975t2242r1050b2301],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_66	[p3l1067t2243r1169b2300],
9	same	JJ	O	same	amod	10	SENT_66	[p3l1199t2259r1369b2301],
10	types	NNS	O	type	prep_of	6	SENT_66	[p3l1396t2252r1571b2313],
11	are	VBP	O	be	cop	12	SENT_66	[p3l1598t2259r1698b2300],
12	present	JJ	DATE	present	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1727t2253r1987b2312],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p3l1727t2253r1987b2312],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_67	[p3l2019t2243r2150b2300],
2	origin	NN	O	origin	nsubjpass	9	SENT_67	[p3l25t2328r222b2398],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l244t2327r320b2386],
4	these	DT	O	these	det	6	SENT_67	[p3l333t2328r502b2386],
5	phosphatic	JJ	O	phosphatic	amod	6	SENT_67	[p3l526t2328r896b2397],
6	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	prep_of	2	SENT_67	[p3l919t2327r1123b2386],
7	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_67	[p3l1145t2328r1199b2386],
8	not	RB	O	not	neg	9	SENT_67	[p3l1222t2337r1332b2386],
9	known	VBN	O	know	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1355t2330r1600b2396],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1355t2330r1600b2396],
11	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1623t2329r1736b2386],
12	they	PRP	O	they	nsubj	13	SENT_67	[p3l1758t2329r1902b2398],
13	appear	VBP	O	appear	conj_but	9	SENT_67	[p3l1924t2344r2151b2398],
14	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_67	[p3l25t2422r91b2471],
15	be	VB	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_67	[p3l126t2413r203b2470],
16	derived	VBN	O	derive	xcomp	13	SENT_67	[p3l239t2413r494b2471],
17	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l529t2412r692b2471],
18	a	DT	O	a	det	20	SENT_67	[p3l729t2430r766b2471],
19	different	JJ	O	different	amod	20	SENT_67	[p3l800t2412r1082b2470],
20	source	NN	O	source	prep_from	16	SENT_67	[p3l1119t2429r1330b2471],
21	than	IN	O	than	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l1366t2413r1518b2470],
22	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_67	[p3l1552t2413r1656b2471],
23	larger	JJR	O	larger	amod	25	SENT_67	[p3l1692t2414r1881b2484],
24	calcitic	JJ	O	calcitic	amod	25	SENT_67	[p3l1916t2413r2151b2471],
25	shells	NNS	O	shell	prep_than	20	SENT_67	[p3l27t2498r270b2556],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p3l27t2498r270b2556],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_68	[p3l27t2498r270b2556],

1	It	PRP	O	it	nsubj	3	SENT_69	[p3l103t2585r156b2640],
2	would	MD	O	would	aux	3	SENT_69	[p3l180t2584r388b2641],
3	appear	VB	O	appear	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l413t2599r640b2652],
4	that	IN	O	that	complm	11	SENT_69	[p3l663t2583r796b2640],
5	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	nsubj	11	SENT_69	[p3l822t2584r1049b2640],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1073t2583r1198b2640],
7	Minard	NNP	PERSON	Minard	conj_and	5	SENT_69	[p3l1224t2583r1476b2641],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_69	[p3l1501t2583r1717b2653],
9	1970	CD	DATE	1970	num	10	SENT_69	[p3l1501t2583r1717b2653],
10	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	7	SENT_69	[p3l1501t2583r1717b2653],
11	assigned	VBN	O	assign	ccomp	3	SENT_69	[p3l1742t2583r2023b2653],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_69	[p3l2048t2584r2150b2641],
13	condensed	JJ	O	condensed	amod	15	SENT_69	[p3l26t2668r381b2725],
14	glauconitic	JJ	O	glauconitic	amod	15	SENT_69	[p3l396t2667r764b2738],
15	unit	NN	O	unit	dobj	11	SENT_69	[p3l781t2668r916b2725],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l934t2677r1000b2725],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	20	SENT_69	[p3l1019t2668r1121b2725],
18	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	20	SENT_69	[p3l1141t2668r1609b2725],
19	Formation	NN	O	formation	nn	20	SENT_69	[p3l1625t2668r1987b2726],
20	west	NN	O	west	prep_to	11	SENT_69	[p3l2003t2677r2152b2726],
21	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l27t2752r102b2811],
22	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	23	SENT_69	[p3l128t2754r210b2811],
23	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_of	20	SENT_69	[p3l250t2754r521b2824],
24	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l556t2754r680b2811],
25	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l715t2763r780b2811],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_69	[p3l817t2753r919b2811],
27	Mount	NNP	LOCATION	Mount	nn	28	SENT_69	[p3l956t2755r1185b2811],
28	Laurel	NNP	LOCATION	Laurel	conj_and	20	SENT_69	[p3l1222t2754r1436b2811],
29	east	JJ	O	east	dep	11	SENT_69	[p3l1471t2763r1601b2811],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1636t2752r1712b2811],
31	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	32	SENT_69	[p3l1738t2755r1819b2811],
32	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_of	11	SENT_69	[p3l1859t2754r2146b2825],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p3l1859t2754r2146b2825],

1	Most	JJS	O	most	nsubj	10	SENT_70	[p3l27t2839r201b2895],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l230t2836r306b2895],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_70	[p3l325t2838r427b2895],
4	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	prep_of	1	SENT_70	[p3l460t2836r664b2895],
5	described	VBN	O	describe	partmod	4	SENT_70	[p3l693t2837r1014b2895],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1044t2837r1111b2893],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_70	[p3l1139t2838r1242b2895],
8	present	JJ	DATE	present	amod	9	SENT_70	[p3l1274t2847r1518b2906],
9	report	NN	O	report	prep_in	5	SENT_70	[p3l1547t2846r1752b2907],
10	came	VBD	O	come	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1782t2854r1956b2896],
11	from	IN	O	from	dep	10	SENT_70	[p3l1988t2837r2150b2896],
12	about	IN	O	about	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l26t2923r218b2981],
13	two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	14	SENT_70	[p3l246t2932r369b2981],
14	meters	NNS	O	meter	prep_about	10	SENT_70	[p3l400t2932r624b2981],
15	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l654t2921r731b2981],
16	dark	JJ	O	dark	amod	21	SENT_70	[p3l749t2923r919b2991],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l749t2923r919b2991],
18	glauconitic	JJ	O	glauconitic	amod	21	SENT_70	[p3l950t2922r1337b2993],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l950t2922r1337b2993],
20	clayey	JJ	O	clayey	amod	21	SENT_70	[p3l1367t2924r1576b2993],
21	sand	NN	O	sand	prep_of	14	SENT_70	[p3l1606t2924r1761b2981],
22	exposed	VBN	O	expose	partmod	21	SENT_70	[p3l1790t2924r2060b2992],
23	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l2090t2933r2152b2981],
24	low	JJ	O	low	amod	25	SENT_70	[p3l27t3008r147b3065],
25	tide	NN	O	tide	prep_at	22	SENT_70	[p3l169t3007r295b3065],
26	along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l320t3008r503b3079],
27	the	DT	O	the	det	29	SENT_70	[p3l524t3008r626b3065],
28	south	JJ	O	south	amod	29	SENT_70	[p3l652t3008r836b3065],
29	side	NN	O	side	prep_along	25	SENT_70	[p3l860t3007r990b3065],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1016t3006r1091b3065],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_70	[p3l1103t3008r1207b3065],
32	canal	NN	O	canal	prep_of	29	SENT_70	[p3l1231t3009r1406b3066],
33	just	RB	O	just	advmod	34	SENT_70	[p3l1421t3008r1551b3078],
34	east	JJ	O	east	advmod	32	SENT_70	[p3l1573t3017r1703b3066],
35	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1726t3007r1802b3066],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_70	[p3l1815t3008r1918b3066],
37	bridge	NN	O	bridge	prep_of	32	SENT_70	[p3l1941t3008r2150b3079],
38	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l26t3102r89b3150],
39	St.	NNP	LOCATION	St.	nn	40	SENT_70	[p3l113t3093r195b3150],
40	Georges	NNP	LOCATION	Georges	prep_at	37	SENT_70	[p3l223t3093r513b3163],
41	;	:	O	;	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l223t3093r513b3163],
42	we	PRP	O	we	nsubj	43	SENT_70	[p3l538t3109r628b3150],
43	believe	VBP	O	believe	parataxis	10	SENT_70	[p3l652t3092r891b3150],
44	it	PRP	O	it	nsubj	48	SENT_70	[p3l915t3092r963b3150],
45	to	TO	O	to	aux	48	SENT_70	[p3l985t3102r1051b3150],
46	be	VB	O	be	cop	48	SENT_70	[p3l1075t3093r1152b3150],
47	the	DT	O	the	det	48	SENT_70	[p3l1176t3093r1279b3150],
48	unit	NN	O	unit	xcomp	43	SENT_70	[p3l1303t3092r1438b3150],
49	assigned	VBN	O	assign	partmod	48	SENT_70	[p3l1461t3092r1742b3163],
50	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1764t3102r1830b3151],
51	the	DT	O	the	det	54	SENT_70	[p3l1854t3093r1956b3151],
52	basal	JJ	O	basal	amod	54	SENT_70	[p3l1980t3093r2151b3151],
53	Mount	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Mount	nn	54	SENT_70	[p3l26t3180r256b3235],
54	Laurel	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Laurel	prep_to	49	SENT_70	[p3l282t3179r499b3235],
55	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l524t3178r606b3248],
56	Owens	NNP	PERSON	Owens	agent	49	SENT_70	[p3l633t3179r860b3235],
57	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l886t3178r1011b3235],
58	Minard	NNP	PERSON	Minard	conj_and	48	SENT_70	[p3l1038t3177r1291b3235],
59	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	58	SENT_70	[p3l1317t3178r1549b3248],
60	1970	CD	DATE	1970	num	61	SENT_70	[p3l1317t3178r1549b3248],
61	)	NN	O	)	dep	58	SENT_70	[p3l1317t3178r1549b3248],
62	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p3l1317t3178r1549b3248],

1	MARSHALLTOWN	NNP	LOCATION	MARSHALLTOWN	nn	2	SENT_71	[p3l481t3375r1015b3419],
2	MOLLUSCAN	NNP	O	MOLLUSCAN	_	0	SENT_71	[p3l1044t3375r1432b3419],
3	FOSSILS	NNS	O	fossil	dep	2	SENT_71	[p3l1460t3375r1694b3419],

1	Along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l102t33r305b104],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_72	[p4l330t34r434b91],
3	Chesapeake	NNP	LOCATION	Chesapeake	nn	6	SENT_72	[p4l463t34r857b102],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l886t34r1011b91],
5	Delaware	NNP	LOCATION	Delaware	conj_and	3	SENT_72	[p4l1038t35r1355b91],
6	Canal	NNP	LOCATION	Canal	prep_along	17	SENT_72	[p4l1384t34r1596b102],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1384t34r1596b102],
8	Sohl	NNP	PERSON	Sohl	nsubj	17	SENT_72	[p4l1629t34r1775b92],
9	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1803t35r1928b92],
10	Mello	NNP	PERSON	Mello	nsubj	17	SENT_72	[p4l1956t36r2150b92],
11	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_72	[p4l26t117r237b187],
12	1970	CD	DATE	1970	dep	8	SENT_72	[p4l26t117r237b187],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l26t117r237b187],
14	p.	NN	O	p.	nn	16	SENT_72	[p4l269t133r328b186],
15	41	CD	NUMBER	41	num	16	SENT_72	[p4l363t118r469b186],
16	)	NN	O	)	appos	8	SENT_72	[p4l363t118r469b186],
17	reported	VBD	O	report	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l498t118r783b186],
18	72	CD	NUMBER	72	num	19	SENT_72	[p4l816t118r895b174],
19	genera	NN	O	genus	dep	24	SENT_72	[p4l925t134r1145b188],
20	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1175t116r1250b175],
21	mollusks	NNS	O	mollusk	prep_of	19	SENT_72	[p4l1269t119r1570b175],
22	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	24	SENT_72	[p4l1601t119r1703b188],
23	39	CD	NUMBER	39	num	24	SENT_72	[p4l1601t119r1703b188],
24	bivalves	NNS	O	bivalve	dep	17	SENT_72	[p4l1737t118r2035b186],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1737t118r2035b186],
26	30	CD	NUMBER	30	num	27	SENT_72	[p4l2071t119r2149b176],
27	gastropods	NNS	O	gastropod	dep	17	SENT_72	[p4l24t202r406b271],
28	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l24t202r406b271],
29	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l444t202r568b259],
30	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	31	SENT_72	[p4l608t202r641b258],
31	cephalopods	NNS	O	cephalopod	dep	17	SENT_72	[p4l681t202r1125b271],
32	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dobj	17	SENT_72	[p4l681t202r1125b271],
33	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l1161t200r1325b259],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_72	[p4l1360t202r1464b260],
35	Marshalltown	NNP	O	Marshalltown	nn	36	SENT_72	[p4l1502t202r1969b260],
36	Formation	NN	O	formation	prep_from	32	SENT_72	[p4l2005t204r2149b260, p4l26t284r284b342],
37	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p4l2005t204r2149b260, p4l26t284r284b342],

1	They	PRP	O	they	nsubj	2	SENT_73	[p4l310t285r482b355],
2	noted	VBD	O	note	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l503t286r694b343],
3	that	IN	O	that	complm	8	SENT_73	[p4l715t286r848b343],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_73	[p4l868t286r971b343],
5	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	nsubjpass	8	SENT_73	[p4l995t284r1199b343],
6	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_73	[p4l1218t302r1374b343],
7	generally	RB	O	generally	advmod	8	SENT_73	[p4l1396t287r1698b356],
8	concentrated	VBN	O	concentrate	ccomp	2	SENT_73	[p4l1718t288r2152b344],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l25t368r92b425],
10	certain	JJ	O	certain	amod	11	SENT_73	[p4l110t368r340b427],
11	beds	NNS	O	bed	prep_in	8	SENT_73	[p4l357t369r528b437],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l357t369r528b437],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l549t370r674b427],
14	that	IN	O	that	complm	32	SENT_73	[p4l692t370r824b427],
15	Exogyra	NNP	O	Exogyra	nn	16	SENT_73	[p4l840t371r1128b440],
16	ponderosa	NN	O	ponderosa	nsubj	32	SENT_73	[p4l1142t368r1509b438],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l1142t368r1509b438],
18	Agerostreafalcata	NNP	O	Agerostreafalcata	nn	21	SENT_73	[p4l1525t369r2148b441],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l1525t369r2148b441],
20	large	JJ	O	large	amod	21	SENT_73	[p4l27t453r185b523],
21	Trigonia	NNP	O	Trigonia	appos	16	SENT_73	[p4l219t455r524b523],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l219t455r524b523],
23	Cardium	NNP	O	Cardium	conj_and	21	SENT_73	[p4l559t451r876b522],
24	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l559t451r876b522],
25	Cucullaea	NNP	LOCATION	Cucullaea	conj_and	21	SENT_73	[p4l910t452r1262b522],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l910t452r1262b522],
27	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l1292t455r1417b512],
28	Cyprimeria	NNP	LOCATION	Cyprimeria	appos	16	SENT_73	[p4l1446t455r1846b524],
29	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l1446t455r1846b524],
30	were	VBD	O	be	cop	32	SENT_73	[p4l1874t472r2030b513],
31	especially	RB	O	especially	advmod	32	SENT_73	[p4l2058t472r2149b513, p4l26t536r284b607],
32	abundant	JJ	O	abundant	conj_and	8	SENT_73	[p4l310t538r646b595],
33	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p4l310t538r646b595],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_74	[p4l677t538r807b596],
2	cephalopods	NNS	O	cephalopod	nsubj	6	SENT_74	[p4l835t538r1256b607],
3	reported	VBN	O	report	partmod	2	SENT_74	[p4l1283t539r1567b608],
4	were	VBD	O	be	cop	6	SENT_74	[p4l1592t555r1747b597],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_74	[p4l1776t539r1879b597],
6	ammonites	NNS	O	ammonite	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l1907t556r2149b597, p4l26t619r185b678],
7	Didymoceras	NNP	O	Didymoceras	dep	6	SENT_74	[p4l206t618r677b690],
8	?	.	O	?	_	0	SENT_74	[p4l206t618r677b690],

1	sp.	NN	O	sp.	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l701t637r812b690],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l701t637r812b690],
3	Anapachydiscus	NNP	O	Anapachydiscus	nn	4	SENT_75	[p4l833t619r1371b691],
4	sp.	NNP	O	sp.	appos	1	SENT_75	[p4l1391t638r1501b691],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1391t638r1501b691],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l1525t623r1650b679],
7	Parapachydiscus	NN	O	parapachydiscus	nn	8	SENT_75	[p4l1670t621r2147b692, p4l27t721r132b763],
8	sp	NN	O	sp	appos	1	SENT_75	[p4l154t721r242b774],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p4l154t721r242b774],

1	Sohl	NNP	PERSON	Sohl	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l270t705r417b763],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	1	SENT_76	[p4l440t706r651b775],
3	1977	CD	DATE	1977	dep	1	SENT_76	[p4l440t706r651b775],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l440t706r651b775],
5	p.	NN	O	p.	nn	7	SENT_76	[p4l676t722r734b775],
6	89	CD	NUMBER	89	num	7	SENT_76	[p4l765t706r868b775],
7	)	NN	O	)	appos	1	SENT_76	[p4l765t706r868b775],
8	observed	VBN	O	observe	partmod	7	SENT_76	[p4l891t706r1196b764],
9	that	IN	O	that	complm	15	SENT_76	[p4l1216t706r1350b764],
10	most	JJS	O	most	amod	11	SENT_76	[p4l1371t716r1538b764],
11	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	nsubj	15	SENT_76	[p4l1561t705r1765b764],
12	were	VBD	O	be	cop	15	SENT_76	[p4l1786t724r1941b765],
13	phosphatic	JJ	O	phosphatic	amod	15	SENT_76	[p4l1964t708r2149b776, p4l26t788r234b858],
14	intemal	JJ	O	intemal	amod	15	SENT_76	[p4l271t788r533b847],
15	molds	NNS	O	mold	ccomp	8	SENT_76	[p4l572t790r797b858],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l572t790r797b858],
17	but	CC	O	but	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l837t790r950b847],
18	that	IN	O	that	complm	24	SENT_76	[p4l988t790r1121b848],
19	calcitic-shelled	JJ	O	calcitic-shelled	amod	20	SENT_76	[p4l1159t789r1659b848],
20	ostreids	NNS	O	ostreid	nsubj	24	SENT_76	[p4l1696t790r1956b849],
21	were	VBD	O	be	cop	24	SENT_76	[p4l1995t808r2150b849],
22	commonly	RB	O	commonly	advmod	23	SENT_76	[p4l25t874r388b943],
23	preserved	JJ	O	preserved	advmod	24	SENT_76	[p4l421t874r749b942],
24	intact	JJ	O	intact	ccomp	8	SENT_76	[p4l782t873r989b931],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_76	[p4l782t873r989b931],

1	He	PRP	O	he	nsubj	3	SENT_77	[p4l1030t876r1125b931],
2	also	RB	O	also	advmod	3	SENT_77	[p4l1161t875r1291b932],
3	suggested	VBD	O	suggest	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1329t875r1644b945],
4	that	IN	O	that	complm	8	SENT_77	[p4l1677t875r1810b932],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_77	[p4l1844t875r1946b932],
6	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nsubjpass	8	SENT_77	[p4l1981t877r2149b933, p4l26t957r350b1014],
7	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_77	[p4l375t973r500b1015],
8	deposited	VBN	O	deposit	ccomp	3	SENT_77	[p4l528t957r852b1026],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l878t957r944b1014],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_77	[p4l971t974r1008b1015],
11	shelf	NN	O	shelf	prep_in	8	SENT_77	[p4l1035t956r1200b1015],
12	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1216t967r1282b1015],
13	lower	JJR	O	lower	amod	15	SENT_77	[p4l1310t959r1496b1016],
14	shoreface	NN	O	shoreface	nn	15	SENT_77	[p4l1522t957r1835b1016],
15	environment	NN	O	environment	prep_to	8	SENT_77	[p4l1862t958r2149b1017, p4l26t1051r215b1099],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_77	[p4l1862t958r2149b1017, p4l26t1051r215b1099],

1	Some	DT	O	some	nsubjpass	9	SENT_78	[p4l243t1041r430b1099],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l455t1040r529b1099],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_78	[p4l542t1042r645b1099],
4	Marshalltown	NNP	LOCATION	Marshalltown	nn	5	SENT_78	[p4l671t1042r1139b1100],
5	bivalves	NNS	O	bivalve	prep_of	1	SENT_78	[p4l1159t1041r1441b1100],
6	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1464t1043r1588b1100],
7	gastropods	NNS	O	gastropod	prep_of	1	SENT_78	[p4l1609t1044r1973b1114],
8	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_78	[p4l1995t1060r2150b1101],
9	illustrated	VBN	O	illustrate	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l25t1124r364b1182],
10	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l382t1125r464b1195],
11	Groot	NNP	O	Groot	agent	9	SENT_78	[p4l485t1126r688b1183],
12	et	FW	O	et	nn	14	SENT_78	[p4l704t1135r766b1183],
13	al.	FW	O	al.	nn	14	SENT_78	[p4l785t1126r860b1183],
14	(	FW	O	(	dobj	9	SENT_78	[p4l885t1126r1119b1195],
15	1954	CD	DATE	1954	num	16	SENT_78	[p4l885t1126r1119b1195],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubjpass	9	SENT_78	[p4l885t1126r1119b1195],
17	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l885t1126r1119b1195],
18	Pickett	NNP	PERSON	Pickett	appos	16	SENT_78	[p4l1141t1126r1375b1183],
19	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_78	[p4l1395t1127r1630b1196],
20	1972	CD	NUMBER	1972	num	21	SENT_78	[p4l1395t1127r1630b1196],
21	)	NNS	O	)	dep	18	SENT_78	[p4l1395t1127r1630b1196],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1395t1127r1630b1196],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l1651t1128r1775b1184],
24	Lauginiger	NNP	PERSON	Lauginiger	conj_and	18	SENT_78	[p4l1795t1126r2153b1197],
25	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	24	SENT_78	[p4l26t1209r259b1279],
26	1988	CD	DATE	1988	num	27	SENT_78	[p4l26t1209r259b1279],
27	)	NN	O	)	dep	24	SENT_78	[p4l26t1209r259b1279],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_78	[p4l26t1209r259b1279],
