1	Paleontological	NNP	O	Paleontological	nn	2	SENT_1	[p1l17t81r380b129],
2	Society	NNP	O	Society	_	0	SENT_1	[p1l398t81r574b129],

1	Trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l15t270r227b302],
2	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l248t270r364b302],
3	Lower	JJR	MISC	lower	prep_from	1	SENT_2	[p1l384t270r517b302],
4	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	nn	7	SENT_2	[p1l538t270r823b313],
5	Starved	NNP	MISC	Starved	nn	7	SENT_2	[p1l844t270r1008b302],
6	Basin	NNP	MISC	Basin	nn	7	SENT_2	[p1l1029t270r1141b302],
7	Facies	NNP	MISC	Facies	dep	15	SENT_2	[p1l1162t270r1286b302],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l1307t270r1353b302],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_2	[p1l1374t270r1445b302],
10	Southern	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Southern	nn	12	SENT_2	[p1l1466t270r1665b302],
11	United	NNP	ORGANIZATION	United	nn	12	SENT_2	[p1l1686t270r1833b302],
12	States	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	States	prep_of	7	SENT_2	[p1l1854t270r1980b302],
13	Author	NN	ORGANIZATION	author	dep	15	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
14	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	13	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
15	s	NNS	O	s	dep	3	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
16	)	CD	NUMBER	)	dep	15	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
17	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l15t320r232b359],
18	David	NNP	PERSON	David	nn	19	SENT_2	[p1l255t324r372b355],
19	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	dep	1	SENT_2	[p1l393t324r433b355],
20	Brezinski	NNP	PERSON	Brezinski	nn	21	SENT_2	[p1l457t324r661b355],
21	Source	NNP	O	Source	dep	19	SENT_2	[p1l15t377r166b409],
22	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l15t377r166b409],
23	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	dep	1	SENT_2	[p1l190t377r363b409],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l383t377r433b409],
25	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	nn	27	SENT_2	[p1l449t377r739b422],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l449t377r739b422],
27	Vol	NNP	O	Vol	prep_of	23	SENT_2	[p1l765t377r845b409],
28	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_2	[p1l765t377r845b409],

1	72	CD	NUMBER	72	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l868t377r925b414],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l868t377r925b414],
3	No.	NN	O	no.	nn	5	SENT_3	[p1l951t377r1018b409],
4	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	5	SENT_3	[p1l1042t377r1062b409],
5	(	NN	O	(	appos	1	SENT_3	[p1l1084t373r1193b414],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_3	[p1l1084t373r1193b414],

1	Tul	NNP	O	Tul	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1084t373r1193b414],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_4	[p1l1084t373r1193b414],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_5	[p1l1084t373r1193b414],

1	1998	CD	DATE	1998	num	2	SENT_6	[p1l1224t373r1340b414],
2	)	CD	NUMBER	)	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1224t373r1340b414],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1224t373r1340b414],
4	pp	NN	O	pp	appos	2	SENT_6	[p1l1366t388r1427b420],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_6	[p1l1366t388r1427b420],

1	http://www.j	NN	O	http://www.j	nn	2	SENT_13	[p1l14t1355r222b1393],
2	stor.org	NN	O	stor.org	_	0	SENT_13	[p1l227t1359r353b1393],

1	718	CD	NUMBER	718	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l325t1612r382b1641],
2	JOURNAL	NNP	O	JOURNAL	dep	1	SENT_14	[p1l952t1616r1124b1645],
3	OF	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1139t1617r1191b1646],
4	PALEONTOLOGY	NNP	O	PALEONTOLOGY	nn	6	SENT_14	[p1l1203t1618r1509b1652],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1203t1618r1509b1652],
6	V.	NNP	O	V.	prep_of	2	SENT_14	[p1l1528t1620r1555b1648],
7	72	CD	NUMBER	72	num	6	SENT_14	[p1l1576t1619r1618b1653],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1576t1619r1618b1653],
9	No.	NN	O	no.	appos	6	SENT_14	[p1l1635t1620r1696b1649],
10	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	9	SENT_14	[p1l1713t1620r1739b1653],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_14	[p1l1713t1620r1739b1653],
12	1998	CD	DATE	1998	dep	1	SENT_14	[p1l1758t1621r1835b1650],

1	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l88t1773r407b1827],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_15	[p1l88t1773r407b1827],

1	Paleontological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paleontological	nn	3	SENT_16	[p1l439t1776r895b1844],
2	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	nn	3	SENT_16	[p1l927t1778r1143b1845],
3	Memoir	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Memoir	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1173t1780r1409b1833],
4	6	CD	NUMBER	6	number	5	SENT_16	[p1l1436t1781r1471b1833],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	6	SENT_16	[p1l1501t1782r1738b1844],
6	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	dep	3	SENT_16	[p1l1501t1782r1738b1844],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1769t1782r1832b1835],
8	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	prep_of	6	SENT_16	[p1l1854t1784r2153b1837, p1l87t1865r208b1916],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l1854t1784r2153b1837, p1l87t1865r208b1916],
10	48	CD	NUMBER	48	number	11	SENT_16	[p1l238t1851r393b1914],
11	[	CD	NUMBER	[	appos	8	SENT_16	[p1l238t1851r393b1914],
12	5	CD	NUMBER	5	num	15	SENT_16	[p1l238t1851r393b1914],
13	]	NN	O	]	nn	15	SENT_16	[p1l238t1851r393b1914],
14	Supplement	NN	O	supplement	nn	15	SENT_16	[p1l425t1852r814b1918],
15	)	NN	O	)	dep	11	SENT_16	[p1l425t1852r814b1918],
16	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_16	[p1l425t1852r814b1918],
17	54	CD	NUMBER	54	num	18	SENT_16	[p1l843t1854r914b1905],
18	p.	NN	O	p.	dep	3	SENT_16	[p1l941t1869r990b1920],

1	SMITH	NNP	O	SMITH	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l19t1926r220b1988],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l19t1926r220b1988],
3	A.	NNP	O	A.	nn	4	SENT_17	[p1l254t1929r320b1979],
4	B.	NNP	O	B.	appos	1	SENT_17	[p1l355t1928r417b1979],
5	1994	CD	DATE	1994	dep	4	SENT_17	[p1l462t1929r613b1980],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_17	[p1l462t1929r613b1980],

1	Systematics	NNS	O	systematic	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l651t1929r997b1996],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1032t1931r1135b1983],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_18	[p1l1168t1932r1255b1984],
4	Fossil	NNP	MISC	Fossil	nn	5	SENT_18	[p1l1288t1932r1460b1985],
5	Record	NNP	MISC	Record	conj_and	1	SENT_18	[p1l1493t1934r1719b1986],
6	:	:	MISC	:	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l1493t1934r1719b1986],
7	Documenting	VBG	MISC	document	dep	1	SENT_18	[p1l1755t1936r2153b2004],
8	Evolutionary	JJ	MISC	evolutionary	amod	9	SENT_18	[p1l85t2004r452b2071],
9	Pattems	NN	MISC	pattem	dobj	7	SENT_18	[p1l478t2006r715b2058],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_18	[p1l478t2006r715b2058],

1	Blackwell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Blackwell	nn	3	SENT_19	[p1l742t2007r1026b2059],
2	Scienti?c	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Scienti?c	nn	3	SENT_19	[p1l1053t2008r1313b2060],
3	Publications	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Publications	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1339t2009r1696b2072],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1339t2009r1696b2072],
5	Oxford	NNP	LOCATION	Oxford	appos	3	SENT_19	[p1l1725t2011r1940b2073],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l1725t2011r1940b2073],
7	223	CD	NUMBER	223	num	9	SENT_19	[p1l1969t2012r2068b2065],
8	p.	NN	O	p.	nn	9	SENT_19	[p1l2098t2029r2145b2081],
9	SWOFFORD	NNP	PERSON	SWOFFORD	appos	3	SENT_19	[p1l17t2079r352b2140],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l17t2079r352b2140],
11	D.	NNP	O	D.	nn	12	SENT_19	[p1l376t2082r441b2133],
12	L.	NNP	O	L.	appos	3	SENT_19	[p1l465t2083r522b2133],
13	1993	CD	DATE	1993	dep	12	SENT_19	[p1l554t2082r706b2135],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_19	[p1l554t2082r706b2135],

1	PAUP	NNP	O	PAUP	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l730t2084r929b2135],
2	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l730t2084r929b2135],
3	Phylogenetic	NNP	O	Phylogenetic	nn	4	SENT_20	[p1l954t2084r1336b2151],
4	Analysis	NNP	O	Analysis	dep	1	SENT_20	[p1l1357t2086r1611b2153],
5	Using	VBG	O	use	partmod	4	SENT_20	[p1l1633t2086r1805b2154],
6	Parsimony	NN	O	parsimony	dobj	5	SENT_20	[p1l1824t2088r2150b2157],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l1824t2088r2150b2157],
8	Version	NNP	O	Version	appos	6	SENT_20	[p1l83t2156r307b2209],
9	3.1.1	CD	NUMBER	3.1.1	num	8	SENT_20	[p1l332t2156r491b2210],
10	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_20	[p1l332t2156r491b2210],

1	Program	NN	O	program	nsubj	2	SENT_21	[p1l516t2159r768b2225],
2	distributed	VBN	O	distribute	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l789t2158r1103b2212],
3	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l1123t2160r1194b2227],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_21	[p1l1216t2161r1304b2214],
5	Illinois	NNP	O	Illinois	nn	8	SENT_21	[p1l1324t2161r1529b2215],
6	Natural	NNP	O	Natural	nn	8	SENT_21	[p1l1552t2163r1771b2216],
7	History	NN	O	history	nn	8	SENT_21	[p1l1791t2164r2012b2231],
8	Survey	NN	O	survey	prep_by	2	SENT_21	[p1l2032t2165r2150b2217, p1l83t2248r200b2299],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l2032t2165r2150b2217, p1l83t2248r200b2299],
10	Champaign	NNP	LOCATION	Champaign	appos	8	SENT_21	[p1l231t2233r585b2300],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_21	[p1l231t2233r585b2300],

1	THOMSON	NNP	LOCATION	THOMSON	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l13t2304r322b2365],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l13t2304r322b2365],
3	C.	NNP	O	C.	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l352t2305r414b2358],
4	W.	NNP	O	W.	nn	5	SENT_22	[p1l446t2306r520b2357],
5	1857	NNP	DATE	1857	appos	1	SENT_22	[p1l559t2306r711b2358],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_22	[p1l559t2306r711b2358],

1	On	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l745t2307r830b2359],
2	some	DT	O	some	det	3	SENT_23	[p1l861t2322r1013b2359],
3	species	NNS	O	species	pobj	1	SENT_23	[p1l1042t2308r1249b2374],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1279t2308r1343b2360],
5	Acidaspis	NNP	O	Acidaspis	prep_of	3	SENT_23	[p1l1361t2309r1649b2376],
6	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l1678t2310r1818b2363],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_23	[p1l1845t2312r1933b2363],
8	Lower	NNP	O	Lower	nn	10	SENT_23	[p1l1960t2313r2152b2364],
9	Silurian	NNP	O	Silurian	nn	10	SENT_23	[p1l83t2380r312b2433],
10	Beds	NNPS	O	Beds	prep_from	5	SENT_23	[p1l338t2381r481b2434],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l509t2381r572b2434],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_23	[p1l592t2383r680b2435],
13	south	NN	O	south	prep_of	10	SENT_23	[p1l706t2383r862b2435],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l888t2383r951b2436],
15	Scotland	NNP	LOCATION	Scotland	prep_of	13	SENT_23	[p1l972t2384r1241b2436],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_23	[p1l972t2384r1241b2436],

1	Quarterly	JJ	SET	quarterly	amod	2	SENT_24	[p1l1270t2385r1548b2452],
2	Journal	NNP	O	Journal	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1572t2387r1787b2439],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l1812t2387r1876b2440],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_24	[p1l1894t2388r1982b2440],
5	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	6	SENT_24	[p1l2006t2388r2148b2441, p1l82t2459r279b2525],
6	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_of	2	SENT_24	[p1l308t2459r525b2526],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l555t2460r617b2512],
8	London	NNP	ORGANIZATION	London	prep_of	2	SENT_24	[p1l640t2461r883b2521],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l640t2461r883b2521],
10	13:206	CD	NUMBER	13:206	num	11	SENT_24	[p1l921t2461r1278b2514],
11	-210	CD	NUMBER	-210	appos	8	SENT_24	[p1l921t2461r1278b2514],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_24	[p1l921t2461r1278b2514],

1	~	NN	O	~	_	0	SENT_25	[p1l1419t2491r1424b2498],

1	TRIPP	NN	LOCATION	tripp	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l12t2532r192b2590],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l12t2532r192b2590],
3	R.	NNP	O	R.	nn	4	SENT_26	[p1l222t2533r283b2582],
4	P.	NNP	O	P.	appos	1	SENT_26	[p1l313t2533r355b2583],
5	1993	CD	DATE	1993	dep	4	SENT_26	[p1l392t2533r545b2585],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_26	[p1l392t2533r545b2585],

1	Review	NN	O	review	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l575t2533r795b2585],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l824t2534r888b2585],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_27	[p1l908t2535r996b2586],
4	trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	prep_of	1	SENT_27	[p1l1022t2535r1281b2587],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l1308t2535r1448b2587],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_27	[p1l1473t2537r1561b2588],
7	Middle	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Middle	nn	10	SENT_27	[p1l1585t2537r1796b2589],
8	Ordovician	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Ordovician	nn	10	SENT_27	[p1l1821t2538r2148b2590],
9	Barr	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Barr	nn	10	SENT_27	[p1l79t2608r212b2659],
10	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	prep_from	4	SENT_27	[p1l236t2608r438b2675],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l236t2608r438b2675],
12	Girvan	NNP	PERSON	Girvan	nn	13	SENT_27	[p1l469t2608r674b2661],
13	district	NN	O	district	appos	1	SENT_27	[p1l703t2609r922b2670],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l703t2609r922b2670],
15	Scotland	NNP	LOCATION	Scotland	appos	1	SENT_27	[p1l953t2610r1222b2663],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_27	[p1l953t2610r1222b2663],

1	TSCHERNYSCHEW	NNP	LOCATION	TSCHERNYSCHEW	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l11t2759r542b2819],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l11t2759r542b2819],
3	A.	NNP	O	A.	appos	1	SENT_29	[p1l576t2761r643b2811],
4	1893	CD	DATE	1893	num	3	SENT_29	[p1l685t2760r838b2812],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_29	[p1l685t2760r838b2812],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_30	[p1l871t2762r985b2812],
2	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1017t2761r1179b2813],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1211t2762r1274b2813],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_30	[p1l1301t2763r1388b2814],
5	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	6	SENT_30	[p1l1420t2764r1612b2815],
6	Devonian	NNP	MISC	Devonian	prep_of	2	SENT_30	[p1l1642t2765r1924b2816],
7	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l1959t2781r2027b2817],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_30	[p1l2060t2767r2147b2817],
9	westem	NN	O	westem	nn	10	SENT_30	[p1l80t2842r306b2886],
10	slope	NN	O	slope	prep_on	2	SENT_30	[p1l340t2834r493b2902],
11	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l525t2834r589b2887],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_30	[p1l615t2835r702b2888],
13	Urals	NNS	MISC	ural	prep_of	2	SENT_30	[p1l734t2836r907b2888],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_30	[p1l734t2836r907b2888],

1	M?moires	NNP	MISC	M?moires	nn	4	SENT_31	[p1l941t2836r1236b2890],
2	du	NNP	MISC	du	nn	4	SENT_31	[p1l1269t2837r1340b2890],
3	Comit?	NNP	MISC	Comit?	nn	4	SENT_31	[p1l1371t2838r1586b2891],
4	G?ologique	NNP	MISC	G?ologique	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1617t2839r1974b2908],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l1617t2839r1974b2908],
6	4	CD	NUMBER	4	number	7	SENT_31	[p1l2007t2841r2143b2904],
7	(	CD	NUMBER	(	appos	4	SENT_31	[p1l2007t2841r2143b2904],
8	3	CD	NUMBER	3	num	9	SENT_31	[p1l2007t2841r2143b2904],
9	)	NN	O	)	dep	7	SENT_31	[p1l2007t2841r2143b2904],
10	:	:	O	:	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l2007t2841r2143b2904],
11	1-221	CD	NUMBER	1-221	dep	4	SENT_31	[p1l86t2910r275b2962],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_31	[p1l86t2910r275b2962],

1	[	NN	O	[	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l312t2912r389b2973],
2	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l312t2912r389b2973],
3	Russian	JJ	MISC	russian	prep_in	1	SENT_32	[p1l420t2912r649b2963],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l678t2912r781b2964],
5	German	JJ	MISC	german	prep_in	1	SENT_32	[p1l809t2913r1084b2975],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_32	[p1l809t2913r1084b2975],
7	]	SYM	O	]	dep	1	SENT_32	[p1l809t2913r1084b2975],

1	VOGDES	NNP	LOCATION	VOGDES	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l11t2983r269b3044],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l11t2983r269b3044],
3	A.	NNP	O	A.	nn	4	SENT_33	[p1l296t2985r362b3036],
4	W.	NNP	O	W.	appos	1	SENT_33	[p1l390t2985r463b3036],
5	1917	CD	DATE	1917	dep	4	SENT_33	[p1l498t2985r652b3037],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_33	[p1l498t2985r652b3037],

1	Palaeozoic	JJ	PERSON	palaeozoic	amod	2	SENT_34	[p1l679t2985r995b3038],
2	Crustacea	NN	PERSON	crustacea	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1020t2986r1324b3040],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_34	[p1l1020t2986r1324b3040],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_35	[p1l1350t2988r1463b3040],
2	publications	NNS	O	publication	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1485t2988r1843b3055],
3	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1869t2990r1971b3042],
4	notes	NNS	O	note	conj_and	2	SENT_35	[p1l1993t3000r2145b3043],
5	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l79t3076r148b3113],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_35	[p1l179t3062r267b3114],
7	genera	NN	O	genus	prep_on	2	SENT_35	[p1l297t3078r492b3129],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l521t3063r623b3115],
9	species	NNS	O	species	prep_on	2	SENT_35	[p1l655t3063r862b3131],
10	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l892t3064r1082b3132],
11	the	DT	DURATION	the	det	14	SENT_35	[p1l1111t3066r1200b3118],
12	past	JJ	DURATION	past	amod	14	SENT_35	[p1l1227t3075r1345b3133],
13	twenty	CD	DURATION	twenty	num	14	SENT_35	[p1l1373t3075r1570b3136],
14	years	NNS	NUMBER	year	prep_during	2	SENT_35	[p1l1599t3083r1769b3134],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1599t3083r1769b3134],
16	1897-1917	CD	DATE	1897-1917	appos	14	SENT_35	[p1l1806t3069r2142b3122],
17	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_35	[p1l1806t3069r2142b3122],

1	Transactions	NNS	O	transaction	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l77t3136r447b3190],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l475t3137r539b3190],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_36	[p1l561t3138r649b3190],
4	San	NNP	ORGANIZATION	San	nn	6	SENT_36	[p1l678t3138r784b3191],
5	Diego	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Diego	nn	6	SENT_36	[p1l813t3139r990b3206],
6	Society	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Society	prep_of	1	SENT_36	[p1l1019t3140r1237b3207],
7	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1265t3140r1330b3193],
8	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	9	SENT_36	[p1l1351t3141r1569b3194],
9	History	NN	ORGANIZATION	history	prep_of	6	SENT_36	[p1l1596t3142r1831b3209],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1596t3142r1831b3209],
11	3:3	CD	NUMBER	3:3	num	12	SENT_36	[p1l1863t3143r2114b3196],
12	?	NN	O	?	appos	1	SENT_36	[p1l1863t3143r2114b3196],
13	141	CD	NUMBER	141	dep	12	SENT_36	[p1l1863t3143r2114b3196],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_36	[p1l1863t3143r2114b3196],

1	WEBER	NNP	LOCATION	WEBER	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l10t3213r240b3273],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l10t3213r240b3273],
3	V.	NNP	O	V.	nn	4	SENT_37	[p1l267t3214r324b3265],
4	N.	NNP	O	N.	appos	1	SENT_37	[p1l352t3214r418b3265],
5	1948	CD	DATE	1948	dep	4	SENT_37	[p1l453t3214r606b3267],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_37	[p1l453t3214r606b3267],

1	Trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l634t3214r913b3268],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l940t3215r1004b3268],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_38	[p1l1023t3216r1110b3268],
4	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	5	SENT_38	[p1l1136t3216r1364b3269],
5	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_of	1	SENT_38	[p1l1388t3217r1627b3285],
6	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1653t3218r1717b3271],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_38	[p1l1735t3219r1822b3271],
8	USSR	NNP	ORGANIZATION	USSR	prep_of	1	SENT_38	[p1l1847t3220r2042b3272],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_38	[p1l1847t3220r2042b3272],

1	Pt	NN	O	pt	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l2068t3221r2142b3273],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_39	[p1l2068t3221r2142b3273],

1	1	LS	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l85t3288r127b3340],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_40	[p1l85t3288r127b3340],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_41	[p1l159t3288r272b3341],
2	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	3	SENT_41	[p1l300t3290r493b3341],
3	Silurian	NNP	MISC	Silurian	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l520t3289r748b3342],
4	trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	dep	3	SENT_41	[p1l778t3290r1054b3343],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_41	[p1l778t3290r1054b3343],

1	Monogra?i	NNP	PERSON	Monogra?i	nn	4	SENT_42	[p1l1085t3292r1412b3359],
2	po	NNP	O	po	nn	4	SENT_42	[p1l1441t3307r1513b3359],
3	Paleontologii	NNP	O	Paleontologii	nn	4	SENT_42	[p1l1542t3293r1930b3361],
4	SSSR	NNP	O	SSSR	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l1960t3295r2143b3355],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l1960t3295r2143b3355],
6	69:1	CD	NUMBER	69:1	num	7	SENT_42	[p1l77t3367r369b3418],
7	?	NN	O	?	appos	4	SENT_42	[p1l77t3367r369b3418],
8	114	CD	NUMBER	114	dep	7	SENT_42	[p1l77t3367r369b3418],
9	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_42	[p1l77t3367r369b3418],

1	[	NN	O	[	_	0	SENT_43	[p1l404t3368r482b3429],
2	In	IN	O	in	dep	1	SENT_43	[p1l404t3368r482b3429],
3	Russian	JJ	MISC	russian	amod	4	SENT_43	[p1l512t3368r763b3430],
4	]	NN	O	]	pobj	2	SENT_43	[p1l512t3368r763b3430],

1	oo	NN	O	oo	_	0	SENT_46	[p1l607t3701r666b3738],

1	WHITTINGTON	NNP	LOCATION	WHITTINGTON	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l16t112r452b173],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l16t112r452b173],
3	B.	NNP	O	B.	appos	1	SENT_47	[p2l485t114r547b166],
4	1965	CD	DATE	1965	num	3	SENT_47	[p2l589t114r742b167],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_47	[p2l589t114r742b167],

1	Trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l776t116r1056b169],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l1089t117r1152b169],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_48	[p2l1177t118r1266b170],
4	Ordovician	NNP	MISC	Ordovician	nn	7	SENT_48	[p2l1297t118r1625b172],
5	Table	NNP	MISC	Table	nn	7	SENT_48	[p2l1657t120r1818b173],
6	Head	NNP	MISC	Head	nn	7	SENT_48	[p2l1848t122r2002b174],
7	Formation	NN	MISC	formation	prep_of	1	SENT_48	[p2l2033t123r2152b175, p2l85t187r302b249],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l2033t123r2152b175, p2l85t187r302b249],
9	western	JJ	O	western	amod	10	SENT_48	[p2l333t198r560b242],
10	Newfoundland	NNP	LOCATION	Newfoundland	appos	7	SENT_48	[p2l587t190r1038b244],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_48	[p2l587t190r1038b244],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l166t382r176b400],
2	AND	CC	O	and	cc	3	SENT_50	[p2l211t354r333b392],
3	W.	NNP	PERSON	W.	nn	5	SENT_50	[p2l364t343r439b393],
4	R.	NNP	PERSON	R.	nn	5	SENT_50	[p2l475t343r535b394],
5	EVITT	NNP	PERSON	EVITT	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l571t344r760b403],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l571t344r760b403],
7	II	NNP	O	II	appos	5	SENT_50	[p2l796t345r857b395],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_50	[p2l796t345r857b395],

1	1954	CD	DATE	1954	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l900t345r1054b396],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_51	[p2l900t345r1054b396],

1	Geological	JJ	ORGANIZATION	geological	amod	2	SENT_53	[p2l264t419r586b486],
2	Society	NN	ORGANIZATION	society	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l614t420r831b488],
3	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l860t421r924b474],
4	America	NNP	ORGANIZATION	America	nn	5	SENT_53	[p2l947t423r1199b475],
5	Memoir	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Memoir	prep_of	2	SENT_53	[p2l1225t424r1471b485],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1225t424r1471b485],
7	59	CD	NUMBER	59	appos	5	SENT_53	[p2l1501t425r1588b485],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_53	[p2l1501t425r1588b485],
9	137	CD	NUMBER	137	num	10	SENT_53	[p2l1625t425r1724b478],
10	p.	NN	O	p.	dep	2	SENT_53	[p2l1753t441r1803b493],

1	WU	NNP	PERSON	WU	nn	2	SENT_54	[p2l13t493r123b545],
2	HONGJI	NNP	PERSON	HONGJI	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l152t494r384b546],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_54	[p2l152t494r384b546],

1	1977	CD	DATE	1977	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l425t495r577b547],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_55	[p2l425t495r577b547],

1	Comments	NNS	O	comment	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l610t495r928b549],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l960t512r1028b549],
3	new	JJ	O	new	amod	4	SENT_56	[p2l1059t513r1180b550],
4	genera	NN	O	genus	prep_on	1	SENT_56	[p2l1211t514r1406b565],
5	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l1436t499r1539b551],
6	species	NNS	O	species	prep_on	1	SENT_56	[p2l1570t500r1778b567],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l1808t501r1872b553],
8	SilurianDevonian	NNP	O	SilurianDevonian	nn	9	SENT_56	[p2l1898t502r2150b554, p2l82t568r364b620],
9	trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	prep_of	1	SENT_56	[p2l398t569r657b622],
10	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l692t570r745b622],
11	southwest	NN	O	southwest	nn	12	SENT_56	[p2l782t571r1074b624],
12	China	NNP	LOCATION	China	prep_in	1	SENT_56	[p2l1104t571r1281b625],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l1313t573r1417b625],
14	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	15	SENT_56	[p2l1449t573r1584b626],
15	signi?cance	NN	O	signi?cance	conj_and	12	SENT_56	[p2l1616t574r1979b641],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_56	[p2l1616t574r1979b641],

1	[	NN	O	[	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l1197t650r1274b712],
2	In	IN	O	in	amod	3	SENT_58	[p2l1197t650r1274b712],
3	Chinese	JJ	MISC	chinese	dep	1	SENT_58	[p2l1311t649r1547b703],
4	with	IN	O	with	prep	3	SENT_58	[p2l1584t651r1713b703],
5	English	JJ	MISC	english	amod	6	SENT_58	[p2l1748t652r1971b719],
6	summar	NN	O	summar	dep	4	SENT_58	[p2l2007t668r2149b705, p2l81t750r194b788],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_58	[p2l236t736r270b798],
8	]	SYM	O	]	dep	3	SENT_58	[p2l236t736r270b798],

1	YI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	YI	nn	2	SENT_59	[p2l12t805r82b856],
2	YO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	YO	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],
3	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	4	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],
4	l	NN	O	l	dep	2	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],
6	\	CD	NUMBER	\	num	7	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],
7	IGEN	NNP	ORGANIZATION	IGEN	appos	4	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],
8	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_59	[p2l116t751r383b858],

1	1978	CD	DATE	1978	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l429t806r581b859],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_60	[p2l429t806r581b859],

1	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	2	SENT_61	[p2l622t807r851b859],
2	Trilobita	NN	MISC	trilobita	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l885t808r1153b869],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l885t808r1153b869],
4	p.	NN	O	p.	appos	2	SENT_61	[p2l1188t824r1238b876],
5	265-269	CD	NUMBER	265-269	num	4	SENT_61	[p2l1278t809r1548b863],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_61	[p2l1278t809r1548b863],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1584t812r1644b863],
2	Hubei	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Hubei	nn	4	SENT_62	[p2l1678t812r1854b864],
3	Province	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Province	nn	4	SENT_62	[p2l1890t813r2149b866],
4	Bureau	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Bureau	dobj	10	SENT_62	[p2l79t881r290b934],
5	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l334t881r398b934],
6	Geology	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geology	nn	9	SENT_62	[p2l435t882r700b950],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l435t882r700b950],
8	Sanxia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Sanxia	appos	9	SENT_62	[p2l746t884r945b937],
9	Stratigraphical	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Stratigraphical	prep_of	4	SENT_62	[p2l988t885r1417b953],
10	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Research	dep	1	SENT_62	[p2l1461t888r1728b940],
11	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Group	nn	12	SENT_62	[p2l1771t888r1955b956],
12	(	NNP	O	(	nsubj	13	SENT_62	[p2l1998t890r2147b953],
13	ed	VBD	O	ed	dep	10	SENT_62	[p2l1998t890r2147b953],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_62	[p2l1998t890r2147b953],
15	)	SYM	O	)	dep	1	SENT_62	[p2l1998t890r2147b953],

1	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1998t890r2147b953],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	4	SENT_63	[p2l81t957r289b1020],
3	Sinian	JJ	O	sinian	amod	2	SENT_63	[p2l81t957r289b1020],
4	to	TO	O	to	dep	6	SENT_63	[p2l330t967r383b1011],
5	Permian	NNP	O	Permian	nn	6	SENT_63	[p2l424t960r666b1012],
6	Stratigraphy	NNP	O	Stratigraphy	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l708t960r1069b1029],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1109t962r1212b1014],
8	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	conj_and	6	SENT_63	[p2l1252t963r1638b1031],
9	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l1679t964r1731b1017],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_63	[p2l1772t966r1859b1018],
11	Xiadong	NNP	LOCATION	Xiadong	nn	13	SENT_63	[p2l1897t966r2148b1034],
12	Area	NNP	LOCATION	Area	nn	13	SENT_63	[p2l79t1036r258b1098],
13	)	NNP	O	)	prep_in	8	SENT_63	[p2l79t1036r258b1098],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_63	[p2l79t1036r258b1098],

1	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	2	SENT_64	[p2l290t1036r611b1103],
2	Press	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Press	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l638t1038r808b1098],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l638t1038r808b1098],
4	Beijing	NNP	LOCATION	Beijing	appos	2	SENT_64	[p2l836t1038r1066b1106],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_64	[p2l836t1038r1066b1106],

1	[	NN	O	[	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l1102t1040r1180b1102],
2	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l1102t1040r1180b1102],
3	Chinese	JJ	MISC	chinese	prep_in	1	SENT_65	[p2l1207t1039r1483b1104],
4	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_65	[p2l1207t1039r1483b1104],
5	]	SYM	O	]	dep	1	SENT_65	[p2l1207t1039r1483b1104],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_66	[p2l162t1152r171b1161],

1	1989	CD	DATE	1989	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l216t1110r368b1162],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_67	[p2l216t1110r368b1162],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_68	[p2l404t1111r518b1163],
2	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	3	SENT_68	[p2l553t1111r782b1164],
3	stratigraphy	NN	O	stratigraphy	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l817t1113r1166b1181],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l1203t1114r1306b1166],
5	paleontology	NN	O	paleontology	conj_and	3	SENT_68	[p2l1338t1115r1721b1183],
6	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l1756t1117r1808b1169],
7	Elangshan	NNP	LOCATION	Elangshan	nn	8	SENT_68	[p2l1842t1117r2146b1185],
8	district	NN	O	district	prep_in	3	SENT_68	[p2l77t1185r297b1246],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l77t1185r297b1246],
10	Sichuan	NNP	LOCATION	Sichuan	appos	8	SENT_68	[p2l322t1185r572b1240],
11	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_68	[p2l322t1185r572b1240],

1	Description	NN	O	description	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l597t1187r937b1255],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l961t1189r1025b1241],
3	selected	VBN	O	select	amod	4	SENT_69	[p2l1042t1190r1276b1243],
4	fossils	NNS	O	fossil	prep_of	1	SENT_69	[p2l1297t1190r1497b1244],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_69	[p2l1297t1190r1497b1244],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1524t1192r1604b1255],
2	4	CD	NUMBER	4	num	4	SENT_70	[p2l1524t1192r1604b1255],
3	)	NN	O	)	nn	4	SENT_70	[p2l1524t1192r1604b1255],
4	Trilobita	NN	O	trilobita	dep	1	SENT_70	[p2l1624t1191r1890b1245],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_70	[p2l1624t1191r1890b1245],

1	Bulletin	NNP	O	Bulletin	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1912t1193r2146b1246],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l78t1260r142b1313],
3	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_71	[p2l163t1261r251b1313],
4	Chengdu	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chengdu	nn	5	SENT_71	[p2l276t1261r541b1329],
5	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Institute	prep_of	1	SENT_71	[p2l567t1263r807b1316],
6	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l833t1263r898b1316],
7	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	10	SENT_71	[p2l918t1264r1239b1332],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1266t1266r1369b1318],
9	Mineralogical	NNP	O	Mineralogical	nn	10	SENT_71	[p2l1394t1266r1805b1335],
10	Resources	NNPS	O	Resources	prep_of	1	SENT_71	[p2l1830t1269r2145b1330],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l1830t1269r2145b1330],
12	11:138	CD	NUMBER	11:138	num	13	SENT_71	[p2l85t1338r443b1392],
13	-147	CD	NUMBER	-147	appos	10	SENT_71	[p2l85t1338r443b1392],
14	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_71	[p2l85t1338r443b1392],

1	[	NN	O	[	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l478t1341r557b1403],
2	In	IN	O	in	amod	3	SENT_72	[p2l478t1341r557b1403],
3	Chinese	JJ	MISC	chinese	dep	1	SENT_72	[p2l585t1340r820b1394],
4	with	IN	O	with	prep	3	SENT_72	[p2l848t1342r976b1394],
5	English	JJ	MISC	english	amod	6	SENT_72	[p2l1004t1343r1227b1410],
6	abstract	JJ	O	abstract	dep	4	SENT_72	[p2l1256t1344r1521b1408],
7	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_72	[p2l1256t1344r1521b1408],
8	]	SYM	O	]	dep	3	SENT_72	[p2l1256t1344r1521b1408],

1	YOUNG	NNP	O	YOUNG	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l9t1412r242b1473],
2	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l9t1412r242b1473],
3	J.	NNP	O	J.	appos	1	SENT_73	[p2l274t1414r316b1466],
4	1868	CD	DATE	1868	num	3	SENT_73	[p2l357t1414r509b1466],
5	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_73	[p2l357t1414r509b1466],

1	On	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l545t1414r630b1466],
2	new	JJ	O	new	amod	3	SENT_74	[p2l663t1430r782b1467],
3	forms	NNS	O	form	pobj	1	SENT_74	[p2l813t1415r982b1468],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l1014t1416r1078b1468],
5	Crustacea	NNP	LOCATION	Crustacea	prep_of	3	SENT_74	[p2l1103t1416r1407b1478],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l1103t1416r1407b1478],
7	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l1442t1418r1581b1471],
8	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_74	[p2l1612t1419r1699b1472],
9	Silurian	JJ	MISC	silurian	amod	10	SENT_74	[p2l1730t1420r1959b1473],
10	rocks	NNS	O	rock	prep_from	3	SENT_74	[p2l1988t1421r2144b1474],
11	at	IN	O	at	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l78t1499r128b1543],
12	Girvan	NNP	PERSON	Girvan	prep_at	10	SENT_74	[p2l158t1491r379b1544],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_74	[p2l158t1491r379b1544],

1	Proceedings	NNP	O	Proceedings	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l414t1493r770b1561],
2	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l804t1494r907b1546],
3	Transactions	NNS	O	transaction	conj_and	1	SENT_75	[p2l936t1495r1306b1548],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l1339t1496r1402b1549],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_75	[p2l1427t1497r1515b1549],
6	Natural	JJ	O	natural	amod	7	SENT_75	[p2l1546t1498r1764b1550],
7	History	NN	O	history	prep_of	3	SENT_75	[p2l1795t1498r2016b1566],
8	Society	NN	O	society	dep	1	SENT_75	[p2l2047t1499r2144b1552, p2l75t1568r216b1635],
9	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l246t1569r310b1622],
10	Glasgow	NNP	LOCATION	Glasgow	prep_of	8	SENT_75	[p2l333t1570r605b1637],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l333t1570r605b1637],
12	12169-173	CD	NUMBER	12169-173	appos	10	SENT_75	[p2l642t1571r966b1624],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_75	[p2l642t1571r966b1624],

1	ACCEPTED	VBN	O	accept	_	0	SENT_76	[p2l8t1704r315b1754],
2	2	CD	DATE	2	dobj	1	SENT_76	[p2l342t1703r375b1754],
3	DECEMBER	NNP	DATE	DECEMBER	tmod	1	SENT_76	[p2l404t1705r728b1756],
4	1997	CD	DATE	1997	num	3	SENT_76	[p2l761t1706r897b1757],

1	TRILOBITES	NNP	O	TRILOBITES	nn	4	SENT_77	[p2l66t1832r407b1877],
2	FROM	NNP	O	FROM	nn	4	SENT_77	[p2l431t1832r601b1877],
3	LOWER	NNP	O	LOWER	nn	4	SENT_77	[p2l622t1833r836b1877],
4	MISSISSIPPIAN	NNP	O	MISSISSIPPIAN	_	0	SENT_77	[p2l856t1834r1277b1879],
5	STARVED	NNP	O	STARVED	nn	7	SENT_77	[p2l1299t1835r1569b1880],
6	BASIN	NNP	O	BASIN	nn	7	SENT_77	[p2l1592t1836r1771b1881],
7	FACIES	NNPS	O	FACIES	dep	4	SENT_77	[p2l1793t1837r1993b1882],
8	OF	IN	O	of	prep	7	SENT_77	[p2l2018t1838r2093b1882],

1	THE	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_78	[p2l612t1902r728b1945],
2	SOUTHERN	NNP	O	SOUTHERN	nn	3	SENT_78	[p2l752t1902r1070b1947],
3	UNITED	NNP	O	UNITED	_	0	SENT_78	[p2l1091t1904r1313b1947],
4	STATES	NNS	O	state	dep	3	SENT_78	[p2l1337t1904r1545b1949],

1	DAVID	NNP	PERSON	DAVID	nn	3	SENT_79	[p2l883t1998r1006b2026],
2	K.	NNP	PERSON	K.	nn	3	SENT_79	[p2l1022t1998r1056b2034],
3	BREZINSKI	NNP	PERSON	BREZINSKI	_	0	SENT_79	[p2l1072t1998r1278b2027],

1	Maryland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Maryland	nn	3	SENT_80	[p2l586t2045r724b2078],
2	Geological	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Geological	nn	3	SENT_80	[p2l736t2045r890b2079],
3	Survey	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Survey	_	0	SENT_80	[p2l903t2046r1009b2079],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p2l903t2046r1009b2079],
5	2300	CD	DATE	2300	appos	3	SENT_80	[p2l1023t2046r1093b2073],
6	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	St.	nn	8	SENT_80	[p2l1106t2047r1141b2073],
7	Paul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Paul	nn	8	SENT_80	[p2l1156t2047r1218b2073],
8	Street	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Street	dep	3	SENT_80	[p2l1232t2047r1320b2077],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_80	[p2l1232t2047r1320b2077],
10	Baltimore	NNP	LOCATION	Baltimore	appos	8	SENT_80	[p2l1334t2048r1474b2074],
11	21218	CD	NUMBER	21218	num	10	SENT_80	[p2l1486t2048r1572b2074],

1	ABSTRACT	NN	O	abstract	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l108t2171r321b2196],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_81	[p2l108t2171r321b2196],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_82	[p2l108t2171r321b2196],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_82	[p2l108t2171r321b2196],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	4	SENT_83	[p2l108t2171r321b2196],
2	distinctive	JJ	O	distinctive	amod	4	SENT_83	[p2l330t2171r477b2197],
3	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	4	SENT_83	[p2l486t2171r597b2197],
4	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	nsubj	5	SENT_83	[p2l607t2171r685b2198],
5	occurs	VBZ	O	occur	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l694t2180r784b2198],
6	within	IN	O	within	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l795t2172r883b2198],
7	condensed	JJ	O	condensed	amod	9	SENT_83	[p2l893t2173r1041b2199],
8	statigraphic	JJ	O	statigraphic	amod	9	SENT_83	[p2l1052t2173r1214b2207],
9	sections	NNS	O	section	prep_within	5	SENT_83	[p2l1224t2174r1336b2200],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1346t2174r1377b2200],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_83	[p2l1384t2174r1425b2200],
12	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	18	SENT_83	[p2l1434t2175r1527b2200],
13	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	nn	18	SENT_83	[p2l1535t2174r1727b2208],
14	(	NNP	O	(	nn	18	SENT_83	[p2l1737t2175r1924b2207],
15	Toumaisian	NNP	MISC	Toumaisian	nn	18	SENT_83	[p2l1737t2175r1924b2207],
16	)	NNP	O	)	nn	18	SENT_83	[p2l1737t2175r1924b2207],
17	Chappel	NNP	O	Chappel	nn	18	SENT_83	[p2l1932t2175r2049b2209],
18	Limestone	NNP	O	Limestone	prep_of	9	SENT_83	[p2l108t2208r257b2235],
19	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l270t2209r301b2235],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	22	SENT_83	[p2l312t2209r353b2235],
21	Llano	NNP	LOCATION	Llano	nn	22	SENT_83	[p2l366t2209r447b2235],
22	region	NN	O	region	prep_of	18	SENT_83	[p2l461t2209r549b2242],
23	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l563t2209r595b2235],
24	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_of	22	SENT_83	[p2l605t2210r693b2240],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l605t2210r693b2240],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_83	[p2l708t2210r749b2236],
27	Welden	NNP	O	Welden	nn	28	SENT_83	[p2l762t2210r868b2236],
28	Limestone	NNP	O	Limestone	prep_of	18	SENT_83	[p2l881t2210r1029b2237],
29	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1042t2211r1073b2237],
30	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	prep_of	28	SENT_83	[p2l1084t2211r1237b2241],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1084t2211r1237b2241],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1252t2211r1302b2237],
33	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_83	[p2l1315t2212r1357b2238],
34	Chouteau	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chouteau	nn	35	SENT_83	[p2l1370t2212r1504b2238],
35	Limestone	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Limestone	conj_and	22	SENT_83	[p2l1517t2212r1665b2238],
36	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1677t2212r1709b2238],
37	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Union	nn	38	SENT_83	[p2l1719t2213r1805b2239],
38	County	NNP	ORGANIZATION	County	prep_of	35	SENT_83	[p2l1819t2213r1928b2246],
39	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1819t2213r1928b2246],
40	Illinois	NNP	LOCATION	Illinois	appos	38	SENT_83	[p2l1941t2213r2047b2239],
41	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_83	[p2l1941t2213r2047b2239],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_84	[p2l107t2246r162b2272],
2	seven	CD	NUMBER	seven	num	3	SENT_84	[p2l178t2254r256b2272],
3	species	NNS	O	species	nsubjpass	8	SENT_84	[p2l272t2246r372b2279],
4	comprising	VBG	O	comprise	partmod	3	SENT_84	[p2l387t2246r545b2280],
5	this	DT	O	this	det	6	SENT_84	[p2l561t2247r610b2273],
6	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	dobj	4	SENT_84	[p2l626t2247r703b2273],
7	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_84	[p2l718t2255r760b2273],
8	interpreted	VBN	O	interpret	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l775t2247r927b2280],
9	to	TO	O	to	aux	11	SENT_84	[p2l942t2252r968b2273],
10	have	VB	O	have	aux	11	SENT_84	[p2l983t2248r1048b2274],
11	inhabited	VBN	O	inhabit	xcomp	8	SENT_84	[p2l1064t2248r1194b2274],
12	sediment-starved	JJ	O	sediment-starved	amod	14	SENT_84	[p2l1210t2248r1451b2275],
13	basinal	JJ	O	basinal	amod	14	SENT_84	[p2l1465t2249r1563b2275],
14	environments	NNS	O	environment	dobj	11	SENT_84	[p2l1578t2250r1776b2276],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_84	[p2l1578t2250r1776b2276],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_85	[p2l1792t2250r1846b2276],
2	starved-basin	JJ	O	starved-basin	amod	3	SENT_85	[p2l1861t2250r2048b2276],
3	facies	NNS	O	facy	nsubj	4	SENT_85	[p2l108t2283r189b2309],
4	existed	VBD	O	exist	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l202t2283r301b2309],
5	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l314t2283r340b2309],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_85	[p2l353t2284r395b2310],
7	south	JJ	O	south	amod	8	SENT_85	[p2l408t2284r597b2310],
8	?	NNP	O	?	prep_in	4	SENT_85	[p2l408t2284r597b2310],
9	central	JJ	O	central	amod	11	SENT_85	[p2l408t2284r597b2310],
10	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	11	SENT_85	[p2l609t2284r704b2310],
11	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dobj	4	SENT_85	[p2l717t2284r799b2311],
12	throughout	IN	O	throughout	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l813t2285r967b2318],
13	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_85	[p2l979t2285r1021b2311],
14	Toumaisian	JJ	LOCATION	toumaisian	amod	16	SENT_85	[p2l1033t2285r1198b2312],
15	(	NN	O	(	nn	16	SENT_85	[p2l1211t2286r1432b2317],
16	Kinderhookian	NN	O	kinderhookian	prep_throughout	4	SENT_85	[p2l1211t2286r1432b2317],
17	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l1445t2291r1471b2312],
18	Osagean	JJ	LOCATION	osagean	amod	19	SENT_85	[p2l1483t2287r1622b2320],
19	)	NN	O	)	prep_to	4	SENT_85	[p2l1483t2287r1622b2320],
20	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_85	[p2l1483t2287r1622b2320],

1	Two	CD	NUMBER	two	num	2	SENT_86	[p2l1635t2287r1697b2313],
2	species	NNS	O	species	nsubj	15	SENT_86	[p2l1710t2287r1809b2320],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l1822t2287r1890b2313],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_86	[p2l1901t2287r1950b2314],
5	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	prep_from	2	SENT_86	[p2l1963t2287r2047b2318],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l1963t2287r2047b2318],
7	Australosutura	NNP	O	Australosutura	nn	8	SENT_86	[p2l105t2322r318b2348],
8	llanoensis	NN	O	llanoensis	prep_from	2	SENT_86	[p2l332t2322r480b2352],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l332t2322r480b2352],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l497t2322r546b2348],
11	Carbanocoryphe	NNP	O	Carbanocoryphe	nn	12	SENT_86	[p2l560t2322r797b2356],
12	planucauda	NN	O	planucauda	conj_and	5	SENT_86	[p2l807t2323r981b2356],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l807t2323r981b2356],
14	are	VBP	O	be	cop	15	SENT_86	[p2l998t2331r1040b2350],
15	new	JJ	O	new	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l1053t2332r1117b2350],
16	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_86	[p2l1053t2332r1117b2350],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_87	[p2l1131t2324r1185b2350],
2	remaining	VBG	O	remain	amod	4	SENT_87	[p2l1198t2324r1341b2358],
3	?ve	JJ	O	?ve	amod	4	SENT_87	[p2l1354t2324r1406b2351],
4	species	NNS	O	species	nsubj	40	SENT_87	[p2l1419t2324r1527b2358],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l1419t2324r1527b2358],
6	Grij?thidella	NNP	PERSON	Grij?thidella	nsubj	7	SENT_87	[p2l1541t2325r1723b2358],
7	doris	VBZ	O	dori	parataxis	40	SENT_87	[p2l1736t2325r1808b2352],
8	(	NNP	O	(	nn	10	SENT_87	[p2l1821t2326r1911b2357],
9	Hall	NNP	O	Hall	nn	10	SENT_87	[p2l1821t2326r1911b2357],
10	)	NNP	O	)	dobj	7	SENT_87	[p2l1821t2326r1911b2357],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l1821t2326r1911b2357],
12	Grijj	NNP	O	Grijj	nn	14	SENT_87	[p2l1924t2326r2047b2359, p2l107t2359r177b2385],
13	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	14	SENT_87	[p2l1924t2326r2047b2359, p2l107t2359r177b2385],
14	ithidella	NN	O	ithidellum	nn	15	SENT_87	[p2l1924t2326r2047b2359, p2l107t2359r177b2385],
15	altemata	NN	O	altema	appos	10	SENT_87	[p2l194t2359r322b2386],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	18	SENT_87	[p2l340t2359r444b2393],
17	Girty	NNP	O	Girty	nn	18	SENT_87	[p2l340t2359r444b2393],
18	)	NN	O	)	dep	15	SENT_87	[p2l340t2359r444b2393],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l340t2359r444b2393],
20	Carbonocoryphe	NN	O	carbonocoryphe	nn	21	SENT_87	[p2l464t2360r700b2393],
21	depressa	NN	O	depressa	conj_and	10	SENT_87	[p2l717t2360r841b2394],
22	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	23	SENT_87	[p2l859t2361r963b2394],
23	Girty	NNP	O	Girty	dep	21	SENT_87	[p2l859t2361r963b2394],
24	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	23	SENT_87	[p2l859t2361r963b2394],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l859t2361r963b2394],
26	Thigif?des	FW	O	thigif?des	nn	30	SENT_87	[p2l983t2361r1129b2394],
27	roundyi	FW	O	roundyi	nn	30	SENT_87	[p2l1147t2362r1255b2395],
28	(	FW	O	(	nn	30	SENT_87	[p2l1272t2362r1376b2396],
29	Girty	FW	O	girty	nn	30	SENT_87	[p2l1272t2362r1376b2396],
30	)	FW	O	)	appos	23	SENT_87	[p2l1272t2362r1376b2396],
31	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l1272t2362r1376b2396],
32	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l1394t2362r1444b2389],
33	Pudoproetus	NN	O	pudoproetus	nn	34	SENT_87	[p2l1460t2362r1639b2396],
34	chappelensis	NN	O	chappelensis	dobj	7	SENT_87	[p2l1656t2363r1837b2396],
35	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	37	SENT_87	[p2l1854t2364r1989b2395],
36	Hessler	NNP	PERSON	Hessler	nn	37	SENT_87	[p2l1854t2364r1989b2395],
37	)	NN	O	)	dep	34	SENT_87	[p2l1854t2364r1989b2395],
38	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l1854t2364r1989b2395],
39	are	VBP	O	be	cop	40	SENT_87	[p2l2006t2372r2048b2390],
40	restricted	JJ	O	restricted	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l107t2400r238b2426],
41	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l250t2404r277b2426],
42	starved-basin	JJ	O	starved-basin	amod	43	SENT_87	[p2l291t2400r479b2426],
43	facies	NNS	O	facy	prep_to	40	SENT_87	[p2l492t2400r580b2426],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_87	[p2l492t2400r580b2426],

1	INTRODUCTION	NN	O	introduction	_	0	SENT_88	[p2l840t2620r1323b2664],

1	OWER	NNP	O	OWER	nn	3	SENT_89	[p2l148t2730r337b2773],
2	MISSISSIPPIAN	NNP	O	MISSISSIPPIAN	nn	3	SENT_89	[p2l380t2731r830b2774],
3	trilobites	NNS	O	trilobite	nsubjpass	9	SENT_89	[p2l874t2717r1162b2776],
4	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l1206t2718r1278b2776],
5	North	NNP	LOCATION	North	nn	6	SENT_89	[p2l1314t2719r1504b2776],
6	America	NNP	LOCATION	America	prep_of	3	SENT_89	[p2l1546t2720r1830b2777],
7	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	9	SENT_89	[p2l1870t2738r1967b2778],
8	well	RB	O	well	advmod	9	SENT_89	[p2l2009t2721r2147b2778],
9	known	VBN	O	know	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l190t2801r414b2859],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l445t2801r605b2860],
11	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nn	12	SENT_89	[p2l637t2802r798b2860],
12	facies	NNS	O	facy	prep_from	9	SENT_89	[p2l824t2802r1032b2861],
13	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_89	[p2l824t2802r1032b2861],

1	Hessler	NNP	PERSON	Hessler	tmod	26	SENT_90	[p2l1066t2804r1313b2862],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	1	SENT_90	[p2l1344t2803r1549b2874],
3	1963	CD	DATE	1963	dep	1	SENT_90	[p2l1344t2803r1549b2874],
4	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l1344t2803r1549b2874],
5	1965	CD	DATE	1965	num	6	SENT_90	[p2l1591t2804r1791b2875],
6	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	26	SENT_90	[p2l1591t2804r1791b2875],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l1591t2804r1791b2875],
8	Chamberlain	NNP	PERSON	Chamberlain	dep	17	SENT_90	[p2l1825t2805r2147b2864, p2l9t2886r130b2944],
9	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	8	SENT_90	[p2l163t2885r370b2956],
10	1969	CD	DATE	1969	dep	8	SENT_90	[p2l163t2885r370b2956],
11	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l163t2885r370b2956],
12	1977	CD	DATE	1977	num	13	SENT_90	[p2l410t2886r591b2956],
13	)	NN	O	)	conj_and	10	SENT_90	[p2l410t2886r591b2956],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l624t2886r741b2945],
15	Brezinski	NNP	PERSON	Brezinski	conj_and	10	SENT_90	[p2l771t2887r1085b2946],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	dep	17	SENT_90	[p2l1117t2887r1323b2958],
17	1986	CD	DATE	1986	dep	6	SENT_90	[p2l1117t2887r1323b2958],
18	,	,	DATE	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l1117t2887r1323b2958],
19	1988a	NN	DATE	1988a	appos	17	SENT_90	[p2l1364t2888r1572b2957],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l1364t2888r1572b2957],
21	b	NN	O	b	nn	22	SENT_90	[p2l1603t2889r1669b2959],
22	)	NN	O	)	appos	17	SENT_90	[p2l1603t2889r1669b2959],
23	are	VBP	O	be	cop	26	SENT_90	[p2l1703t2907r1800b2948],
24	but	CC	O	but	advmod	26	SENT_90	[p2l1828t2890r1934b2948],
25	a	DT	O	a	det	26	SENT_90	[p2l1963t2907r1999b2948],
26	few	JJ	O	few	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l2027t2890r2147b2949],
27	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l9t2970r81b3028],
28	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_90	[p2l106t2970r204b3029],
29	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	32	SENT_90	[p2l235t2972r450b3029],
30	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	nn	32	SENT_90	[p2l479t2971r931b3046],
31	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	32	SENT_90	[p2l962t2972r1219b3031],
32	studies	NNS	O	study	prep_of	26	SENT_90	[p2l1250t2973r1474b3031],
33	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	35	SENT_90	[p2l1505t2973r1627b3032],
34	have	VBP	O	have	aux	35	SENT_90	[p2l1653t2974r1806b3032],
35	described	VBN	O	describe	rcmod	32	SENT_90	[p2l1837t2975r2148b3034],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_90	[p2l9t3055r107b3114],
37	relatively	RB	O	relatively	advmod	38	SENT_90	[p2l135t3056r446b3131],
38	diverse	JJ	O	diverse	amod	40	SENT_90	[p2l474t3056r711b3115],
39	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	40	SENT_90	[p2l741t3057r999b3115],
40	faunas	NNS	O	fauna	dobj	35	SENT_90	[p2l1028t3057r1239b3116],
41	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l1269t3058r1429b3116],
42	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nn	43	SENT_90	[p2l1457t3058r1619b3117],
43	limestone	NN	O	limestone	prep_from	35	SENT_90	[p2l1640t3060r1974b3118],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_90	[p2l1640t3060r1974b3118],

1	Brezinski	NNP	PERSON	Brezinski	nsubj	6	SENT_91	[p2l2003t3061r2145b3118, p2l9t3142r203b3201],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	1	SENT_91	[p2l249t3143r463b3213],
3	1990	CD	DATE	1990	num	4	SENT_91	[p2l249t3143r463b3213],
4	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_91	[p2l249t3143r463b3213],
5	has	VBZ	O	have	aux	6	SENT_91	[p2l508t3142r615b3201],
6	shown	VBN	O	show	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l663t3143r875b3202],
7	that	IN	O	that	complm	18	SENT_91	[p2l919t3143r1042b3202],
8	a	DT	O	a	det	11	SENT_91	[p2l1084t3161r1120b3202],
9	low-diversity	JJ	O	low-diversity	amod	11	SENT_91	[p2l1162t3144r1600b3219],
10	Osagean	JJ	MISC	osagean	amod	11	SENT_91	[p2l1643t3145r1924b3221],
11	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	nsubj	18	SENT_91	[p2l1967t3145r2148b3205],
12	composed	VBN	O	compose	partmod	11	SENT_91	[p2l9t3227r341b3302],
13	primarily	RB	O	primarily	advmod	12	SENT_91	[p2l371t3228r677b3302],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l708t3227r780b3286],
15	the	DT	O	the	det	17	SENT_91	[p2l805t3228r903b3286],
16	genus	NN	O	genus	nn	17	SENT_91	[p2l934t3245r1122b3303],
17	Australosutura	NNP	MISC	Australosutura	prep_of	12	SENT_91	[p2l1148t3229r1645b3288],
18	occupied	VBD	O	occupy	ccomp	6	SENT_91	[p2l1675t3230r1970b3305],
19	platform-edge	JJ	O	platform-edge	amod	21	SENT_91	[p2l1997t3231r2145b3305, p2l8t3311r349b3386],
20	Waulsortian	JJ	MISC	waulsortian	amod	21	SENT_91	[p2l378t3311r774b3370],
21	reefs	NNS	O	reef	dobj	18	SENT_91	[p2l802t3312r959b3371],
22	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l990t3313r1052b3370],
23	northeast	JJ	O	northeast	amod	24	SENT_91	[p2l1081t3313r1383b3371],
24	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	prep_in	18	SENT_91	[p2l1410t3313r1766b3372],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_91	[p2l1410t3313r1766b3372],

1	Unlike	IN	O	unlike	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l1800t3315r2020b3373],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_92	[p2l2048t3314r2146b3373],
3	deep	JJ	O	deep	amod	5	SENT_92	[p2l7t3395r374b3472],
4	?	NN	O	?	nn	5	SENT_92	[p2l7t3395r374b3472],
5	water	NN	O	water	prep_unlike	38	SENT_92	[p2l7t3395r374b3472],
6	European	JJ	MISC	european	amod	8	SENT_92	[p2l407t3397r722b3472],
7	Kulm	NNP	MISC	Kulm	nn	8	SENT_92	[p2l758t3397r944b3455],
8	facies	NNS	O	facy	dep	5	SENT_92	[p2l977t3397r1166b3456],
9	where	WRB	O	where	advmod	16	SENT_92	[p2l1202t3397r1400b3457],
10	a	DT	O	a	det	12	SENT_92	[p2l1436t3416r1472b3457],
11	distinctive	JJ	O	distinctive	amod	12	SENT_92	[p2l1504t3398r1845b3458],
12	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	nsubj	16	SENT_92	[p2l1880t3399r2061b3458],
13	is	VBZ	O	be	cop	16	SENT_92	[p2l2094t3400r2144b3458],
14	well	RB	O	well	advmod	15	SENT_92	[p2l8t3481r146b3539],
15	known	VBN	O	know	amod	16	SENT_92	[p2l179t3481r402b3539],
16	(	NN	O	(	rcmod	8	SENT_92	[p2l438t3482r565b3551],
17	see	VB	O	see	dep	16	SENT_92	[p2l438t3482r565b3551],
18	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l598t3481r694b3539],
19	example	NN	O	example	nn	20	SENT_92	[p2l725t3482r1002b3557],
20	Hahn	NNP	PERSON	Hahn	prep_for	17	SENT_92	[p2l1035t3482r1212b3540],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l1245t3483r1361b3541],
22	Hahn	NNP	PERSON	Hahn	prep_for	17	SENT_92	[p2l1393t3483r1587b3551],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l1393t3483r1587b3551],
24	1988	CD	DATE	1988	num	25	SENT_92	[p2l1631t3483r1831b3554],
25	)	CD	NUMBER	)	nsubjpass	38	SENT_92	[p2l1631t3483r1831b3554],
26	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l1631t3483r1831b3554],
27	off-shelf	JJ	O	off-shelf	amod	28	SENT_92	[p2l1866t3484r2153b3543],
28	species	NNS	O	species	appos	25	SENT_92	[p2l9t3568r242b3642],
29	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l286t3567r446b3625],
30	North	JJ	MISC	north	amod	34	SENT_92	[p2l487t3568r677b3626],
31	American	JJ	MISC	american	amod	34	SENT_92	[p2l720t3570r1043b3626],
32	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	34	SENT_92	[p2l1084t3570r1299b3627],
33	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	nn	34	SENT_92	[p2l1339t3570r1791b3644],
34	strata	NN	O	stratum	prep_from	28	SENT_92	[p2l1833t3579r2009b3628],
35	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	38	SENT_92	[p2l2048t3587r2145b3629],
36	very	RB	O	very	advmod	38	SENT_92	[p2l7t3668r155b3724],
37	poorly	RB	O	poorly	advmod	38	SENT_92	[p2l185t3651r399b3725],
38	known	VBN	O	know	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l430t3651r670b3709],
39	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_92	[p2l430t3651r670b3709],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_93	[p2l706t3651r831b3710],
2	only	JJ	O	only	amod	6	SENT_93	[p2l863t3652r1007b3726],
3	documented	JJ	O	documented	amod	6	SENT_93	[p2l1038t3651r1440b3711],
4	North	JJ	MISC	north	amod	6	SENT_93	[p2l1470t3652r1660b3711],
5	American	JJ	MISC	american	amod	6	SENT_93	[p2l1690t3654r2013b3712],
6	occurrences	NNS	O	occurrence	nsubj	12	SENT_93	[p2l2043t3671r2143b3712, p2l7t3754r318b3795],
7	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l344t3737r417b3795],
8	Carboniferous	JJ	O	carboniferous	amod	11	SENT_93	[p2l436t3738r904b3796],
9	off-shelf	JJ	O	off-shelf	amod	11	SENT_93	[p2l930t3738r1217b3797],
10	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	11	SENT_93	[p2l1234t3739r1492b3798],
11	species	NNS	O	species	prep_of	6	SENT_93	[p2l1516t3740r1748b3814],
12	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l1773t3741r1823b3798],
13	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l1846t3741r1926b3815],
14	Hahn	NNP	PERSON	Hahn	prep_by	12	SENT_93	[p2l1949t3741r2142b3809],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_93	[p2l1949t3741r2142b3809],

1	Paul	NNP	PERSON	Paul	nn	2	SENT_94	[p3l7t10r191b78],
2	]	NNP	O	]	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l7t10r191b78],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l7t10r191b78],
4	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l222t10r339b69],
5	Chamberlain	NNP	PERSON	Chamberlain	conj_and	2	SENT_94	[p3l364t10r788b69],
6	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	5	SENT_94	[p3l816t11r1050b82],
7	1980	CD	DATE	1980	num	8	SENT_94	[p3l816t11r1050b82],
8	)	NN	O	)	dep	5	SENT_94	[p3l816t11r1050b82],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l816t11r1050b82],
10	who	WP	O	who	nsubj	11	SENT_94	[p3l1078t11r1217b69],
11	described	VBD	O	describe	rcmod	2	SENT_94	[p3l1244t12r1557b71],
12	a	DT	O	a	det	13	SENT_94	[p3l1583t30r1618b71],
13	species	NNS	O	species	dobj	11	SENT_94	[p3l1643t13r1875b87],
14	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l1902t13r1973b71],
15	Carbonocoryphe	NNP	O	Carbonocoryphe	prep_of	13	SENT_94	[p3l1995t15r2143b72, p3l7t95r435b169],
16	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l465t95r625b154],
17	?ysch	JJ	O	?ysch	amod	18	SENT_94	[p3l655t96r848b170],
18	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	prep_from	11	SENT_94	[p3l878t96r1144b172],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l1175t97r1237b155],
20	Idaho	NNP	LOCATION	Idaho	prep_in	18	SENT_94	[p3l1268t97r1469b155],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_94	[p3l1268t97r1469b155],

1	Paleogeographic	JJ	MISC	paleogeographic	amod	2	SENT_95	[p3l90t179r611b254],
2	reconstructions	NNS	O	reconstruction	dep	7	SENT_95	[p3l646t181r1123b239],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1160t180r1230b239],
4	Lane	NNP	PERSON	Lane	prep_of	2	SENT_95	[p3l1258t182r1415b239],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	4	SENT_95	[p3l1453t181r1676b251],
6	1978	CD	DATE	1978	dep	7	SENT_95	[p3l1453t181r1676b251],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	24	SENT_95	[p3l1453t181r1676b251],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1453t181r1676b251],
9	Lane	NNP	PERSON	Lane	conj_and	7	SENT_95	[p3l1713t183r1871b240],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1905t183r2018b241],
11	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	12	SENT_95	[p3l2051t184r2144b241],
12	Keyser	NNP	PERSON	Keyser	conj_and	7	SENT_95	[p3l8t266r231b339],
13	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	15	SENT_95	[p3l256t266r461b336],
14	1980	CD	DATE	1980	num	15	SENT_95	[p3l256t266r461b336],
15	)	NN	O	)	dep	7	SENT_95	[p3l256t266r461b336],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l490t266r603b325],
17	Gutshick	NN	PERSON	gutshick	conj_and	7	SENT_95	[p3l627t267r912b325],
18	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l937t266r1049b325],
19	Sandberg	NNP	PERSON	Sandberg	conj_and	7	SENT_95	[p3l1075t267r1370b342],
20	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	19	SENT_95	[p3l1396t268r1601b338],
21	1983	CD	DATE	1983	num	22	SENT_95	[p3l1396t268r1601b338],
22	)	NN	O	)	nsubj	24	SENT_95	[p3l1396t268r1601b338],
23	have	VBP	O	have	aux	24	SENT_95	[p3l1626t268r1775b326],
24	shown	VBN	O	show	dep	33	SENT_95	[p3l1801t268r2005b327],
25	that	IN	O	that	complm	26	SENT_95	[p3l2029t269r2146b327],
26	extensive	JJ	O	extensive	dep	24	SENT_95	[p3l7t351r302b409],
27	off	IN	O	off	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l347t350r630b418],
28	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	29	SENT_95	[p3l347t350r630b418],
29	shelf	NN	O	shelf	prep_off	26	SENT_95	[p3l347t350r630b418],
30	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l347t350r630b418],
31	deep-water	JJ	O	deep-water	amod	32	SENT_95	[p3l678t351r1028b425],
32	environments	NNS	O	environment	nsubj	33	SENT_95	[p3l1069t354r1495b411],
33	existed	VBD	O	exist	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1539t354r1760b411],
34	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1804t353r2007b428],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_95	[p3l2049t355r2144b412],
36	Early	JJ	MISC	early	amod	37	SENT_95	[p3l6t434r176b508],
37	Carboniferous	NNP	MISC	Carboniferous	prep_during	33	SENT_95	[p3l199t434r647b492],
38	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l673t434r786b493],
39	stretched	VBN	O	stretch	conj_and	33	SENT_95	[p3l811t435r1091b493],
40	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1114t436r1269b493],
41	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_from	39	SENT_95	[p3l1289t436r1468b494],
42	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l1493t436r1613b494],
43	southern	JJ	O	southern	amod	44	SENT_95	[p3l1638t436r1906b495],
44	Illinois	NNP	LOCATION	Illinois	prep_into	39	SENT_95	[p3l1927t437r2144b496],
45	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l8t519r120b577],
46	Indiana	NNP	LOCATION	Indiana	prep_into	39	SENT_95	[p3l145t520r395b578],
47	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_95	[p3l145t520r395b578],

1	Examination	NN	O	examination	nsubj	12	SENT_96	[p3l423t520r826b578],
2	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l851t520r921b578],
3	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	4	SENT_96	[p3l940t521r1185b579],
4	collections	NNS	O	collection	prep_of	1	SENT_96	[p3l1209t522r1544b580],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1569t522r1724b580],
6	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_from	4	SENT_96	[p3l1744t523r1941b589],
7	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1744t523r1941b589],
8	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	prep_from	4	SENT_96	[p3l1968t523r2142b581, p3l6t606r199b673],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1968t523r2142b581, p3l6t606r199b673],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l225t606r338b664],
11	Illinois	NNP	LOCATION	Illinois	conj_and	6	SENT_96	[p3l360t607r577b665],
12	indicates	VBZ	O	indicate	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l601t607r876b665],
13	that	IN	O	that	complm	19	SENT_96	[p3l899t608r1017b665],
14	a	DT	O	a	det	18	SENT_96	[p3l1037t624r1073b665],
15	generically	RB	O	generically	advmod	16	SENT_96	[p3l1094t608r1440b682],
16	distinct	JJ	O	distinct	amod	18	SENT_96	[p3l1461t608r1690b666],
17	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	18	SENT_96	[p3l1709t608r1953b666],
18	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	nsubj	19	SENT_96	[p3l1972t608r2146b667],
19	inhabited	VBD	O	inhabit	ccomp	12	SENT_96	[p3l12t690r303b749],
20	these	DT	O	these	det	24	SENT_96	[p3l327t690r489b749],
21	deep-water	JJ	O	deep-water	amod	24	SENT_96	[p3l513t691r871b766],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l513t691r871b766],
23	starved-basin	JJ	O	starved-basin	amod	24	SENT_96	[p3l901t692r1319b751],
24	milieus	NNS	O	milieu	dobj	19	SENT_96	[p3l1344t693r1572b752],
25	during	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l1597t694r1803b769],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_96	[p3l1826t695r1922b753],
27	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	28	SENT_96	[p3l1944t696r2151b754],
28	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	prep_during	24	SENT_96	[p3l11t776r443b852],
29	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	31	SENT_96	[p3l481t778r1315b854],
30	Kinderhookian-Osagean	JJ	O	kinderhookian-osagean	amod	31	SENT_96	[p3l481t778r1315b854],
31	)	NN	O	)	dep	28	SENT_96	[p3l481t778r1315b854],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_96	[p3l481t778r1315b854],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_97	[p3l1353t780r1477b838],
2	composition	NN	O	composition	nsubj	6	SENT_97	[p3l1514t781r1902b855],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l1939t781r2009b839],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_97	[p3l2039t782r2148b840],
5	fauna	NNS	O	fauna	prep_of	2	SENT_97	[p3l11t861r187b920],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l215t863r263b920],
7	unlike	IN	O	unlike	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l294t862r489b921],
8	that	DT	O	that	prep_unlike	6	SENT_97	[p3l518t863r635b921],
9	known	VBN	O	know	dep	8	SENT_97	[p3l663t863r878b922],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l907t863r1062b922],
11	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nn	12	SENT_97	[p3l1091t864r1245b923],
12	faunas	NNS	O	fauna	prep_from	9	SENT_97	[p3l1268t865r1472b924],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l1503t866r1615b925],
14	appears	VBZ	O	appear	dep	8	SENT_97	[p3l1645t883r1883b941],
15	to	TO	O	to	aux	16	SENT_97	[p3l1913t876r1972b925],
16	have	VB	O	have	xcomp	14	SENT_97	[p3l2000t867r2149b926],
17	some	DT	O	some	det	19	SENT_97	[p3l13t964r177b1006],
18	generic	JJ	O	generic	amod	19	SENT_97	[p3l208t948r436b1022],
19	af?nities	NNS	O	af?nities	dobj	16	SENT_97	[p3l467t948r737b1007],
20	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l768t958r828b1007],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	24	SENT_97	[p3l857t949r953b1008],
22	European	JJ	O	european	amod	24	SENT_97	[p3l981t951r1284b1025],
23	Kulm	NNP	O	Kulm	nn	24	SENT_97	[p3l1313t951r1494b1009],
24	facies	NNS	O	facy	prep_to	19	SENT_97	[p3l1521t951r1718b1010],
25	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_97	[p3l1521t951r1718b1010],

1	The	DT	O	the	det	2	SENT_98	[p3l1750t952r1872b1010],
2	purpose	NN	O	purpose	nsubj	6	SENT_98	[p3l1900t969r2149b1027],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l11t1032r81b1090],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_98	[p3l106t1034r215b1091],
5	paper	NN	O	paper	prep_of	2	SENT_98	[p3l246t1050r423b1108],
6	is	VBZ	O	be	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l452t1034r501b1092],
7	to	TO	O	to	aux	8	SENT_98	[p3l533t1043r592b1092],
8	redescribe	VB	O	redescribe	ccomp	6	SENT_98	[p3l622t1035r944b1093],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_98	[p3l973t1035r1069b1093],
10	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	11	SENT_98	[p3l1098t1036r1344b1094],
11	species	NNS	O	species	dobj	8	SENT_98	[p3l1375t1037r1597b1111],
12	known	VBN	O	know	partmod	11	SENT_98	[p3l1627t1037r1843b1095],
13	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1872t1038r2027b1095],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_98	[p3l2053t1038r2149b1096],
15	Chappel	NNP	O	Chappel	nn	16	SENT_98	[p3l11t1119r271b1194],
16	Limestone	NNP	O	Limestone	prep_from	12	SENT_98	[p3l300t1120r631b1178],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l660t1120r731b1178],
18	central	JJ	O	central	amod	19	SENT_98	[p3l752t1121r962b1179],
19	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_of	16	SENT_98	[p3l990t1122r1188b1190],
20	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l990t1122r1188b1190],
21	the	DT	O	the	det	23	SENT_98	[p3l1218t1122r1313b1180],
22	Welden	NNP	PERSON	Welden	nn	23	SENT_98	[p3l1339t1122r1579b1181],
23	Limestone	NNP	PERSON	Limestone	conj_and	11	SENT_98	[p3l1607t1124r1938b1182],
24	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1964t1123r2034b1182],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_98	[p3l2053t1124r2149b1182],
26	Lawrence	NNP	O	Lawrence	nn	27	SENT_98	[p3l10t1207r321b1264],
27	Uplift	NNP	O	Uplift	prep_of	23	SENT_98	[p3l364t1207r550b1281],
28	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l593t1206r663b1265],
29	south	RB	O	south	advmod	31	SENT_98	[p3l702t1207r1120b1266],
30	?	CD	NUMBER	?	dep	31	SENT_98	[p3l702t1207r1120b1266],
31	central	JJ	O	central	amod	32	SENT_98	[p3l702t1207r1120b1266],
32	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	prep_of	27	SENT_98	[p3l1164t1208r1509b1277],
33	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1164t1208r1509b1277],
34	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1555t1209r1667b1268],
35	the	DT	O	the	det	37	SENT_98	[p3l1710t1209r1805b1267],
36	Chouteau	NNP	LOCATION	Chouteau	nn	37	SENT_98	[p3l1847t1210r2149b1269],
37	Limestone	NNP	LOCATION	Limestone	conj_and	11	SENT_98	[p3l10t1293r342b1351],
38	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l377t1293r447b1351],
39	southem	NNP	O	southem	nn	40	SENT_98	[p3l477t1294r746b1352],
40	Illinois	NNP	LOCATION	Illinois	prep_of	37	SENT_98	[p3l779t1294r1015b1363],
41	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l779t1294r1015b1363],
42	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1052t1295r1165b1354],
43	to	TO	O	to	aux	44	SENT_98	[p3l1199t1304r1259b1353],
44	discuss	VB	O	discuss	conj_and	8	SENT_98	[p3l1292t1296r1516b1354],
45	their	PRP$	O	they	poss	46	SENT_98	[p3l1551t1296r1696b1354],
46	paleozoogeo	NN	O	paleozoogeo	dep	44	SENT_98	[p3l1724t1297r2147b1372],
47	?	CD	NUMBER	?	number	48	SENT_98	[p3l1724t1297r2147b1372],
48	graphic	JJ	O	graphic	dobj	44	SENT_98	[p3l10t1379r243b1454],
49	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l274t1379r386b1437],
50	paleoenvironmental	JJ	O	paleoenvironmental	amod	51	SENT_98	[p3l414t1380r1038b1454],
51	implications	NNS	O	implication	dobj	44	SENT_98	[p3l1064t1381r1466b1456],
52	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_98	[p3l1064t1381r1466b1456],

1	This	DT	O	this	det	2	SENT_99	[p3l91t1463r235b1522],
2	study	NN	O	study	nsubjpass	4	SENT_99	[p3l273t1464r447b1538],
3	is	VBZ	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_99	[p3l482t1465r533b1522],
4	based	VBN	O	base	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l568t1465r755b1523],
5	primarily	RB	O	primarily	advmod	4	SENT_99	[p3l788t1465r1094b1540],
6	upon	IN	O	upon	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l1128t1483r1290b1541],
7	existing	VBG	O	exist	amod	9	SENT_99	[p3l1325t1466r1583b1541],
8	museum	NN	O	museum	nn	9	SENT_99	[p3l1617t1483r1896b1525],
9	collections	NNS	O	collection	prep_upon	4	SENT_99	[p3l1927t1468r2146b1526, p3l10t1550r165b1607],
10	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l200t1549r272b1607],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	14	SENT_99	[p3l299t1549r398b1608],
12	U.S.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	U.S.	nn	14	SENT_99	[p3l430t1551r570b1609],
13	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	14	SENT_99	[p3l606t1551r887b1609],
14	Museum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Museum	prep_of	9	SENT_99	[p3l920t1552r1225b1619],
15	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l920t1552r1225b1619],
16	Chicago	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chicago	nn	18	SENT_99	[p3l1259t1551r1532b1627],
17	Field	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Field	nn	18	SENT_99	[p3l1564t1552r1733b1611],
18	Museum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Museum	prep_upon	4	SENT_99	[p3l1763t1554r2052b1611],
19	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l2081t1553r2153b1611],
20	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	nn	21	SENT_99	[p3l9t1637r252b1695],
21	History	NN	ORGANIZATION	history	prep_of	18	SENT_99	[p3l282t1638r546b1712],
22	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l282t1638r546b1712],
23	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l579t1638r694b1696],
24	Carnegie	NNP	O	Carnegie	nn	25	SENT_99	[p3l723t1639r1018b1713],
25	Museum	NNP	O	Museum	conj_and	9	SENT_99	[p3l1047t1641r1334b1697],
26	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l1362t1639r1433b1697],
27	Natural	NNP	O	Natural	nn	28	SENT_99	[p3l1456t1640r1700b1698],
28	History	NN	O	history	prep_of	25	SENT_99	[p3l1728t1641r1990b1714],
29	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_99	[p3l1728t1641r1990b1714],

1	Additional	JJ	O	additional	amod	2	SENT_100	[p3l2022t1641r2145b1699, p3l10t1721r257b1780],
2	collections	NNS	O	collection	nsubjpass	4	SENT_100	[p3l281t1722r634b1781],
3	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	4	SENT_100	[p3l661t1740r818b1781],
4	made	VBN	O	make	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l841t1722r1018b1781],
5	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l1042t1723r1201b1782],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	8	SENT_100	[p3l1223t1723r1321b1782],
7	Chappel	NNP	LOCATION	Chappel	nn	8	SENT_100	[p3l1344t1724r1616b1799],
8	Limestone	NNP	LOCATION	Limestone	prep_from	4	SENT_100	[p3l1639t1725r1985b1784],
9	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l2007t1743r2149b1784],
10	San	NNP	LOCATION	San	nn	16	SENT_100	[p3l10t1809r130b1867],
11	Saba	NNP	LOCATION	Saba	nn	16	SENT_100	[p3l167t1809r341b1877],
12	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l167t1809r341b1877],
13	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	nn	16	SENT_100	[p3l380t1810r566b1868],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l604t1810r719b1868],
15	Welden	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Welden	nn	16	SENT_100	[p3l755t1810r1002b1868],
16	Limestone	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Limestone	prep_near	8	SENT_100	[p3l1038t1812r1384b1869],
17	along	IN	O	along	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l1420t1812r1600b1886],
18	J	NNP	O	J	nn	20	SENT_100	[p3l1634t1813r1665b1870],
19	ackfork	NNP	O	ackfork	nn	20	SENT_100	[p3l1668t1812r1919b1870],
20	Creek	NNP	LOCATION	Creek	prep_along	4	SENT_100	[p3l1951t1813r2148b1871],
21	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l8t1911r150b1953],
22	Ada	NNP	LOCATION	Ada	nn	24	SENT_100	[p3l174t1895r328b1963],
23	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l174t1895r328b1963],
24	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	prep_near	20	SENT_100	[p3l358t1894r700b1954],
25	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l724t1896r806b1970],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	27	SENT_100	[p3l833t1896r930b1954],
27	author	NN	O	author	agent	4	SENT_100	[p3l959t1896r1167b1954],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l1192t1897r1310b1955],
29	A.	NN	PERSON	a.	nn	30	SENT_100	[p3l1335t1898r1409b1955],
30	Kollar	NNP	PERSON	Kollar	conj_and	27	SENT_100	[p3l1441t1898r1650b1956],
31	utilizing	VBG	O	utilize	xcomp	4	SENT_100	[p3l1673t1898r1946b1973],
32	funding	NN	O	funding	dobj	31	SENT_100	[p3l1969t1898r2144b1957, p3l9t1982r111b2056],
33	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l141t1981r301b2039],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_100	[p3l330t1982r426b2040],
35	Carnegie	NNP	O	Carnegie	nn	36	SENT_100	[p3l457t1982r753b2057],
36	Museum	NNP	O	Museum	prep_from	31	SENT_100	[p3l783t1984r1070b2041],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l1099t1983r1170b2041],
38	Natural	NNP	O	Natural	nn	39	SENT_100	[p3l1195t1984r1439b2042],
39	History	NN	O	history	prep_of	36	SENT_100	[p3l1469t1985r1732b2059],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_100	[p3l1469t1985r1732b2059],

1	Terminology	NN	O	terminology	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l90t2067r511b2142],
2	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l565t2067r660b2125],
3	trilobite	NN	O	trilobite	nn	5	SENT_101	[p3l712t2068r971b2126],
4	species	NNS	O	species	nn	5	SENT_101	[p3l1025t2070r1258b2143],
5	confonns	NNS	O	confonn	prep_for	1	SENT_101	[p3l1311t2069r1619b2127],
6	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l1673t2079r1735b2128],
7	Harrington	NNP	PERSON	Harrington	prep_to	5	SENT_101	[p3l1787t2071r2146b2145],
8	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	7	SENT_101	[p3l10t2151r222b2222],
9	1959	CD	DATE	1959	num	10	SENT_101	[p3l10t2151r222b2222],
10	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_101	[p3l10t2151r222b2222],
11	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l264t2152r380b2210],
12	Richter	NNP	PERSON	Richter	conj_and	10	SENT_101	[p3l420t2152r661b2211],
13	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l700t2153r815b2212],
14	Richter	NNP	PERSON	Richter	dep	1	SENT_101	[p3l853t2153r1096b2212],
15	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	14	SENT_101	[p3l1135t2154r1367b2224],
16	1949	CD	DATE	1949	num	17	SENT_101	[p3l1135t2154r1367b2224],
17	)	NN	O	)	dep	14	SENT_101	[p3l1135t2154r1367b2224],
18	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_101	[p3l1135t2154r1367b2224],

1	Specimens	NNS	O	specimen	nsubj	2	SENT_102	[p3l1411t2155r1761b2229],
2	utilized	VBD	O	utilize	dep	7	SENT_102	[p3l1800t2156r2046b2215],
3	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l2083t2156r2144b2214],
4	this	DT	O	this	det	5	SENT_102	[p3l8t2237r122b2296],
5	study	NN	O	study	prep_in	2	SENT_102	[p3l152t2238r326b2312],
6	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	7	SENT_102	[p3l353t2256r450b2297],
7	reposited	VBN	O	reposit	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l474t2239r775b2313],
8	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l801t2240r863b2297],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_102	[p3l888t2239r986b2298],
10	Chicago	NNP	LOCATION	Chicago	nn	12	SENT_102	[p3l1011t2240r1284b2315],
11	Field	NNP	O	Field	nn	12	SENT_102	[p3l1308t2241r1477b2299],
12	Museum	NNP	O	Museum	prep_in	7	SENT_102	[p3l1501t2243r1788b2299],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l1810t2241r1883b2300],
14	Natural	NNP	O	Natural	nn	15	SENT_102	[p3l1901t2243r2144b2300],
15	History	NN	O	history	prep_of	12	SENT_102	[p3l7t2325r255b2399],
16	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	17	SENT_102	[p3l283t2325r526b2395],
17	CFM	NNP	ORGANIZATION	CFM	nsubjpass	7	SENT_102	[p3l283t2325r526b2395],
18	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	17	SENT_102	[p3l283t2325r526b2395],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l283t2325r526b2395],
20	the	DT	O	the	det	21	SENT_102	[p3l553t2325r652b2383],
21	Section	NN	O	section	appos	17	SENT_102	[p3l679t2326r922b2384],
22	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l948t2326r1020b2384],
23	Invertebrate	NNP	O	Invertebrate	nn	24	SENT_102	[p3l1039t2327r1434b2385],
24	Paleontology	NNP	O	Paleontology	prep_of	21	SENT_102	[p3l1459t2328r1890b2402],
25	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l1914t2328r1986b2386],
26	Carnegie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Carnegie	nn	27	SENT_102	[p3l2003t2329r2142b2387, p3l7t2411r184b2485],
27	Museum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Museum	prep_of	24	SENT_102	[p3l216t2413r503b2469],
28	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l532t2411r605b2469],
29	Natural	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Natural	prep_of	27	SENT_102	[p3l631t2412r874b2469],
30	History	NN	ORGANIZATION	history	nn	33	SENT_102	[p3l908t2413r1155b2486],
31	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	33	SENT_102	[p3l1189t2413r1386b2482],
32	CM	NN	O	cm	nn	33	SENT_102	[p3l1189t2413r1386b2482],
33	)	NN	O	)	dep	29	SENT_102	[p3l1189t2413r1386b2482],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l1189t2413r1386b2482],
35	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l1420t2413r1536b2471],
36	the	DT	O	the	det	40	SENT_102	[p3l1569t2413r1666b2471],
37	United	NNP	ORGANIZATION	United	nn	40	SENT_102	[p3l1698t2414r1920b2472],
38	States	NNP	ORGANIZATION	States	nn	40	SENT_102	[p3l1953t2415r2144b2472],
39	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	National	nn	40	SENT_102	[p3l7t2498r287b2556],
40	Museum	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Museum	prep_of	27	SENT_102	[p3l318t2500r606b2557],
41	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	42	SENT_102	[p3l636t2499r940b2568],
42	USNM	NNP	ORGANIZATION	USNM	dep	40	SENT_102	[p3l636t2499r940b2568],
43	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	42	SENT_102	[p3l636t2499r940b2568],
44	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_102	[p3l636t2499r940b2568],

1	This	DT	O	this	nsubj	3	SENT_103	[p3l514t2643r573b2667],
2	content	JJ	O	content	amod	1	SENT_103	[p3l583t2647r684b2667],
3	downloaded	VBN	O	download	_	0	SENT_103	[p3l693t2643r860b2667],
4	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_103	[p3l869t2643r935b2667],
5	144.92	CD	NUMBER	144.92	prep_from	3	SENT_103	[p3l947t2643r1156b2667],
6	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_103	[p3l947t2643r1156b2667],

1	l42	NN	O	l42	_	0	SENT_104	[p3l947t2643r1156b2667],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_104	[p3l947t2643r1156b2667],

1	l58	NN	O	l58	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l947t2643r1156b2667],
2	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1167t2651r1201b2667],
3	Wed	NNP	TIME	Wed	prep_on	1	SENT_105	[p3l1210t2643r1281b2671],
4	,	,	TIME	,	_	0	SENT_105	[p3l1210t2643r1281b2671],
5	8	CD	TIME	8	appos	3	SENT_105	[p3l1293t2643r1307b2667],
6	May	NNP	DATE	May	tmod	5	SENT_105	[p3l1317t2644r1379b2674],
7	2013	CD	DATE	2013	num	6	SENT_105	[p3l1390t2643r1455b2667],
8	16:24:58	CD	TIME	16:24:58	num	9	SENT_105	[p3l1469t2643r1586b2667],
9	PM	NN	TIME	pm	dep	1	SENT_105	[p3l1597t2644r1645b2667],

1	BREZINSKI	NNP	PERSON	BREZINSKI	_	0	SENT_106	[p3l364t2793r862b2823],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_106	[p3l364t2793r862b2823],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_107	[p3l364t2793r862b2823],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_107	[p3l364t2793r862b2823],

1	MISSISSIPPIAN	NNP	O	MISSISSIPPIAN	nn	2	SENT_108	[p3l364t2793r862b2823],
2	TRILOBIT	NNP	O	TRILOBIT	_	0	SENT_108	[p3l874t2793r1045b2822],
3	ES	NN	O	e	dep	2	SENT_108	[p3l1041t2793r1086b2822],
4	719	CD	NUMBER	719	dep	2	SENT_108	[p3l1738t2788r1795b2822],

1	kilometers	NNS	O	kilometer	_	0	SENT_109	[p4l1797t1090r1979b1120],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_110	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_110	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],

1	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_111	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],

1	A	DT	O	a	det	2	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
2	~	NN	O	~	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
3	/	:	O	/	punct	4	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
4	?	CD	NUMBER	?	dep	2	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
5	l	NN	O	l	dep	4	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
6	??	CD	NUMBER	??	dep	5	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
7	\	NN	O	\	dep	6	SENT_112	[p4l1146t1132r1317b1168],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l1322t1141r1404b1160],
9	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l1322t1141r1404b1160],
10	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_112	[p4l1322t1141r1404b1160],
11	?	CD	NUMBER	?	appos	2	SENT_112	[p4l1409t1114r1531b1169],
12	"	``	O	"	punct	13	SENT_112	[p4l1409t1114r1531b1169],
13	?	CD	NUMBER	?	dep	2	SENT_112	[p4l1409t1114r1531b1169],
14	\	CD	NUMBER	\	num	15	SENT_112	[p4l1409t1114r1531b1169],
15	J	NN	O	j	dep	13	SENT_112	[p4l1409t1114r1531b1169],

1	Emergent	JJ	O	emergent	amod	2	SENT_113	[p4l1587t1213r1788b1257],
2	areas	NNS	O	area	_	0	SENT_113	[p4l1811t1221r1927b1248],

1	Shelf	NN	O	shelf	nn	2	SENT_114	[p4l1589t1360r1694b1396],
2	areas	NNS	O	area	_	0	SENT_114	[p4l1714t1368r1828b1396],

1	Slope	NN	O	slope	nn	2	SENT_115	[p4l1588t1508r1703b1554],
2	areas	NNS	O	area	nsubj	3	SENT_115	[p4l1724t1519r1839b1547],
3	Starved	VBN	O	starve	_	0	SENT_115	[p4l1591t1654r1747b1701],
4	basin	NN	O	basin	nn	5	SENT_115	[p4l1771t1656r1880b1701],
5	_	NN	O	_	dobj	3	SENT_115	[p4l1960t1694r1989b1700],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_115	[p4l1960t1694r1989b1700],

1	(	NN	O	(	_	0	SENT_116	[p4l1571t1694r1668b1739],
2	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_116	[p4l1571t1694r1668b1739],
3	tniobrte	NN	O	tniobrte	nn	4	SENT_116	[p4l1688t1695r1839b1731],
4	IOC3Il	NN	O	ioc3il	prep_with	1	SENT_116	[p4l1863t1694r2056b1737],
5	?	CD	NUMBER	?	num	7	SENT_116	[p4l1863t1694r2056b1737],
6	heS	NN	O	he	nn	7	SENT_116	[p4l1863t1694r2056b1737],
7	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_116	[p4l1863t1694r2056b1737],

1	FIGURE	NN	O	figure	_	0	SENT_117	[p4l10t1857r224b1907],
2	1	CD	NUMBER	1	dep	1	SENT_117	[p4l265t1855r718b1908],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_117	[p4l265t1855r718b1908],

1	?	NN	O	?	_	0	SENT_118	[p4l265t1855r718b1908],
2	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_118	[p4l265t1855r718b1908],

1	Generalized	NNP	O	Generalized	nn	5	SENT_119	[p4l265t1855r718b1908],
2	Toumaisian	NNP	O	Toumaisian	nn	5	SENT_119	[p4l755t1855r1091b1908],
3	(	NNP	O	(	nn	5	SENT_119	[p4l1132t1856r1342b1918],
4	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	5	SENT_119	[p4l1132t1856r1342b1918],
5	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	_	0	SENT_119	[p4l1377t1854r1794b1922],
6	)	CD	NUMBER	)	num	7	SENT_119	[p4l1377t1854r1794b1922],
7	paleogeography	NN	O	paleogeography	dep	5	SENT_119	[p4l1830t1855r2147b1922, p4l77t1933r240b1999],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_119	[p4l282t1931r344b1984],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_119	[p4l381t1932r466b1983],
10	south	JJ	O	south	amod	11	SENT_119	[p4l510t1932r895b1983],
11	?	NNP	O	?	prep_of	7	SENT_119	[p4l510t1932r895b1983],
12	central	JJ	O	central	amod	14	SENT_119	[p4l510t1932r895b1983],
13	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	14	SENT_119	[p4l935t1931r1129b1983],
14	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	dep	7	SENT_119	[p4l1172t1931r1354b1983],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_119	[p4l1172t1931r1354b1983],

1	Map	NN	O	map	nsubj	2	SENT_120	[p4l1398t1933r1528b1998],
2	adapted	VBD	O	adapt	_	0	SENT_120	[p4l1568t1932r1790b1998],
3	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_120	[p4l1830t1931r1969b1983],
4	Lane	NNP	PERSON	Lane	prep_from	2	SENT_120	[p4l2007t1933r2148b1983],
5	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	4	SENT_120	[p4l80t2007r268b2069],
6	1978	CD	DATE	1978	num	7	SENT_120	[p4l80t2007r268b2069],
7	)	NN	O	)	dobj	2	SENT_120	[p4l80t2007r268b2069],
8	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_120	[p4l304t2007r405b2058],
9	Gutshick	NN	PERSON	gutshick	dobj	2	SENT_120	[p4l440t2007r700b2075],
10	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_120	[p4l733t2008r835b2058],
11	Sandberg	NNP	PERSON	Sandberg	dobj	2	SENT_120	[p4l871t2007r1137b2073],
12	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	11	SENT_120	[p4l1174t2007r1378b2069],
13	1983	CD	DATE	1983	num	14	SENT_120	[p4l1174t2007r1378b2069],
14	)	NN	O	)	dep	11	SENT_120	[p4l1174t2007r1378b2069],
15	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_120	[p4l1174t2007r1378b2069],

1	Trilobite	NNP	O	Trilobite	nn	2	SENT_121	[p4l1414t2007r1660b2058],
2	locations	NNS	O	location	nsubj	12	SENT_121	[p4l1695t2007r1950b2058],
3	A	DT	O	a	amod	2	SENT_121	[p4l1984t2009r2050b2066],
4	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l1984t2009r2050b2066],
5	B	NN	O	b	dep	3	SENT_121	[p4l2085t2008r2147b2066],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l2085t2008r2147b2066],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l80t2083r182b2133],
8	C	NN	O	c	conj_and	2	SENT_121	[p4l204t2082r249b2134],
9	are	VBP	O	be	cop	12	SENT_121	[p4l273t2097r358b2133],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_121	[p4l381t2082r466b2133],
11	Chappel	NNP	O	Chappel	nn	12	SENT_121	[p4l488t2082r727b2148],
12	Limestone	NNP	O	Limestone	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l749t2083r1052b2133],
13	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l1075t2082r1137b2133],
14	the	DT	O	the	det	16	SENT_121	[p4l1154t2082r1238b2133],
15	Llano	NNP	LOCATION	Llano	nn	16	SENT_121	[p4l1261t2082r1427b2133],
16	region	NN	O	region	prep_of	12	SENT_121	[p4l1449t2082r1631b2147],
17	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l1653t2081r1716b2134],
18	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_of	16	SENT_121	[p4l1731t2083r1911b2141],
19	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l1731t2083r1911b2141],
20	Welden	NNP	LOCATION	Welden	nn	21	SENT_121	[p4l1932t2082r2149b2134],
21	Limestone	NNP	LOCATION	Limestone	conj_and	12	SENT_121	[p4l78t2158r381b2209],
22	from	IN	O	from	prep	21	SENT_121	[p4l423t2156r561b2209],
23	near	IN	O	near	pcomp	22	SENT_121	[p4l600t2172r724b2208],
24	Ada	NNP	LOCATION	Ada	nn	26	SENT_121	[p4l763t2158r896b2216],
25	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l763t2158r896b2216],
26	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	pobj	23	SENT_121	[p4l940t2157r1253b2216],
27	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l940t2157r1253b2216],
28	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l1295t2158r1396b2208],
29	Chouteau	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Chouteau	nn	30	SENT_121	[p4l1436t2157r1710b2209],
30	Limestone	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Limestone	conj_and	12	SENT_121	[p4l1749t2158r2051b2209],
31	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	of	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l2091t2157r2153b2209],
32	Union	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Union	nn	33	SENT_121	[p4l78t2232r256b2283],
33	County	NNP	ORGANIZATION	County	prep_of	30	SENT_121	[p4l285t2231r509b2298],
34	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l285t2231r509b2298],
35	Illinois	NNP	LOCATION	Illinois	appos	33	SENT_121	[p4l538t2231r757b2290],
36	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l538t2231r757b2290],
37	respectively	RB	O	respectively	advmod	12	SENT_121	[p4l785t2231r1143b2298],
38	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l785t2231r1143b2298],
39	'	''	O	'	_	0	SENT_121	[p4l2029t2230r2031b2232],

1	PALEOGEOGRAPHIC	NNP	O	PALEOGEOGRAPHIC	nn	2	SENT_122	[p4l644t2451r1264b2494],
2	MODEL	NNP	O	MODEL	_	0	SENT_122	[p4l1291t2451r1518b2495],

1	Lane	NNP	PERSON	Lane	nsubj	22	SENT_123	[p4l93t2550r256b2606],
2	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	1	SENT_123	[p4l290t2548r524b2618],
3	1978	CD	DATE	1978	num	4	SENT_123	[p4l290t2548r524b2618],
4	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_123	[p4l290t2548r524b2618],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l290t2548r524b2618],
6	Lane	NNP	PERSON	Lane	nn	9	SENT_123	[p4l559t2550r721b2606],
7	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l754t2549r870b2606],
8	De	NNP	PERSON	De	nn	9	SENT_123	[p4l902t2550r996b2606],
9	Keyser	NNP	PERSON	Keyser	nsubj	22	SENT_123	[p4l1029t2549r1260b2622],
10	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	12	SENT_123	[p4l1291t2549r1524b2618],
11	1980	CD	DATE	1980	num	12	SENT_123	[p4l1291t2549r1524b2618],
12	)	NN	O	)	dep	9	SENT_123	[p4l1291t2549r1524b2618],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l1291t2549r1524b2618],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l1560t2550r1675b2607],
15	Gutshick	NNP	PERSON	Gutshick	nsubj	22	SENT_123	[p4l1707t2549r2003b2607],
16	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l2033t2550r2149b2607],
17	Sandberg	NNP	PERSON	Sandberg	conj_and	15	SENT_123	[p4l13t2631r319b2706],
18	(	CD	NUMBER	(	num	20	SENT_123	[p4l352t2630r565b2700],
19	1983	CD	DATE	1983	num	20	SENT_123	[p4l352t2630r565b2700],
20	)	NN	O	)	dep	15	SENT_123	[p4l352t2630r565b2700],
21	have	VBP	O	have	aux	22	SENT_123	[p4l596t2632r751b2689],
22	outlined	VBN	O	outline	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l782t2631r1050b2689],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_123	[p4l1080t2632r1177b2689],
24	regional	JJ	O	regional	amod	25	SENT_123	[p4l1207t2631r1474b2706],
25	paleogeography	NN	O	paleogeography	dobj	22	SENT_123	[p4l1503t2632r2026b2706],
26	for	IN	O	for	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l2055t2632r2150b2690],
27	Lower	NNP	MISC	Lower	nn	29	SENT_123	[p4l10t2717r224b2774],
28	Mississippian	NNP	MISC	Mississippian	nn	29	SENT_123	[p4l251t2715r703b2790],
29	strata	NN	O	stratum	prep_for	22	SENT_123	[p4l733t2725r909b2774],
30	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l935t2715r1007b2773],
31	the	DT	O	the	det	35	SENT_123	[p4l1029t2716r1127b2774],
32	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	35	SENT_123	[p4l1154t2716r1377b2774],
33	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	nn	35	SENT_123	[p4l1406t2717r1597b2774],
34	(	NNP	O	(	nn	35	SENT_123	[p4l1626t2717r1777b2791],
35	Fig	NNP	O	Fig	prep_of	29	SENT_123	[p4l1626t2717r1777b2791],
36	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_123	[p4l1626t2717r1777b2791],

1	1	CD	NUMBER	1	_	0	SENT_124	[p4l1815t2717r1890b2785],
2	)	NN	O	)	dep	1	SENT_124	[p4l1815t2717r1890b2785],
3	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_124	[p4l1815t2717r1890b2785],

1	During	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l1918t2716r2149b2791],
2	much	JJ	O	much	prep_during	11	SENT_125	[p4l11t2800r192b2857],
3	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l225t2800r297b2857],
4	the	DT	O	the	det	5	SENT_125	[p4l326t2800r423b2857],
5	Paleozoic	JJ	MISC	paleozoic	prep_of	2	SENT_125	[p4l456t2800r793b2867],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l456t2800r793b2867],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_125	[p4l828t2800r926b2857],
8	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	9	SENT_125	[p4l958t2800r1181b2858],
9	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	nsubjpass	11	SENT_125	[p4l1216t2800r1407b2858],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_125	[p4l1440t2817r1565b2857],
11	transected	VBN	O	transect	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l1599t2800r1930b2858],
12	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l1960t2801r2040b2874],
13	an	DT	O	a	det	16	SENT_125	[p4l2074t2817r2149b2858],
14	intermittently	RB	O	intermittently	advmod	15	SENT_125	[p4l11t2884r456b2957],
15	emergent	JJ	O	emergent	amod	16	SENT_125	[p4l493t2893r800b2959],
16	area	NN	O	area	agent	11	SENT_125	[p4l833t2901r970b2941],
17	that	WDT	O	that	nsubj	18	SENT_125	[p4l1004t2884r1127b2942],
18	extended	VBD	O	extend	rcmod	16	SENT_125	[p4l1160t2885r1456b2942],
19	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l1491t2884r1650b2941],
20	northem	NNP	O	northem	nn	22	SENT_125	[p4l1684t2884r1959b2942],
21	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	22	SENT_125	[p4l1995t2885r2147b2942],
22	Mexico	NNP	LOCATION	Mexico	prep_from	18	SENT_125	[p4l10t2969r259b3026],
23	northeastward	RB	O	northeastward	advmod	18	SENT_125	[p4l288t2968r754b3027],
24	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l782t2968r1036b3043],
25	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_125	[p4l1063t2969r1161b3027],
26	central	JJ	O	central	amod	28	SENT_125	[p4l1190t2970r1410b3027],
27	United	NNP	LOCATION	United	nn	28	SENT_125	[p4l1438t2969r1660b3027],
28	States	NNPS	LOCATION	States	prep_through	18	SENT_125	[p4l1689t2970r1880b3027],
29	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l1907t2978r1969b3027],
30	Wisconsin	NNP	LOCATION	Wisconsin	prep_to	28	SENT_125	[p4l1995t2970r2146b3027, p4l11t3052r240b3109],
31	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_125	[p4l1995t2970r2146b3027, p4l11t3052r240b3109],

1	During	IN	O	during	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l270t3052r501b3127],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_126	[p4l527t3052r625b3110],
3	Early	JJ	O	early	amod	4	SENT_126	[p4l649t3053r826b3126],
4	Mississippian	NNP	O	Mississippian	prep_during	16	SENT_126	[p4l851t3052r1303b3127],
5	this	DT	O	this	det	7	SENT_126	[p4l1328t3052r1442b3110],
6	positive	JJ	O	positive	amod	7	SENT_126	[p4l1466t3052r1726b3127],
7	area	NN	O	area	nsubjpass	16	SENT_126	[p4l1751t3070r1901b3119],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l1751t3070r1901b3119],
9	known	VBN	O	know	partmod	7	SENT_126	[p4l1924t3053r2148b3110],
10	as	IN	O	as	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l11t3153r77b3193],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	13	SENT_126	[p4l120t3136r218b3193],
12	Transcontinental	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Transcontinental	nn	13	SENT_126	[p4l261t3136r807b3194],
13	Arch	NNP	ORGANIZATION	Arch	prep_as	9	SENT_126	[p4l850t3136r1030b3202],
14	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l850t3136r1030b3202],
15	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	16	SENT_126	[p4l1075t3153r1201b3194],
16	rimmed	VBN	O	rim	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l1243t3136r1497b3194],
17	by	IN	O	by	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l1538t3137r1619b3209],
18	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nn	19	SENT_126	[p4l1663t3136r1825b3194],
19	areas	NNS	O	area	agent	16	SENT_126	[p4l1862t3153r2026b3194],
20	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l2069t3154r2148b3194],
21	which	WDT	O	which	rel	25	SENT_126	[p4l10t3219r209b3277],
22	carbonate	NN	O	carbonate	nn	23	SENT_126	[p4l243t3220r561b3278],
23	rocks	NNS	O	rock	nsubjpass	25	SENT_126	[p4l595t3220r770b3278],
24	were	VBD	O	be	auxpass	25	SENT_126	[p4l804t3237r963b3278],
25	deposited	VBN	O	deposit	rcmod	19	SENT_126	[p4l997t3220r1326b3295],
26	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_126	[p4l997t3220r1326b3295],

1	On	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l1364t3221r1462b3278],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	4	SENT_127	[p4l1496t3220r1594b3278],
3	east	JJ	O	east	amod	4	SENT_127	[p4l1627t3230r1754b3279],
4	side	NN	O	side	prep_on	12	SENT_127	[p4l1788t3221r1917b3278],
5	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l1950t3221r2022b3279],
6	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_127	[p4l2050t3221r2147b3279],
7	arch	NN	O	arch	prep_of	4	SENT_127	[p4l12t3303r168b3369],
8	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l12t3303r168b3369],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	11	SENT_127	[p4l195t3304r294b3361],
10	Burlington	NNP	LOCATION	Burlington	nn	11	SENT_127	[p4l319t3304r675b3378],
11	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nsubj	12	SENT_127	[p4l701t3304r863b3362],
12	extended	VBN	O	extend	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l882t3305r1177b3362],
13	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l1201t3304r1361b3361],
14	southeast	NN	O	southeast	nn	15	SENT_127	[p4l1385t3304r1688b3362],
15	Iowa	NNP	LOCATION	Iowa	prep_from	12	SENT_127	[p4l1710t3307r1874b3362],
16	through	IN	O	through	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l1896t3305r2149b3379],
17	Missouri	NNP	LOCATION	Missouri	prep_through	12	SENT_127	[p4l11t3387r301b3445],
18	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l343t3387r468b3444],
19	northeastern	JJ	O	northeastern	amod	20	SENT_127	[p4l511t3387r916b3445],
20	Oklahoma	NNP	LOCATION	Oklahoma	prep_into	12	SENT_127	[p4l957t3388r1314b3445],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_127	[p4l957t3388r1314b3445],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_128	[p4l1358t3389r1425b3446],
2	north	RB	O	north	advmod	4	SENT_128	[p4l1466t3388r1900b3446],
3	?	CD	NUMBER	?	npadvmod	4	SENT_128	[p4l1466t3388r1900b3446],
4	central	JJ	O	central	amod	5	SENT_128	[p4l1466t3388r1900b3446],
5	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	Texas	prep_in	11	SENT_128	[p4l1941t3389r2146b3455],
6	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_128	[p4l1941t3389r2146b3455],
7	the	DT	O	the	det	9	SENT_128	[p4l10t3473r108b3531],
8	Chappel	NNP	O	Chappel	nn	9	SENT_128	[p4l138t3473r410b3549],
9	Limestone	NNP	O	Limestone	nsubjpass	11	SENT_128	[p4l440t3474r786b3533],
10	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	11	SENT_128	[p4l816t3491r941b3532],
11	deposited	VBN	O	deposit	_	0	SENT_128	[p4l971t3474r1301b3550],
12	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_128	[p4l971t3474r1301b3550],

1	These	DT	O	these	det	4	SENT_129	[p4l1333t3474r1528b3533],
2	thick	JJ	O	thick	amod	4	SENT_129	[p4l1556t3473r1721b3533],
3	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nn	4	SENT_129	[p4l1748t3474r1909b3533],
4	deposits	NNS	O	deposit	nsubj	15	SENT_129	[p4l1931t3475r2146b3551, p4l11t3556r104b3622],
5	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l1931t3475r2146b3551, p4l11t3556r104b3622],
6	which	WDT	O	which	nsubjpass	8	SENT_129	[p4l137t3556r337b3614],
7	are	VBP	O	be	auxpass	8	SENT_129	[p4l369t3573r465b3613],
8	known	VBN	O	know	rcmod	4	SENT_129	[p4l494t3557r718b3614],
9	only	RB	O	only	advmod	8	SENT_129	[p4l748t3558r891b3630],
10	from	IN	O	from	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l922t3557r1081b3614],
11	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_129	[p4l1109t3557r1208b3615],
12	subsurface	NN	O	subsurface	prep_from	8	SENT_129	[p4l1239t3557r1606b3624],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l1239t3557r1606b3624],
14	are	VBP	O	be	cop	15	SENT_129	[p4l1639t3575r1734b3615],
15	coeval	JJ	O	coeval	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l1764t3559r1976b3615],
16	with	IN	O	with	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l2004t3558r2148b3616],
17	a	DT	O	a	det	19	SENT_129	[p4l12t3657r47b3697],
18	thin	JJ	O	thin	amod	19	SENT_129	[p4l79t3640r205b3698],
19	(	NN	O	(	nn	24	SENT_129	[p4l241t3641r299b3709],
20	1	CD	NUMBER	1	num	21	SENT_129	[p4l241t3641r299b3709],
21	meter	NN	O	meter	npadvmod	22	SENT_129	[p4l340t3649r526b3698],
22	thick	JJ	O	thick	amod	24	SENT_129	[p4l560t3641r748b3709],
23	)	NN	O	)	nn	24	SENT_129	[p4l560t3641r748b3709],
24	limestone	NN	O	limestone	prep_with	15	SENT_129	[p4l785t3641r1102b3699],
25	bearing	VBG	O	bear	xcomp	15	SENT_129	[p4l1135t3641r1380b3716],
26	the	DT	O	the	det	28	SENT_129	[p4l1414t3642r1512b3699],
27	same	JJ	O	same	amod	28	SENT_129	[p4l1547t3658r1712b3699],
28	name	NN	O	name	dobj	25	SENT_129	[p4l1746t3659r1922b3699],
29	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l1955t3643r2017b3699],
30	the	DT	O	the	det	32	SENT_129	[p4l2051t3642r2147b3700],
31	Llano	NNP	LOCATION	Llano	nn	32	SENT_129	[p4l11t3725r200b3783],
32	region	NN	O	region	prep_in	25	SENT_129	[p4l242t3725r452b3799],
33	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l494t3725r566b3783],
34	the	DT	O	the	det	36	SENT_129	[p4l602t3725r701b3783],
35	south-central	JJ	O	south-central	amod	36	SENT_129	[p4l745t3725r1170b3784],
36	part	NN	O	part	prep_of	32	SENT_129	[p4l1211t3734r1339b3800],
37	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l1380t3726r1452b3784],
38	the	DT	O	the	det	39	SENT_129	[p4l1488t3726r1585b3784],
39	state	NN	O	state	prep_of	36	SENT_129	[p4l1630t3736r1792b3784],
40	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_129	[p4l1630t3736r1792b3784],

1	In	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_130	[p4l1838t3728r1904b3784],
2	southcentral	JJ	O	southcentral	pobj	1	SENT_130	[p4l1948t3727r2147b3785, p5l10t11r231b68],

1	New	NNP	LOCATION	New	nn	2	SENT_131	[p5l259t11r411b68],
2	Mexico	NNP	LOCATION	Mexico	nsubj	16	SENT_131	[p5l439t11r708b77],
3	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l439t11r708b77],
4	near	IN	O	near	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l737t28r878b69],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	7	SENT_131	[p5l902t11r1001b68],
6	southern	JJ	O	southern	amod	7	SENT_131	[p5l1030t11r1309b69],
7	terminus	NN	O	terminus	prep_near	16	SENT_131	[p5l1337t11r1622b70],
8	of	IN	O	of	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l1649t12r1721b70],
9	the	DT	O	the	det	10	SENT_131	[p5l1741t12r1838b69],
10	arch	NN	O	arch	prep_of	7	SENT_131	[p5l1865t13r2021b79],
11	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l1865t13r2021b79],
12	the	DT	O	the	det	15	SENT_131	[p5l2050t12r2148b70],
13	Lake	NNP	LOCATION	Lake	nn	15	SENT_131	[p5l10t95r172b152],
14	Valley	NNP	LOCATION	Valley	nn	15	SENT_131	[p5l203t96r412b169],
15	shelf	NN	O	shelf	nsubj	16	SENT_131	[p5l444t95r607b153],
16	passed	VBD	O	pass	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l629t96r848b169],
17	southward	RB	O	southward	advmod	16	SENT_131	[p5l879t95r1219b154],
18	into	IN	O	into	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l1247t96r1372b154],
19	oceanic	JJ	O	oceanic	amod	20	SENT_131	[p5l1402t96r1649b154],
20	basin	NN	O	basin	prep_into	16	SENT_131	[p5l1677t97r1867b154],
21	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_131	[p5l1677t97r1867b154],

1	Bordering	VBG	O	border	csubj	12	SENT_132	[p5l1898t97r2146b154, p5l11t178r113b252],
2	the	DT	O	the	det	3	SENT_132	[p5l152t178r250b236],
3	arch	NN	O	arch	dobj	1	SENT_132	[p5l290t178r428b236],
4	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l468t196r548b236],
5	the	DT	O	the	det	6	SENT_132	[p5l587t178r686b236],
6	southwest	NN	O	southwest	prep_on	1	SENT_132	[p5l726t179r1053b236],
7	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l1090t179r1152b236],
8	Arizona	NNP	LOCATION	Arizona	prep_in	6	SENT_132	[p5l1189t178r1454b237],
9	was	VBD	O	be	cop	12	SENT_132	[p5l1491t196r1615b237],
10	the	DT	O	the	det	12	SENT_132	[p5l1654t179r1752b237],
11	EscabrosaRedwall	NNP	O	EscabrosaRedwall	nn	12	SENT_132	[p5l1790t180r2146b238, p5l10t263r281b320],
12	shelf	NN	O	shelf	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l307t263r480b330],
13	,	,	O	,	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l307t263r480b330],
14	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l508t264r624b321],
15	farther	RBR	O	farther	advmod	27	SENT_132	[p5l647t263r866b321],
16	to	TO	O	to	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l888t273r949b321],
17	the	DT	O	the	det	18	SENT_132	[p5l974t263r1071b321],
18	north	NN	O	north	prep_to	15	SENT_132	[p5l1094t264r1267b321],
19	in	IN	O	in	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l1289t264r1351b320],
20	Wyoming	NNP	LOCATION	Wyoming	prep_in	18	SENT_132	[p5l1372t264r1696b338],
21	and	CC	O	and	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l1720t265r1836b322],
22	Montana	NNP	LOCATION	Montana	conj_and	20	SENT_132	[p5l1857t266r2149b322],
23	the	DT	O	the	det	25	SENT_132	[p5l10t346r107b404],
24	Madison	NNP	O	Madison	nn	25	SENT_132	[p5l137t347r425b404],
25	Limestone	NNP	O	Limestone	nsubjpass	27	SENT_132	[p5l454t348r800b405],
26	was	VBD	O	be	auxpass	27	SENT_132	[p5l830t364r955b405],
27	deposited	VBN	O	deposit	conj_and	12	SENT_132	[p5l987t347r1300b422],
28	on	IN	O	on	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l1330t365r1409b405],
29	the	DT	O	the	det	31	SENT_132	[p5l1440t348r1537b405],
30	Madison	NNP	O	Madison	nn	31	SENT_132	[p5l1567t349r1853b406],
31	shelf	NN	O	shelf	prep_on	27	SENT_132	[p5l1886t348r2057b406],
32	.	.	O	.	_	0	SENT_132	[p5l1886t348r2057b406],
